### String 1 ###

Good race. I haven't been that excited in a good long while.
Now let me guess what you're thinking about. You want to be the
King of the Hill on the Metro. I'm right, aren't I?
\>Everybody who races these roads thinks that way, more or less.
Hardly anyone ever actually makes it, though. 
\>So if you're serious about it, start by taking over the C1
Loop. $\Bloodhound\*, $\Midnight Cinderella\*, and
$\Platinum Prince\* are considered the fastest racers on the C1.
\>Take them down, and you will be the de facto master there.
And you might just run across them, if you've got what it
takes.
\>And if you don't, well, then that just means you're another run
of the mill street racer, that's all\.\

### String 2 ###

Huh? You want something? Yeah, people call me $\Bloodhound\*.
I'm considered the fastest racer on the C1 Loop at this time of
night, or something.
\>What's that? You want to race me? Knock it off.
I'm in no mood for jokes. I mean, you can't mean it.
\>I'm not getting any vibes off your car, and I've got things to
do, whatever you may think. I sure haven't got time to waste
giving driving lessons to newbies.
\>But if you're serious, show me what you can do. 
You know how, right?

### String 3 ###

You've clearly shown me what you can do. I admit, I didn't
recognize you. I can hardly believe that you're that same loser
who challenged me before.
\>I guess my perceptions aren't all that reliable after all.
Racing you put me in the mind of $\King Speed\*, the legendary
street racer who used to be the fastest driver on the Metro.
\>I wonder what he's doing these days. It's been three years
since he quit street racing, and the Metro is a whole different
place now. 
\>He might have been able to bring out your full potential, 
but there's no point in wishing about what might have been.
You'll have to find your own way to the top\.\

### String 4 ###

Say, have you been over to *\Shibuya Rte. 3\* yet? What you need
now is experience. Showing your face over there wouldn't be
a bad idea\.\

### String 5 ###

You want something? Well, make it fast. I've got a conference
first thing in the morning. Don't tell me you want to race or
anything like that. Do you know who the $\Platinum Prince\* is?
\>He's a racer on with no equal on the C1 Loop at dawn.
And that's who you're attempting to challenge at this moment.
So you're wasting my time.
\>Sorry about that, but I don't see you as having what it takes
to keep up with me. And I make a point of only racing against
drivers who'd be worth the effort it take to take them down.
\>And there'd be no profit in beating you as you are now.
Come back when you've got some experience\.\

### String 6 ###

You're a far better driver than I imagined.
I'm sorry I insulted you before. 
\>Ever since $\King Speed\* quit, I've been disgusted with all the
street racers with their dreams of being the fastest on the
Metro, though they lack the ability to back up these ambitions.
\>But you're different. I can't help thinking that you might have
what it takes to be the next $\King Speed\*, though that probably
doesn't give you much comfort.
\>All you need to do is keep on driving in your own way. But if
there's ever anything I can do, just ask. I've been here a good
long while, and I know my way around.
\>I'm glad we met. Maybe my brother brought us together\.\

### String 7 ###

One more thing: *\Shibuya Rte. 3\* also has its share of street
racers who're looking to be the fastest. It'd be a great place
to build up your skills. Check it out\.\

### String 8 ###

So you're a street racer too, huh? Eh? You want to race me?
\>Oh, hey--Oops, I thought you were serious for a moment.
\>Listen, just in case you don't know, I'm known as $\Cinderella
After Midnight\* around these parts, and I'm considered the
fastest street racer on the C1 Loop during these hours.
\>I'm not trying to run you down or anything, but I don't see any
point in racing you as you are now. 
\>You see, street racing is a form of communication, and we just
don't speak the same language.
\>But we'll meet again when the time comes, you see?

### String 9 ###

Wow. I had no idea you were so fast. I see now that you can't
judge a racer by his looks alone. You remind me of a street
racer I one admired: $\King Speed\*.
\>I'm sure you've heard of him. He was the fastest racer on the
Metro. He came from nowhere one night, and was King of the Hill
before anyone knew what was happening.
\>I only saw him once myself, at dawn on the C1 Loop, near Shiba
City Park. He came up from behind me with unbelievable speed,
and was rocketing past me before I knew it.
\>He disappeared after that, but he's still my hero. Now I'm
looking forward to seeing you eventually becoming a street
racer as special as he was. Good luck!

### String 10 ###

By the way, have you been to *\Shibuya Rte. 3\* yet? 
I hear they've got some competent racers over there too Sounds 
like it'd be just the place to prove yourself\.\

### String 11 ###

Is it true that you took out C1's top three?
Either way, isn't it a little too soon to rest on your laurels?
C1 is far from being the entire Metro.
\>The C1 from the Hamazaki Bridge to the Edo Bridge, the Rte. 9 
Fukugawa from Edo Bridge to Tatsumi, and the Wangan and Rte. 11 
Daiba...
\>We call those courses the Shinkanjo, and the people racing here 
are all way above the ones racing on C1.
\>Skull Bullet, who recently came here from America, and the three 
street racers who are cooperating with him: $\Azure Sniper\*, $\Silent 
Cassiopeia\*,
\>$\Garnet Dawn\*... If you want to become famous in Shinkanjo, you'll 
come across one of them sooner or later. Good luck, even if it 
won't be enough\.\

### String 12 ###

I hear you took out one of $\Skull Bullet\*'s companions.
I see you're as full of surprises as ever.
You know, I heard a strange rumor today.
\>I thought I might as well tell you about it too. While I think 
it's a mistake, seeing as he hasn't shown himself on The Metro 
for 3 years, if it's true you should definitely go.
\>I've never met him myself, but I have a strong feeling...
If you see his driving for yourself, it'll definitely change 
your own driving.
\>The rumor says that he's on Rte. 4 PA in a blue Skyline Coupe.
I've told you all I need to. The rest is up to you\.\

### String 13 ###

So you took down another of $\Skull Bullet\*'s comrades. You just
get faster and faster. Do you remember me mentioning that you
put me in the mind of $\King Speed\*?
\>Well, every time I hear about you taking down so-and-so, or
wiping out some street racing team or other, I wonder whether
you're going to disappear one day like $\King Speed\* did.
\>The thought makes my heart ache...
\>Sorry about that. That was stupid of me. But driving is all
I've got. I just don't know what to talk about anymore. I'll
see you later. Good night\.\

### String 14 ###

So you took down another of $\Skull Bullet\*'s comrades. You just
get faster and faster. Do you remember me mentioning that you
put me in the mind of $\King Speed\*?
\>Well, every time I hear about you taking down so-and-so, or
wiping out some street racing team or other, I wonder whether
you're going to disappear one day like $\King Speed\* did.
\>The thought makes my heart ache...
\>Sorry about that. That was stupid of me. But driving is all
I've got. I just don't know what to talk about anymore. I'll
see you later. Good night\.\

### String 15 ###

So you took down another of $\Skull Bullet\*'s comrades. You just
get faster and faster. Do you remember me mentioning that you
put me in the mind of $\King Speed\*?
\>Well, every time I hear about you taking down so-and-so, or
wiping out some street racing team or other, I wonder whether
you're going to disappear one day like $\King Speed\* did.
\>The thought makes my heart ache...
\>Sorry about that. That was stupid of me. But driving is all
I've got. I just don't know what to talk about anymore. I'll
see you later. Good night\.\

### String 16 ###

Sorry about that. That was stupid of me. But driving is all
I've got. I just don't know what to talk about anymore. I'll see
you later. Good night\.\

### String 17 ###

So you've finally taken out all of $\Skull Bullet\*'s comrades.
\>You're pretty good. I bet you'll be hearing from $\Snake Eyes\*
pretty soon. You're on collision course. He was pretty fast in
the illegal street racing community, I hear. 
\>If you're not careful, he'll nail you. Speaking of which, have
you heard that $\King Speed\* is sneaking back onto the road again?
He's as mean and cold as ever.
\>He didn't even tell me he was back again. And we go back a long
way together, too, to when we were still called the $\Thirteen
Demon Lords\*. So I know him inside out.
\>And I bet he won't leave it at this, either. 
He isn't emotionally prepared for it yet, though, so it's
probably best just to let things be, for the time being\.\

### String 18 ###

I can guess what you're doing here. You want to meet $\King
Speed\*, right? Sorry to disappoint you, but he's not here. He
died three years ago. 
\>He was a better street racer than you could possibly imagine.
Why are you hung up on ghosts?
\>Get yourself enough experience, customize your car
sufficiently, and I bet you'll be better than he ever was. 
\>I don't know who put this bug in your ear, but just forget 
about $\King Speed\*\.\

### String 19 ###

I've been waiting for you. I guess I didn't give Japanese 
street racers enough credit. So I guess you already know what 
I'm doing here, right? 
\>A Japanese street racer came to my country three years ago. 
\>They called him $\Snake Eyes\*, and he took down one good American 
street racer after another, quickly making a name for himself 
in the local community. 
\>Then he and I went at it one day, and he won. I then heard he'd 
gone back to Japan, and I followed him here, in order to settle 
the score. 
\>And just when I was finally about to catch up with him, you 
came along and took $\Snake Eyes\* down before I could. That would 
cause a reassessment of what he thinks of me too. 
\>I'm tired of talking. Let's do this\.\

### String 20 ###

I hear you busted $\Skull Bullet\*. I swear, it's just one thing
after another with you. OK, OK, you got me. 
\>Once upon a time, I was known as $\King Speed\*. I don't know who 
decided it, but people said I was the fastest street racer on 
the Metro.
\>Then I figured out that such designations didn't mean squat. It
was just a puny bit of glory in an isolated community, that of
street racers competing in custom cars. Nothing more. 
\>Knowing this, if still want that title, then be my guest. But 
don't expect any help from me, either. I just wanted to tell 
you that. So long for now\.\

### String 21 ###

This is your secret hideout? It's awfully filthy, for a garage
belonging to the current big-name street racer. Oh, sorry, I
haven't introduced myself. 
\>My name's Tsutomu Shiraishi, though around these parts, I'm 
probably better known as $\Mad Murdock\*. I guess you could say 
I'm Phantom Nine\*'s ace driver. 
\>Our leader, $\Snake Eyes\*, is very interested in you since you 
took down the top three street racers on the C1 Loop, in 
addition to busting $\Skull Bullet\* himself. 
\>Maybe you didn't know this, but Phantom Nine\* is considered the 
best street racing team on the Metro Expressway, and it's 
really annoying to have street racers like you buzzing around. 
\>So if you don't quit messing around, we're gonna come looking 
for you. That's all I wanted to say\.\

### String 22 ###

You're $\King Speed\*, aren't you. I've been looking for you. I've
wanted to study your driving technique for the longest time\.\

### String 23 ###

You do know that I'm out of the street racing game, right?

### String 24 ###

That's not true. $\King Speed\* never quit street racing, even 
after you quit the Metro. Surely you know that better than
anyone else\.\

### String 25 ###

(Silence)

### String 26 ###

Do you want to hear the real reason why $\King Speed\* quit the
Metro? Three years ago, his girlfriend was suddenly
taken ill. But nothing mattered to him more than cars at that
\>time, and she died without hardly seeing him while she was in
the hospital. And I guess that once she was dead, he finally
figured out what was really important. He wasn't for anything
\>after that. His driving lost its spark, and he couldn't race
much either. He had to quit the road. But I think he's
finally figured out how he really feels about things. Take out
\>Phantom Nine\*, trash $\Snake Eyes\*, and use your driving skill to
bring $\King Speed\* back to his senses\.\

### String 27 ###

Should I... Should I go street racing once more? Do I still
deserve to hit the road again?

### String 28 ###

Are you still thrashing around about this?

### String 29 ###

Honestly..\.\

### String 30 ###

You disappoint me. You, $\King Speed\*, fastest street racer on the
Metro--you were my hero. But look at you now! 
\>Bound by the past, trying to hide from reality. Open your eyes! 
Stop breaking my heart!

### String 31 ###

(Silence)

### String 32 ###

So you're finally racing against $\Snake Eyes\*, right? I wanted to
ask you a favor. I quit street racing three years ago for
personal reasons. I'd lost my enthusiasm for street racing. 
\>I figured I'd never drive on the Metro again. But then, I met 
you, with your smoldering passion for street racing. 
\>I drove to the Metro that day as if drawn by something, and 
after racing you, I realized that my own passion for street 
racing hadn't been entirely extinguished after all. 
\>I can't lie to myself anymore. So take $\Snake Eyes\* down, and 
show me what street racing is really all about!

### String 33 ###

Here you are at last. I've waited so long for this. I was beaten
by another street racer five years ago, on this spot. He went on
to become King of the Hill on the Metro. They called
\>him $\King Speed\*. I went to America to improve my skills, and not
a day went by but that I didn't think of him. Then, after I came
back to Japan, I heard the rumors that he'd quit the Metro.
\>was stunned. The last five years of my life had been for
nothing. Then I found out about you, and something about you put
me in the mind of $\King Speed\* himself, even if your car or your
\>driving technique weren't the same. I've waited, and waited, for
you to accumulate ability on a par with $\King Speed\*, to kick
$\Skull Bullet\* to the curb, and run Phantom Nine\* off the road. 
\>$\King Speed\* may have thought he was supporting you, but that's 
not true. I made you what you are, and you exist solely for me 
to take you down! You ready? Make it good for me\.\

### String 34 ###

Good race. Watching you gave me a powerful feeling. And I
finally realized, even if after the fact, that this isn't about
logic. 
\>In the three years since I left, I forgot that what I might be 
driving for, or where I might be heading to, was totally 
irrelevant. 
\>What matters is the determination to keep on racing. And you 
taught me that, for which I must thank you. So, thank you. 
\>I hope we'll drive together again sometime. When next we meet, 
it'll be on the Metro\.\

### String 35 ###

