### String 1 ###

You're more likely to hit interference from other 
cars when yourace at night, because that's when you 
get the most traffic. 
\>But even a car with a low-powered engine might still 
have a shot against more powerful cars, if its driver 
can turn traffic conditions like these to his advantage\.\

### String 2 ###

Night time's the right time for racing, that's what I
say. 
\>I mean, you get enough cars on the road to keep you from 
wiping out, but not so many that they get in your way. 
\>That makes it the most demanding time, though, in terms 
of driving skills. So watch it. All the good drivers 
come out at night\.\

### String 3 ###

You can get up to some decent speeds around
daybreak, because there aren't many other cars on 
the road. 
\>But that also means it's when you're more likely to run 
into guys who don't stop for nothing\.\

### String 4 ###

