### String 1 ###

When I race, the more competitive I feel, the hotter I get,
until I'm trading paint. I bet you know what that's like, right?
\>There do seem to be some street racers on the Metro who hardly 
ever seem to hit walls, though. 
\>Such racers can evidently get practically godlike *\handles\*, and 
someday, I'd like to have a handle like that myself. I bet
they're really stylish\.\

### String 2 ###

Buy a street racing team leader's car, and put that team's
sticker on it. I bet you'll get an interesting *\handle\*--nahh,
just "Patches" or something like that, really\.\

### String 3 ###

Street racing should be good, clean fun, by following the rules!
That's what it's all about, right? I can't stand guys who drive
the wrong way! 
\>And they can be spotted right away, because they get special 
*\handles\* to identify them. You need to watch your step too\.\

### String 4 ###

Aw, no, how could this happen? I know I've been on a losing
streak lately, but that's no reason for people to slap a *\handle\*
like that on me! 
\>What kind of *\handle\*, you ask? I'd die of embarrassment if I 
tried to say it aloud!

### String 5 ###

I race until late at night, so I can only go driving around this
time. Consequently, people have started using a particular
*\handle\* to refer to me. 
\>I've been deliberately showing up late at night so I could get 
just such a handle. I hope people will notice that before too 
much longer\.\

### String 6 ###

I have had it with all the rude street racers out there! I got
so mad I nearly hit the horn. But I didn't, because if you do
that too much, you get a nasty *\handle\*. 
\>You'd better not lean on the horn too much either\.\

### String 7 ###

You're working so hard that I'm gonna give you a tip about how
to deal with Shinjuku Rte. 4! 
\>The key place there is right after you reach the Shinjuku exit, 
especially the Shinjuku Station roundabout! You need expert 
driving skills to navigate those narrow streets at top speed! 
\>But if you can do it, you'll be a hero! A hero, I say!

### String 8 ###

Ack! Look at the time! Once again, I've raced straight through
to morning!

### String 9 ###

Have you heard of "overhang"? That's the part of the chassis
that sticks out over the tires. The weight of this part of the
car affects the car's performance. 
\>It's like a crowbar and a hammer of the same weight. They don't 
have the same heft. 
\>In the same way, a car's overhang weight can make its front 
swing when you turn a corner, or otherwise affect the handling 
or steering. 
\>You can improve these various characteristics by lightening the 
overhang, either by using a carbon shell hood, or by using 
lightweight bumpers, or even lighter weight engine components. 
\>Even lighter weight headlights can help\.\

### String 10 ###

Small, lightweight chassis, rear-wheel drive, and 250
horsepower: only the Nissan Silvia gives this kind of driving
pleasure. 
\>Driving a Silvia feels like you're directly plugged in to the 
car itself. It shifts smoothly, making changing gears good. 
\>I'm so happy that somebody made a car that's such a pleasure to 
drive. And I like that wedge-shaped notch-back coupe styling, 
too. Everything about this car is good, really\.\

### String 11 ###

The WRX kicks ass at 4000rpm and up! And it keeps the ponies
coming even if you understeer in a turn. That two-liter turbo is
the ultimate!

### String 12 ###

If you're short on cash, I recommend starting by beefing up your
engine's systems. Things like the suspension or the clutch can
wait, though you'll have to get around to them eventually\.\

### String 13 ###

If you're going to run a series of races, one more thing you
need to keep in mind is when to hit the nitro. 
\>You don't want to overuse it in your first race, only to have 
your engine overheat just when you need it most. That is no fun. 
\>It's when you're running a series of races that you most need to 
keep your cool\.\

### String 14 ###

If you really want to beat your opponents in the turns, you need
to know about pedal work, not just staying on the line. Ideally,
you want to go slow into the curve, and be first out again.
\>Yeah. Me, I can't do it\.\

### String 15 ###

Having a camber angle would be really cool, you know? I really
want tires angled way out. It'd be just the thing for a VIP car.
Oh, and I've gotta have tassels. 
\>No two ways about it, they've gotta be hanging off the car's 
roof. Oh yeah, that's it all right... Now as to the car itself
... I wonder if anybody would sell me a black Nissan Cima...


### String 16 ###

It isn't easy configuring settings. It takes some delicacy. You
have to do it a little at a time, or you never know what might
happen. Are you adjusting your car's settings? 
\>You can start by firming up the dampers and stabilizers to give 
your car a solid ride. 
\>But you have to be careful not to firm them up too much, or else 
you'll have a hard time driving the car instead. 
\>Then you can also improve the ride by lowering the chassis, and
finish up by adjusting the springs to taste. I can't say these
will work in all circumstances, but it might be worth a try\.\

### String 17 ###

Are you the street racer who took down $\Snake Eyes\*? 
\>I quit the Metro after $\King Speed\* stepped down, but I decided to
start racing again when I heard the stories going around about
you. In you, I've finally found something to strive for. 
\>And one day, I will take you down! So keep racing until that day 
comes\.\

### String 18 ###

I just met an old friend of mine, over at the Rte. 4 Parking
Area: Phantom Nine\*'s $\Namahage\*. I don't know why he's racing with
$\Snake Eyes\*, but I figure he's got his reasons. 
\>He runs silent and deep, he does. Don't let your guard down 
around him. You might run into him if you take down all of the 
street racing teams on Rte. 4\.\

### String 19 ###

Hey, that Nissan Skyline Coupe... Was that $\King Speed\* at the
wheel? Nahh, couldn't be. I mean, he's supposed to have died
three years ago\.\

### String 20 ###

Have you heard of $\Wolves' Requiem\*? He's a street racer who shows
up frequently on Rte. 4. *\He sticks strictly to cars off the
factory floor\*. 
\>Word has it he refuses to race anyone driving a custom car\.\

### String 21 ###

I hear that $\Mosquito Lemon\*, who races on Rte. 4, is thinking of
getting a new car, and he's looking for any racers on that road
who *\sell cars\* frequently\.\

### String 22 ###

$\Iron Racer\*, who drives along Rte. 4, is a regular bundle of
nerves. 
\>He says he won't go the Metro if there are any drivers there who 
are blasting *\music\* from their car stereos, because it distracts 
him\.\

### String 23 ###

Seems that $\King Of Eden\* is thinking of buying a new car sometime
soon. I hear he goes to Rte. 4 if he hears that there's an RX-8
there that's got less than *\62mi\* on its odometer\.\

### String 24 ###

$\Loyal Knight\*, who hangs out at the Yoyogi Parking Area,
apparently has over $\621mi\* on his car's odometer. And he says
he'll only race against other drivers who've got similar mileage\.\

### String 25 ###

If you want to race $\Gentle Rain\*, I suggest you *\customize your
car's chassis to the max\*. 
\>He's a metalworker, you see, so he tracks down news about 
heavily tricked-out cars and heads for Rte. 4\.\

### String 26 ###

I hear that $\Last Flight\* always races down Rte. 4 before a
flight. Seems he tries to win as *\quickly\* as possible, so that
he'll be in time for take-off\.\

### String 27 ###

$\Panel Bomber\* believes in horsepower over all else. He keeps
saying at the Yoyogi Parking Area that he doesn't like racing
against cars that don't even have *\400 ponies\*\.\

### String 28 ###

$\Crybaby\*'s got some nerve! I went all the way to the Yoyogi
Parking Area to race him, only to have him say, "I don't feel
like racing anyone whose car isn't *\turbocharged\*."
\> 
What's wrong with a NA car, I ask you?!

### String 29 ###

$\Stalking Hammer\*, who races down Rte. 4, appears to be stymied
as to what make of car to choose, yet again. 
\>I hear he's racing the Metro in search of cars whose owners like 
them so much that they'd *\buy another one\*\.\

### String 30 ###

They say that programmers are all about numbers, and $\West
Shinjuku Assembler\*, who hangs out at the Yoyogi Parking Area, is
no exception. 
\>To hear him tell it, he doesn't like racing against drivers who 
don't put *\extra meters\* on their cars. He thinks they're 
slovenly\.\

### String 31 ###

You can tell just by looking that $\Matashichi the First\* is a
wannabe. 
\>The other day, I saw him at the Yoyogi Parking Area going around 
asking everybody, "Who the hell are these Phantom Nine\* guys, 
anyway?"

### String 32 ###

$\Matashichi the Second\*, who racers Rte. 4, is always quarreling
with $\Matashichi the First\*. But in reality, he actually looks up
to him as his mentor, don't you think? 
\>I mean, he goes around saying that "if my mentor gets taken out, 
I'll be there for him."

### String 33 ###

The comedy duo of Maebashi and Hiranishi, who race down Rte. 4,
say they're trying to make connections with people in the biz so
they can make their big break. 
\>The other day, they asked me if I knew anybody on The Bone\*\.\

### String 34 ###

$\Maebashi\* and $\Hiranishi\*, who are part of the Wanderers street
racing team, are a stand-up comedy duo from Kansai. Their timing
on the Metro is perfect. 
\>$\Maebashi\* starts the race with the set-up, and $\Hiranishi\* delivers 
the punchline. Established performers say ironically that their 
timing is better on the road than on stage

### String 35 ###

The Nayuta Team name was apparently chosen from symbols that
signify "infinity". 
\>They're mad about numbers, and it's said that they care more 
about getting accurate measurements than racing. 
\>Their cars have all been optimized for their respective drivers, 
though, like top speed, torque, and weight reductions.
So they get decent racing results too\.\

### String 36 ###

Have you raced against Asian Ages\*? It's a racing team made up of
racers from China, South Korea, and India. 
\>$\Black Dragon\*, their leader, is a veteran street racer on the 
Metro, while $\Tiger of Light\*, his deputy, is an up-and-comer on 
the South Korean circuit. 
\>And $\Elephant Emperor\*, from India, is a customizing genius. Seems 
he configures all their settings\.\

### String 37 ###

Yes, Urban Stars\* spends more money as a team on customization
than anyone else on the Metro. 
\>They looked at my jalopy and said, "Money talks when it comes to 
customization."
That burned me but good! I'll trash them next time I see them!

### String 38 ###

Man! I lost to Urban Stars\*! Maybe money IS what counts when
it comes to customization after all\.\

### String 39 ###

I hear that Three Dragon Kings\* (D3), Nagoya's fastest street
racers, have come to the Metro. Somebody's seen him on Rte. 3. 
\>According to some guys who trekked to Nagoya, they race one 
after another: $\The Rook\* first, $\The Bishop\* second, and $\the Knight\* 
third. 
\>Their cars are apparently very powerful, with tremendous 
acceleration. You're liable to meet them, like it or not, if you 
take down all the street racing teams on Rte. 3\.\

### String 40 ###

Have you heard the rumors about this incredible street racing
team from Osaka? That's right, No Loser\* is apparently popping up
on Rte. 4. 
\>Word is they've already busted up a bunch of cars, which fits 
their reputation as best street racing team on their home turf, 
the Osaka Ring Road. 
\>We Metro locals have got to show them who's boss\.\

### String 41 ###

Rumor has it that $\Tiger of Wind\* and $\Pink Dragon\*, two members of
the Asian Ages\* street racing team, don't get along. 
\>Don't you believe it. The other day, they came after me in a 
perfect one-two combination and blew me away\.\

### String 42 ###

I hear that Urban Stars\*' $\Spiral Blade\* is a politician with one
of the main parties. Seems his secretary is also on the team,
with the handle of "$\Unseen Shield\*." 
\>And this $\Unseen Shield\* gives stealthy support when $\Spiral Blade\* 
is racing, so they say\.\

### String 43 ###

No Loser\* is famous for having their top three members race one
after another. 
\>$\Chaotic Instigator\* charges in first, followed by $\Nuclear Warhead 
of Terror\*, and $\Naniwa's Warship\* bringing up the rear. 
\>The power they show is amazing. 
It must take a fair amount of nerve to race them\.\

### String 44 ###

I am most satisfied with the way you drive. I look forward to
racing you again. If possible, I want to take you down when next
we meet\.\

### String 45 ###

I lightened the weight of my car to this extent, and yet, I
still couldn't win... Inconceivable! Please race me again!

### String 46 ###

My intake efficiency was perfect, so it makes no sense that I
should have lost. No! It couldn't be that my luck is running
out, could it?!

### String 47 ###

I realized something while racing you. 
\>While nothing could be better than having perfect braking, one 
can lose races that one should have won if one puts the brakes 
on one's heart too strongly. 
\>I will try being more aggressive when I take the curves in my 
next race\.\

### String 48 ###

I met $\Tiger of Light\* right after the street racing team I'd been
on disbanded. When I saw him drive, I recalled the man who was
once called the fastest racer on the Metro. 
\>I mean, I sensed that unbounded potential, the unfinished 
aspects, in him. He was the first one that came to mind when I 
decided to put a new street racing team together. 
\>I figured we could do some interesting stuff. But I also know 
that even though we may be teammates, we'll never be partners. 
Someday, we'll have to race one another\.\

### String 49 ###

I met $\Black Dragon\* when I first came to the Metro
from South Korea. I'd never seen a street racer both so
magnificent and so clever. 
\>We soon formed a rivalry: he'd boost his horsepower, and so 
would I. He'd take a curve as tightly as he could, and I'd shave 
it even closer. Nowadays, though, we have a truce. 
\>There's $\Snake Eyes\*, who wiped out the street racing team that 
$\Black Dragon\* used to belong to. And there's a new street racer 
out there too, who's gunning for $\Snake Eyes\*. 
\>So I didn't hesitate to team up with $\Black Dragon\*. If anything, 
I'm proud to team up with a street racer of his caliber. And one
day, we'll have it out, once and for all\.\

### String 50 ###

$\Tiger of Light\* is a truly terrific street racer. He introduced
me to the joys of street racing. I feel, however, that one day I
must inevitably surpass him. 
\>Such is the law of this place: there can only be one at the top. 
When the time comes for us to race one another, I will face 
him with all that I have. 
\>I will draw upon all that I have learned from him. It will be 
the highest tribute that I can pay\.\

### String 51 ###

$\Black Dragon\* and I go way back. We were on the same team before
this one. He hasn't changed in the slightest. The only thing on
his mind is how to drive faster than anybody else. 
\>I can't help thinking that he's gotten even bigger by teaming up 
with $\Tiger of Light\*. I suspect that he needs something to give 
him a leg up in the world, more than anything else\.\

### String 52 ###

When I was in college, I did an exchange program in Japan, and
my current team leader helped me out in a lot of ways during
that time. 
\>He let me ride shotgun in his car, among other things. Even 
after I went back home, I never forgot him. 
\>I'm going to build up my driving skills, in hopes that I can 
eventually catch up to him, and get him to recognize my ability
as a street racer\.\

### String 53 ###

I was still in my teens the first time I got in a car. I was
promptly captivated by the speed, and started getting into the
street racing scene. 
\>Later, a Japanese talent agency scouted me, and I moved to 
Tokyo. Then I found out about the Metro Expressway, and $\Tiger of 
Light\* invited me to join this team. 
\>I plan to strike out on my own once I've built up the skill to 
do so, though, and follow in the footsteps of $\Cinderella After
Midnight\*. I'm just getting started here, you see\.\

### String 54 ###

I first heard of $\Black Dragon\* while I was in Hong Kong. He's one
of the top street racers on the Metro, and even now, I aspire to 
be like him. 
\>It wasn't until I came to Japan, though, that I found out that 
there are even better street racers here: $\King Speed\*, $\Snake 
Eyes\*, $\Platinum Prince\*, 
\>and now, you, with all the attention you're getting. Asian Ages\* 
is just my jumping-off point. 
\>Maybe I'll look back on being part of this street racing team 
someday, when I've become the next $\King Speed\*\.\

### String 55 ###

I thought I was pretty fast, but I was dead wrong. There's
always someone better, I guess. I haven't been this excited in a
long time!

### String 56 ###

Now that I've raced you, I want to know more about you and your
car. I'd like to race you again sometime, if the opportunity
presents itself\.\

### String 57 ###

Oh, man, what a street racing team I've gotten mixed up with!
How much do they spend on their cars, anyway? 
\>I tried to spend enough to keep up with them, and the next thing 
I knew, I was up to my eyeballs in debt! 
\>Do you suppose it's true that $\Snake Eyes\* will give you all the 
funds you need to customize your car if you can get into Phantom 
Nine\*? 
\>In that case, I'd go for it, except I can't imagine how much 
it'd cost to customize a car to a level that $\Snake Eyes\* would 
accept in the first place!

### String 58 ###

I'm worried about $\Whispering Bow\*. He's got debt coming out his
ears. I just bet he's customizing his car to try to make himself
look good, even though he can't afford it. 
\>He goes around buying brand new expensive modifications every 
time you turn around. Can't say as  blame him, though. 
\>About the only thing I can do is give him pawned and unredeemed 
parts on the sly\.\

### String 59 ###

I admit it: our team's cars cost money. But I think it 
ultimately takes technique on the part of the driver to take
advantage of that performance. 
\>I'd say the real strength of our team is that we don't depend on 
the performance of our cars. I mean, it probably means more to 
us to win strictly on the merits of our ability, you know?

### String 60 ###

$\Miracle Trickster\* still can't seem to decide whether to go with
a lighter chassis or improved aerodynamics. I figure that if the
choice has got him that flummoxed, he ought to just do both\.\

### String 61 ###

I just can't decide whether to go with improved aerodynamics or
lighter body weight first. There'd be nothing to worry about if
I had the kind of money that $\Hardly Working\* has, though\.\

### String 62 ###

I wish $\Miracle Trickster\* would just shut up and lighten his
car's chassis weight, already. A little consideration would show
it'd be worth it\.\

### String 63 ###

In one sense, a street racing team is like a family. Don't you
ever get lonely, racing around all by yourself like that?

### String 64 ###

Aerodynamics make a man's life worth living. They make your car
look more stylish, too. $\Step-up Winner\* just doesn't get that
stuff\.\

### String 65 ###

Forget about aerodynamics or lighter chassis weight. It's how
much horsepower you've got that makes the difference in your
car's performance. Period. 
\>So if you're going to obsess over anything, it should be your 
car's air intake. Actually, it's not nearly as simple as I might 
make it out to be. Not at all\.\

### String 66 ###

Responsiveness in handling is what counts! All the skill in the
world is all for nothing if the car doesn't react suitably!
\>Though of course, you can customize your car to be as
responsive as all get-out, and it can be totally wasted if you
haven't got the driving skill to make use of it\.\

### String 67 ###

Horsepower, turning radius, and solid braking: these are what
life is all about. The deciding factor is whether you can
decelerate suitably going into a curve or not. 
\>So if you boost your horsepower, don't forget to get better 
brakes too\.\

### String 68 ###

$\Matashichi\*'s puns are awful. I mean, a car is a litter, a
craftsman is a customizer, and a coffee shop is a parking
area! Only street racers will make any sense out of that!

### String 69 ###

I caught $\Maebashi\* and $\Hiranishi\*'s act on TV. It seemed to me
that they were going mainly on momentum and not much else,
much like the way they race\.\

### String 70 ###

You gotta hand it to $\Hamada\* and his custom cars. How does he
manage to make these cars so intense? I'd hate to see him finish
up as a freelancer. 
\>I've even thought of fronting him the capital to go into 
business for himself, though if I did, people would come down on 
me for trying to buy influence again\.\

### String 71 ###

Don't get me wrong. Simply having money doesn't mean you can get
good customization. Rather, you spend what it takes, because you
want quality in customization. You're no different, right? 
\>You'd spend whatever you have to if it'll make your car go 
faster, won't you? That's what I'm talking about\.\

### String 72 ###

My team leader saw me in a model-making magazine, and got in
touch with me. That's how I joined this outfit. I raced against
Hiroki Takigawa, the famous car designer. 
\>To say I was nervous would be an understatement, but I 
completely got over it once we started racing together. 
\>Now we're pretty close friends, with similar interests, though 
he's far and away the better driver\.\

### String 73 ###

I don't rightly understand customization, so I leave it all to
Hamada. 
\>We drive around, with him riding shotgun, and all I have
to say is, "I'd like it a little more like this," and he'll make
it happen. It's amazing. 
\>I know he does customizing work for other street racing teams, 
too, with the Rings\* team complaining about it, but I trust him 
implicitly, broadmindedness and all\.\

### String 74 ###

Money talks, whether in politics or in customization. It's easy
to criticize that attitude, but those who do suddenly change
their tune once they've got money themselves. 
\>I've seen it happen over and over again\.\

### String 75 ###

I've never really seen much need to spend all that much money on
customization. So long as a car is in good enough shape to give
a good ride, that's all I care about. 
\>But now that I'm part of Urban Stars\*, which is a pretty well-
known street racing team on Rte. 4, I've got to produce results 
that won't be embarrassing.
\>So, I've got the money, so I guess I might as well use it, you
know?

### String 76 ###

I've heard about your racing performance. Will you let me make a
street racing movie based on your experiences? I've offered the
role of $\Snake Eyes\* to Takashi Tobikawa. 
\>But before I can make that movie, I need a box office hit with 
my current flick. Would you buy 100 tickets to this film?

### String 77 ###

"Inspiration" is a great word, don't you agree? I like that
word, "inspiration." I wish something would inspire me!

### String 78 ###

You can't win races by relying solely on theory! In the final
analysis, what matters most is the driver's instincts! 
\>And I'm not saying this because I think it's a nuisance to go 
out and drive a given course before actually racing!

### String 79 ###

I wonder what kinds of music people listen to while they're
driving. Some people remove their car stereos to reduce weight.
Me, I guess I'm into hard rock and trance music. 
\>Though sometimes I put on J-pop or R&B, because there's no 
telling just what's out there. It kills me to admit it, but I 
haven't had a chance to use it yet, though\.\

### String 80 ###

Every race ultimately comes down to a competition against
oneself. And only those who triumph in such contests achieve
victory on the track\.\

### String 81 ###

Guys really love to fiddle with the little things, don't they?
Whether it's cars or darts or fishing, they put different parts
together and mess around with them. 
\>I don't see what's so much about that. I mean, it's OK when they 
get all excited and talk about these things, but when they start 
tossing around terms like "turbo" or "suspension", 
\>it just goes right over my head. I wish they'd put down the 
games once in a while and pay some attention to me too\.\

### String 82 ###

