### String 1 ###

Did you know that you can get a legend-type *\handle\* for winning
50 consecutive races or thereabouts? 
\>My only interest right now is in cars, but I'd gladly ride 
shotgun for a racer who had a handle like that. 
\>You should also know that if you have a winning streak snapped 
even once, you'll get another handle on the spot. It's a harsh 
world out there\.\

### String 2 ###

Hey kid! Do you like your current *\handle\*? I've raced the Metro
Expressway for nearly 30 years now, and I had nothing but
shameful handles when I was younger. 
\>So don't let it get you down! People are judging you by the 
total distance you've raced, not just your win/loss record. 
\>You've heard the saying, "Perseverance counts," right? Well, 
there you are. You keep on racing, and you're sure to earn a 
handle that you'll want people to call you by\.\

### String 3 ###

I hear that there used to be a special *\handle\* for street racers
who competed in multiple races in one day with little or no time
off the track. 
\>They also say that these were veteran racers with solid win/loss 
records. I'm hoping to win that handle, though it may take me 
years to get there\.\

### String 4 ###

When history changes, it's a sure bet that there's someone in
the shadows, pulling the strings. 
\>For example, suppose that someone comes along who takes out all 
comers, except for one particular street racer. People are 
naturally going to start assuming that these two are in league. 
\>Moreover, the more renown this racer gets, the more likely 
people are to start referring to him by a special *\handle\* 
signifying that he is, in fact, a manipulator\.\

### String 5 ###

I got a new *\handle\* recently, and I've been wondering why. Then I
realized that I've only been hitting the Metro by night lately. 
\>I guess this handle is people's way of telling me that they want 
me to race at different times too, 
\>that they don't care much for me only hitting the streets at one
particular time of day\.\

### String 6 ###

Now, there are bound to be teams you're not gonna like, as well
as teams that you're gonna have an easy time with. 
\>I've heard tell, though, that you can get a special *\handle\* if 
you only race against certain teams. If that's what you want, 
though, then it's nobody's business but yours\.\

### String 7 ###

You've gotten pretty famous lately. Have you familiarized
yourself with the New Ring Road yet? You know that's not the
official name of that circuit, of course. It's actually made up
\>of the Fukagawa Route, the Bayshore, the Daiba, and the C1 Loop.
It's a nuisance to have to remember each and every part, though,
so everybody just calls it the New Ring Road, based on the shape
\>of the C1. The whole thing is almost 13mi in length, if I'm not
mistaken--longer than the C1 in all. How's that for trivia? Aw,
come on, show some amazement! Please!

### String 8 ###

When you race the New Ring Road, where do you go for the kill?
\>If sheer horsepower is your thing, I bet it's the Bayshore, 
because there aren't too many other roads that are that wide and
straight. 
\>It's the pits, though, if your opponent's car has more 
horsepower than you do. All you'd see in that case is his rear
end, pulling away from you. 
\>Now, you can tell by looking at your opponent's car roughly how 
many horses it puts out. It's something to keep in mind when 
you're looking for opponents to race against\.\

### String 9 ###

Say, the Yokohane and Bayshore Routes outbound are still closed.
Do you know why? 
\>Scuttlebutt is construction, paving, that sort of thing, but I 
think it has to some bigwig or other, who has to travel only at 
specific times--
\>Hey, wait, there's some Men In Black coming this way! 
Hey, I'm not kidding, they're headed over here! Eeeeek!

### String 10 ###

Do you use traction control? No, I'm not talking about dental
care or anything like that. It's a system for keeping cars from
spinning their wheels. 
\>Traction transmits driving force into the ground, you see, which 
makes it crucial to propelling cars forward. And traction 
control ensures that traction works as it should. 
\>Set traction control to high to minimize wheel spinning, and 
keep a tight grip on the road. Conversely, set traction control 
lower if you want to go into controlled drifts. 
\>But if you set traction control too high, you won't be able to 
turn tightly enough in the corners, whereas if you set it too 
low, you'll have a hard time keeping your car in line. 
\>Keep these things in mind when you adjust it. Anyway, the 
important thing is that you use it\.\

### String 11 ###

An "RE" engine type refers to rotary engines, which generate
horsepower by turning a rotor somewhat shaped like an egg.
\>They're lighter and smaller than other reciprocal engine types.
It's amazing to think that they've even made rotary engines that
can run on hydrogen as well as gasoline\.\

### String 12 ###

"F4" engine types refer to flat engines, which have cylinders
lined up horizontally, facing each other. 
\>They're also called boxer engines, because they look like boxers 
getting ready to throw punches. 
\>Their advantage lies in their low center of gravity and strong 
balance, which is a consequence of the cylinders being arranged 
horizontally\.\

### String 13 ###

My car is a red Mazda RX-8. I like rotary engines, you see. It's
really nice, combining a sense of luxury with affordability. The
first time I saw it, I had my doubts about the double doors,
\>but now that I've adjusted to them, I like them. It makes it a
lot easier to get in and out of the back seat. And have you
heard about the RX-8 hydrogen engines? They're ready for road
\>service, or so I hear, and they'll run on gasoline too. They say
it works that way is because of the rotary engine design. So
it's environmentally friendly, and that's what matters now\.\

### String 14 ###

The Nissan Fairlady Z Z33 NA is one helluva car. The more you
customize it, the faster it feels. It takes time and money, but
you can see the fruits of your labors in full. 
\>And there's the engine sound, reverberating throughout the car. 
Nothing feels better than that. I may never stop tinkering with 
this car\.\

### String 15 ###

The Subaru Impreza GDB puts one genuinely at ease. It
accelerates smoothly and stops firmly, even when it rains. 
\>The transmission also handles well, and the car turns just as 
you'd expect. Every part of the car is solidly put together, 
which makes for good performance overall. 
\>The steering wheel and the clutch feel right in your hands. You 
can turn just fine, even if you're going too fast as you go into 
a turn. Nothing about it gives me even an instant's pause. 
\>It's comfortable and handles well too. The engineers really seem 
to have thought of everything. I've never driven anything that 
gave me such peace of mind before\.\

### String 16 ###

With a long nose, short deck, a sleek, glamorous chassis, and a
sort of American retro styling, the Toyota 70 Supra is just too
cute. I'm on my third one in seven years. 
\>It has a tendency to break down if it's been customized, but I 
make up for that with sheer fondness. I'm so glad I found this 
model, and I hope to keep driving it for another decade or two\.\

### String 17 ###

If you're gonna customize your car, start with the engine. It's
the heart of the car, and thus, needs to be the focus of any
customization work. 
\>Next would be the cooling module and the muffler. Then, you 
could buy other parts that you might want to configure to your 
personal preferences. 
\>If you want to work on the gear ratios, you could buy a new 
transmission, as well as a new suspension if you want to lower 
the chassis or make it more rigid. 
\>Oh, and don't forget the brakes. They're easy enough to
overlook, but you're gonna need to be able to decelerate
smoothly into the turns. 
\>And you might customize the aerodynamics too, if you're the type 
that cares about appearances. Basically, careful customization 
is good for your car\.\

### String 18 ###

What's that? You wanna know how to drive faster? Well, if you
ask me, the key is firm, secure, solid traction. When you go
into a turn, decelerate to shift the load forward. 
\>Then turn solidly, keeping the front wheels, and their increased 
load, in mind. Then pull out by turning up the tire traction. 
\>I believe that the secret to driving faster is to adhere to all 
of these basic principles. 
Aside: I hate drifting. I think it's barbaric\.\

### String 19 ###

It's hard to figure out LSD ratios! The higher they are, the
more traction you have, and thus, the more stable the ride,
right? 
\>But that blocks the differential, which makes it hard to turn. 
But if you lower the ratio instead, then you have trouble
coming out of turns smoothly. It's tough to work this out\.\

### String 20 ###

Brakes are really pretty complex. I used to think that the best
thing to do was to hit the brakes hard, but hitting them too
hard cost me some stability in driving. 
\>Brake balance also changes things. Loosening the front brakes, 
for example, leads to oversteering, while loosening the rear 
brakes instead tends to cause understeering. 
\>These are useful things for street racers to know\.\

### String 21 ###

Tires, eh...... The more expensive, the better.
For grip and for friction resistance.
The better tires you equip, the more capable your car becomes.
\>After that it's just a matter of choosing your preferred 
hardness. Hard tires are durable but have low grip.
Soft tires have high grip but low durability.
\>Generally, use hard tires for racing multiple small-time 
opponents, and use soft tires when racing someone strong.
That might be a good way to go about using them\.\

### String 22 ###

Rumor has it that $\King Speed\* is back on the Metro.
Things are likely to heat up if the guy who was once the fastest
racer on the Metro really is racing again. 
\>I guess chaos is what the Metro is all about\.\

### String 23 ###

You're pretty good. I had no idea you'd be that fast. But you're
still no big deal compared to $\Skull Bullet\*. His car is possessed
by the devil himself. If you're not careful, he'll nail you!

### String 24 ###

I never imagined you'd beat me. I didn't think there were any
racers on the New Ring Road who'd be worth the effort, but,
amazingly enough, it seems I was wrong. 
\>All the same, you'd best beware of $\Skull Bullet\*. He's so fast, 
he makes me look like I'm standing still\.\

### String 25 ###

Man! I was supposed to be good enough to take down $\Snake
Eyes\*, only to have some no-name street racer beat me! OK, fine!
I'll make my bones by taking him down!

### String 26 ###

$\Snake Eyes\* and I go way back, but I've never seen him look so
defeated before. Losing to you was a real shock to his system.
\>But I know better than anyone that it'll take more than that
before he'll quit the Metro\.\

### String 27 ###

It bites that my team got beat, but it's a little less painful
to hear that $\Snake Eyes\* went down too. 
\>The Phantom Nine\* is one helluva team, to be sure, but I may have 
been deluded about my own speed simply because I was part of it. 
\>When I realized that what matters is myself, and not the team 
that I may be part of, I felt that I had taken another step 
forward. 
\>I look forward to having it out with you one of these days, not 
as part of the Phantom Nine\*, but as one street racer to another\.\

### String 28 ###

So you started racing the New Ring Road, even though you'd heard
the stories. Did you hear about $\Skull Bullet\*? That's right, the
street racer from America. 
\>Seems an acquaintance of his, a racer by the handle of $\Silent 
Cassiopeia\*, is popping up without warning on the New Ring Road 
after dark. 
\>Word has it that he's helping $\Skull Bullet\* find a particular 
black Supra. He's not likely to turn a blind eye to racers who 
profane his territory along the way, though. 
\>So if you prove yourself on the New Ring Road, you might find 
yourself facing off against him too. Don't say I didn't warn 
you\.\

### String 29 ###

So you've hit the New Ring Road. You're good, I'll be the first
one to admit that, but you still shouldn't let your guard down
over there. 
\>They say that $\Deep Blue Sniper\*, who's supposed to be the fastest 
street racer on the New Ring Road after midnight, is seriously 
bad news. 
\>If you prove yourself on the New Ring Road in those hours, he 
may just come looking for you\.\

### String 30 ###

That woman makes me so mad! That $\Daybreak Garnet\*, who drives
that R-32! She passed by me just now, over there, and she looked
at me and snorted! Put her in her place for me! 
\>She's sure to challenge you to a race if you prove yourself in 
the dawn hours on the New Ring Road!

### String 31 ###

Phantom Nine\*'s $\King Sandstorm\* is certainly a good-looking guy,
but I have to admit that he's not my type. 
\>There's something about him that dazzles, both racers and 
observers, that kind of creeps me out, even though there's no 
doubting his driving ability. 
\>I mean, he used to be partners with $\Snake Eyes\*, after all. He's 
very proud, so he won't race you unless you manage to take down 
all the New Ring Road street racing teams first, at a minimum. 
\>And when he does come after you, he'll be flanked by $\Mad Murdock\* 
and $\Dark Tengu\*\.\

### String 32 ###

There's a group known as the *\Twelve Ruling Saints\*, which was run
off the Metro when $\King Speed\* came along, only to return when he 
was defeated. 
\>One of their number is the $\Crimson Devil\*, whose unique chassis 
lines had a powerful impact on other Metro racers. 
\>And he was no slouch behind the wheel either, to be sure. If you 
can take out all the street racing teams on the New Ring Road, 
he's sure to come looking for you\.\

### String 33 ###

The $\Ignorant Fool\* who comes to the Tatsumi Parking Area after
dark is a real wannabe. He only races *\custom cars\*. If you're
driving a regular car, he won't have anything to do with you\.\

### String 34 ###

I hear that the $\Lonely Nihilist\* will challenge drivers in cars
that seem the right ones for him on the way back from Ariake
Colosseum. 
\>You might run into him if you take the *\Ariake on-ramp\* to 
the New Ring Road\.\

### String 35 ###

I saw the ultimate low-rider at the Tatsumi Parking Area late at
night. 
\>It belongs to a street racer called $\Critical Elegy\*, and he says 
he'll only race against cars *\with similar extreme low-rider 
chassis\*\.\

### String 36 ###

Looks like $\Mad Fat\*, who races the New Ring Road, is on yet
another diet. 
\>Apparently he started it about the time you started racing the 
Metro, and says he won't race there himself until he's been on 
it for at least *\three months\* and seen some results\.\

### String 37 ###

In Japanese gambling slang, "nine" apparently means "stock".
$\Tsujikiri Gambler\* has a superstition: he adds up all the
digits in a given date, and apparently only races the New Ring
Road in the wee hours on those days that *\add up to nine\*\.\

### String 38 ###

$\Unbalanced Ishii\*, who races the New Ring Road in the wee hours,
got his handle because he likes things unbalanced, such as cars
with *\different rear wheels than front wheels\*. 
\>He searches for news about racers with similar sensibilities, 
and looks for them on the Metro\.\

### String 39 ###

I haven't seen $\Golden License\* lately. Probably has something to
do with $\Yellow Desperado\* roving over the New Ring Road. He
shrinks away from reckless drivers like $\Yellow Desperado\*\.\

### String 40 ###

$\Waist Hakujin\*, who hangs out at the Tatsumi Parking Area, has
got money. I hear he's got *\five cars\*, and he really gets worked
up if he finds someone who's got more cars than he does\.\

### String 41 ###

$\Phantom Babe\* of Another Star\* has asked $\Speed Box\* to help her 
deal with a stalker. 
All I did was challenge her to a battle and he chased me around 
all night thinking I was a stalker\.\

### String 42 ###

Racing Storm\* is an amalgamation of at least three other street
racing teams, which has led to factional infighting for control. 
\>The hardcore faction and the "Fun Driving" faction, from which
the leader and deputy leader come, respectively, are the most
strongly opposed to one another\.\

### String 43 ###

If Max Racing\* is the best-known sedan street racing team on the
C1 Loop, then SS Limited\* is its counterpart on the New Ring
Road. 
\>There was some confusion over leadership, but these days,
they're considered a solid, stable team. 
\>I hear they used to race the C1 Loop, only to move to the New 
Ring Road to avoid running afoul of Max Racing\*\.\

### String 44 ###

Road Concerto, a street racing team made up of classical music
performers, is both elegant and tough. They hardly ever talk
amongst themselves, even when they meet in parking areas. 
\>That may make some people think they don't get along, which 
isn't true. 
\>They're very close-knit, and if one of them gets taken down, 
the others will avenge him. The scuttlebutt is that each of them 
is also pretty good behind the wheel\.\

### String 45 ###

There used to be a team of college student street racers on the
C1 Loop. Its leader formed ASF\* after graduation, which is short
for Akihara Speed Factory. 
\>And as its name suggests, it's tied to the the customizing shop 
run by its leader, Kenji Akihara.
\>It's a motley crew, but they're all pretty good, thanks to the
cars they drive, which have all been worked on by their leader,
who's a genius at customizing cars\.\

### String 46 ###

The "Danji\* (Guys)" team from Kyushu is mounting a campaign on
the Metro. 
\>They have really hardcore cars and very macho driving styles, 
which makes them intimidating in ways that other street racing 
teams can't match. 
\>Rumor has it that they originally came to the Metro to meet 
Tokyo girls, 
\>and in fact, some female drivers have fallen for them based on 
the way they race, so they just might get their wish before too 
much longer\.\

### String 47 ###

Haze\* has only three members: they're "the few, the proud" among
street racing teams. 
\>Under normal circumstances, they live quiet lives, and don't 
stand out all that much on the Metro either. 
\>What they've done, however, is take advantage of the fact that 
they go mostly unnoticed to drive in a sort-of stealth manner, 
which has proven to be pretty successful. 
\>So one can't look down on them for it\.\

### String 48 ###

If you want to see a real Mitsubishi Lancer Evolution VIII CT9A,
head for the New Ring Road after dark. That's when Top Level\*,
with their totally customized cars, hit the road. 
\>They've got it in for the Subaru Impreza's driven by Another 
Star\*. They race each other night after night, with their mutual 
pride on the line. 
\>If you do see them, you may find yourself racing them,
because Subarus aren't the only cars they go after\.\

### String 49 ###

They used to be a bunch of street racers who made a name for
themselves on the Metro until circumstances forced them to drop 
out. 
\>They've formed a team called "Be Legend\*", which is also known as 
the Home for Street Racers Seeking a Second Chance. 
\>They used to be known as the Thirteen Demon Lords and the Twelve 
Ruling Saints, so even though their skills have declined through 
lack of use, 
\>it's not likely to take them long to get back their collective 
edge and regain their legendary status\.\

### String 50 ###

There’s a team called Aquarium\*, which is made up of bachelor
street racers. Seems they started out at mixers, but now they're
a pretty dedicated street racing team. 
\>Their big problem now is, they can meet someone, race her, and 
end up beating her, costing themselves a chance even to talk 
to them\.\

### String 51 ###

Free Way\* would be the first name in GT-R street racing teams.
Phantom Nine\* took them out, but apparently they're back on the
New Ring Road. 
\>Apparently their overall driving skills have improved, so I 
guess they're looking for racing opponents\.\

### String 52 ###

There's a group within Strong Formation\* called "Offense Five".
Three of them, known as $\Go-for-Broke Fullback\*, $\Fleetfoot Wide
Receiver\*, and $\Riot Squad Running Back\*, race as a unit. 
\>Theyっ're all really good drivers. Ignore them at your peril\.\

### String 53 ###

There are two groups within the Strong Formation\* team. One is
Defense Five, and they visit parking areas. 
\>Four of them, known as $\Defensive Lineman\*, $\Defensive Back\*, 
$\Top-notch Middle Guard\*, and $\Perfect Nose Guard\*, race four 
abreast at all times. 
\>Either you reach the finish line ahead of them, or you're dead. 
I wish you luck\.\

### String 54 ###

Aside from its leader, Be Legend\* has three other really good
drivers are $\Kong Ming the Transitory\*, $\Whimsical Joan of Arc\*, and
$\Shiodome Genghis Khan\*. 
\>They race in formation, taunting and teasing their opponents. 
It's unbearable, given that they made a name for themselves at 
one time\.\

### String 55 ###

I can't believe there's someone I couldn't beat with these
specifications... Now what do I do about it? 
\>Do I work more hours to make more money for better customizing, 
or do I beef up my driving skills? That is the question\.\

### String 56 ###

Does your speed come from your enjoyment of driving, or because
you take your driving seriously? Your answer will help me decide
whether to side with my leader or my deputy leader\.\

### String 57 ###

That was excellent driving. I have no complaints. I think I have
experienced yet another example of the unfairness of life\.\

### String 58 ###

My philosophy of street racing has changed significantly since
coming to Tokyo and meeting my team leader. And now it is
changing again, as a consequence of meeting you\.\

### String 59 ###

You're fast. How much driving did you have to do to get so good?
Or is this merely a natural difference in ability between us?

### String 60 ###

Meeting you, I have at last realized just how narrow my
worldview is. But I will change, and when I have, I will
challenge you to another race\.\

### String 61 ###

Hey, just what kind of oil additive are you using in your car?
You've got to have some kind of secret to be going that fast,
right? Tell me on the sly, OK?

### String 62 ###

And here I thought I'd finally adjusted to sedans, and could
actually drive them for real. Silly me, I guess\.\

### String 63 ###

I haven't been beaten and felt so invigorated in such a long
time. I see the resemblance between you and $\King Speed\* now. 
\>But is it in how you drive, your car, or in the mood you give 
off? That is the mystery\.\

### String 64 ###

This car is steeped in my father's sentiments. I have inherited
it, and I will pass it on to my descendants. For that reason, I
cannot end up like this!

### String 65 ###

I've been racing around these parts to try to find a certain
someone. He gave me encouragement to keep going when I was on
the verge of closing up shop three years ago. 
\>He frequently raced the Metro. I don't know whether he still 
does, but I'm convinced I'll find him here\.\

### String 66 ###

Has Iwasaki been racing lately? He and I went to intermediate
school together. We always liked cars, even when we didn't have
licenses. 
\>I never imagined he'd grow up to become the fastest racer on 
the Metro, though\.\

### String 67 ###

You're faster than I thought. I didn't think you'd be much of a
challenge. I never imagined you'd beat me. 
\>The president of my company says don't overdo it, but more than 
anything, I want to win!

### String 68 ###

Oh brother. I guess the level of street racing on the Metro
Expressway has improved. I can't win nearly as easily as I could
in the early days. I'll have to beef up my skills accordingly\.\

### String 69 ###

I was naive to think that I could beat you in a race, even if I
was no match when it came to songwriting. But I will chalk this
one up to experience, and eventually I will get faster. 
\>I'm not giving up!

### String 70 ###

Hey you! You couldn't have beaten me unless you cheated! How in
the world did you do it? I'll let you off the hook if you tell
the truth\.\

### String 71 ###

You really were good enough to beat him. That's why I wasn't
able to give you a challenge. But I'm not giving up. One of
these days, I'll take you down!

### String 72 ###

Well, hell. I thought you must be my stalker, when you passed me
like that. I'm scared because that's been happening so much
lately. 
\>I'd be in real trouble if someone as fast as you was stalking 
me\.\

### String 73 ###

You drive pretty good. I may base the protagonist of my next TV
drama on you\.\

### String 74 ###

Thanks to you, I had the opportunity to test out some new parts.
I guess none of them are any good, though\.\

### String 75 ###

Can I snap a picture of your car with my cell phone? I'd like to
send it to my wife. Otherwise, she'll think I'm cheating on her\.\

### String 76 ###

I get carried away when I race. I'm sorry for denting your car.
I'm be more careful in future\.\

### String 77 ###

I'll beat you next time, no matter what it takes! Remember that!

### String 78 ###

The most dangerous moment is the one in which you're most
certain of victory. I'll just have to hope I make it back to the
garage in one piece\.\

### String 79 ###

You're amazing. I'm blown away..\.\

### String 80 ###

Geez! I'd have won if only I'd sold you some defective
customized parts!

### String 81 ###

I never dreamed you'd beat me! I'll do whatever it takes--no,
that's wrong. If I were to take that attitude, it would make me
no better than this team!

### String 82 ###

As one gentleman to another, I accept my defeat graciously. I
will henceforth mend my ways. To that end, I pledge not to use
dirty tricks when I race, from time to time\.\

### String 83 ###

I--I'm sorry, but I'm seeing someone! Eh? Aren't you my stalker?

### String 84 ###

I can count on one hand the street racers who can take the
pressure that I can give. And you have the strongest will of any
of them. 
\>The deciding factor in a race is not your car's specs,
nor your skill behind the wheel, but your strength of will. 
In that sense, you are an excellent street racer\.\

### String 85 ###

I've never been this moved outside of watching a movie before.
That means it was really good driving.
I'd love to become a driver with such moving driving as yours\.\

### String 86 ###

Racing you gave me back a feeling I haven't had in ages. What's
past is past, it's true, but our experiences are always with us\.\

### String 87 ###

I'm glad I returned to racing the Metro, because I've
met a racer like you. I have profited greatly by that alone\.\

### String 88 ###

Never have I experienced such humiliation. Even being beaten by
$\King Speed\* was easier to take than this. When next we meet, I
will settle this score between us!

### String 89 ###

It seems times have changed since I was last on the Metro
Expressway. Or could it be that it is I who have changed? It
would seem that I have let my own driving ability go to my head\.\

### String 90 ###

Did you want to talk to me? You have shown me better driving
than I myself am capable of. 
\>I know you have not been racing for all that long, but surely 
you no longer have need for words of advice\.\

### String 91 ###

You beat me on horsepower? But this car is my precious sidekick.
I can't just trade it in\.\

### String 92 ###

Sigh. I'm just no good. Why can't I take the pressure any better
than this? You'd never have beaten me if I could only overcome
that weakness!

### String 93 ###

My driving instincts must really be failing if you could beat
me. I need to get some more energy, I guess. 
\>I didn't want to mess with it if I could help it, but I have a 
feeling that I don't have the luxury of talking like that 
anymore\.\

### String 94 ###

Hold it, you! I bet you don't think much of me as a street
racer, do you? I just wasn't paying attention, that's all. I
won't make that mistake again, and that's a promise!

### String 95 ###

Losing to you hurts. I think I'll sell off one of my holdings in
the Kanda district, so I can get a new car\.\

### String 96 ###

I'm not necessarily objecting to the way $\Red Sunfire\* drives.
I just don't like how he tries to force it on other street
racers, that's all. 
\>I mean, everybody has his own way of thinking about street 
racing, right?

### String 97 ###

What kind of car are you looking for? The Nissan Skyline Coupe
and Cima are your best bets in *\the sedan category\*, followed by
the Toyota Crown, Celsior, and Aristo. 
\>*\1990s models\* can be had pretty reasonably too, like FDs, GC8, or 
Nissan's R32, Z32, S15, and 180. 
\>And there are Supras from the 1970s and 1980s, as well as 
the 1990s\.\

### String 98 ###

You're a street racer? You're kidding, right? I mean, your car
doesn't look like it goes all that fast. 
\>Wouldn't it be better suited to going for a leisurely drive 
somewhere with a babe in the passenger seat? 
\>Oh, did that make you mad? Then try to get past me. 
I'll take you on any time you like\.\

### String 99 ###

My car and I are one heart, one mind. We'll be together until
the bitter end, though I can't say which of us will give out
first\.\

### String 100 ###

One day, $\King Speed$\ brought his car and told me this.
\>"Make me a car that won't lose to anyone".
\>At first I refused.. It's impossible to create "a car that won't lose to 
anyone". But, I gave in to his strong, unfailing gaze and nodded my 
head.
\>It was a work of art.
Although I had made it, it didn't feel like my car at all\.\

### String 101 ###

I'm not sure whether I believe that story that $\Riverside Crow\*
tells about building a chassis for $\King Speed\*. I mean, he
customized my car too, and it's pretty nice, I admit. 
\>But I wonder if the reason I can't go as fast as $\King Speed\* is 
because I'm just not as good a driver\.\

### String 102 ###

$\Riverside Crow\* says that he customized $\King Speed\*'s chassis. But
I don't know about that. 
\>I mean, yeah, he makes some really fine chassis, but if I were 
$\King Speed\*, I wouldn't trust my car to someone so irresponsible. 
If it is true, then $\King Speed\* must have nerves of steel\.\

### String 103 ###

I was on a team that got wiped out. My teammates all quit the
Metro, but I'm still racing. I want to have it out
with the racers who took my old team down\.\

### String 104 ###

This group I ran into in Osaka, called No Loser\*, was pretty
wild. 
\>They're totally foolhardy, with a passion that you just don't 
find in the typical Metro street racer, who's more into putting 
on airs. I hope I run into them again sometime\.\

### String 105 ###

I felt something in me transformed when I saw $\Blue Speed\*, our
leader, race for the first time. 
\>The sight has been with me ever since, even though I still can't 
catch up to him. Maybe I never will\.\

### String 106 ###

What's inside is what counts. It's true of cars as well as
people. So I concentrate on the insides, and try to leave the
exteriors as unchanged as I can. 
\>And when other street racers see me, they get careless and start 
thinking that they can beat me easily. 
\>But that's not what happens at all when we hit the road. Being 
so unpredictable is fun, don't you agree?

### String 107 ###

When I get in the groove, I tend to get tunnelvision, which can
cause me to make trouble for other drivers before I know what's
happened. 
\>I used to be so scared of that that I couldn't make a　move. 
Nowadays, though, I figure that things will work out if I
just apologize\.\

### String 108 ###

Performance is important, but there's more to it than just
numbers. I also pay attention to my car's interior, as well as
its audio system. 
\>It doesn't pay to shortchange these more contemplative aspects 
of your car\.\

### String 109 ###

As more and more street racing teams vanish from the Metro
Expressway, 
\>I think that one major reason we've hung on is the potential 
inherent in our Mitsubishi Lancer Evolution VIII CT9As. 
\>Another Star\*'s $\Blue Speed\* doesn't give us much credit,
though. I think I'm gonna have to teach him a lesson one of
these days\.\

### String 110 ###

An intelligence operative? Moi? Don't be ridiculous. I'm an
engineer. That's all. Uh-oh! I've gotta be going. Got a date
with a babe\.\

### String 111 ###

I traveled the world when I was young. There was Maria in Italy,
Lisa in Spain, Natasha in Russia... Ah yes, I remember it well\.\

### String 112 ###

Do you have any siblings? I have a sister who's six years
younger than me, whom I haven't seen in a decade. I hear she's
in Hong Kong, where she works as an actress. 
\>But I saw a woman on Shinjuku Rte. 4 not too long ago who looked 
like her. 
\>I didn't have a chance to introduce myself at the time, but I 
just hope I can look out for her in some way\.\

### String 113 ###

How would you like a canned coffee drink? It isn't poisoned, I
assure you. Tee hee. You might find a drop or two of aphrodisiac
mixed in, though\.\

### String 114 ###

I wish I could say that there is nothing that my car cannot do!
But I need to strengthen the chassis before I can get any more
horsepower out of it. 
\>I could trade up to an R34, I suppose, but this car and I have 
been through a lot together, and I can't bring myself to part 
with it\.\

### String 115 ###

$\Supersonic Napoleon\*, the leader of Be Legend\*, also heads up a
popular stage company. Some team members are also apparently
part of the troupe. 
\>I wanted to see them perform, but the show was sold out. Bummer!

### String 116 ###

Oh my, who told you that? Yes, it's true: Masa and I are seeing
one another. We ran into one another at the Tatsumi Parking
Area, about a month ago, I think it was. 
\>I got one look at his Mitsubishi Lancer Evolution VIII CT9A, 
and it was as if a bolt of lightning went through me. 
\>Then I raced him, and that was when I knew that we had to be 
together\.\

### String 117 ###

At last, I found him: the guy who vanished three years ago,
leaving me with his debts! A friend of mine says he spotted him
cruising the New Ring Road in a Subaru Impreza. 
\>Now I've got him, and I'll chase him to the ends of the earth in 
my Mazda RX-8!

### String 118 ###

My bro may say I'm living the good life, but that's not how it
is at all. I have my share of troubles and woes too, but words
alone won't get that across. 
\>I guess we'll just have to race for him to get the message: my 
R34 versus his. Yep, one of these days, 
\>I figure we're gonna have to see, once and for all, which of us 
is faster\.\

### String 119 ###

Eh? Who told you that? OK, OK, it's true: Mana and I are seeing
one another, with an eye toward marriage. It helps that we both
like cars. 
\>She currently resides in Sangenjaya, but has said she'd be 
willing to move\.\

### String 120 ###

Oh my...! My teammate, Nomoto, is dating $\Seductive Amethyst$\,
from the Juicy Heaven\* team! And I had my eye on Nomoto too!
After all, he's the only worthwhile guy on this team! Maybe I'll
try making a play for $\King Speed\* instead\.\

### String 121 ###

I just exchanged words with Juicy Heaven\*'s $\Seductive Amethyst\*!
This is big! This is really big! I've just got to put the pedal
to the metal!

### String 122 ###

How's this for dialogue: "You haven't got a sister like that!
And even if you did, she wouldn't be caught dead around
you!" Pretty good, huh?

### String 123 ###

Lately, we're seeing lots of guys and gals wearing glasses.
Well, I'd like to take them aside for an hour or so, and ask
them how much glasses really mean to them. 
\>I'd like to know if they've ever been to the town of Sabae, in 
Fukui Prefecture. Did you know that 90％ of all eyeglass frames 
made in Japan come from Sabae? 
\>That's amazing! And they have an annual marathon where
contestants are required to wear glasses! 
\>Just think: a marathon where you can't compete if you don't wear 
glasses! Isn't that great?

### String 124 ###

Sigh... Someday I'd like to own a proper garage, with lifts and
tire changers, that sort of thing. But I nearly passed out when
I added up how much it would cost. I need money, lots of money\.\

### String 125 ###

No matter how nice the weather is, it starts to rain when you
wash your car, you know? What's up with that? I really want to
move someplace with a covered carport\.\

### String 126 ###

Talk about lame! The other day, I went for a drive with my
girlfriend. I left the stereo and air conditioner running, with
the engine turned off, and drained the battery. 
\>But a guy happened on the scene in an 80 Supra, and gave me 
a jumpstart.
\>He sure knew his way around under the hood. Do you suppose he
could have been a car customizer?

### String 127 ###

I've become totally nocturnal since I started racing the Metro
Expressway. I'd be dead if they didn't have flex-time where I
work, no doubt about it\.\

### String 128 ###

That stupid cat! It went and left scratches all over the
freshly waxed hood of my car!
\>And that's on top of using my tires to sharpen its claws! I'm
gonna give its owner a piece of my mind!

### String 129 ###

Taking a nap is the thing to do when you're feeling tired. Would
you mind waking me in 20 minutes?

### String 130 ###

