### String 1 ###

It seems to me that of all the characteristics that set one
street racer apart from another, one defining characteristic is
the amount by which they win a given race. 
\>You get some racers who dash for the finish line in the wink of 
an eye, in cars that are optimized to the max. 
\>On the other hand, you get drivers who draw on their driving 
skills to eke out narrow wins in outdated, underpowered AE86's. 
\>They're both terrific, but if I had to choose, I'd go the 
distance in the underpowered car, in hopes of winning the *\handle\* 
that goes along with that kind of performance\.\

### String 2 ###

Whenever I race, I always either bump or rear-end the other
cars, and just generally have a lousy time. 
\>And I guess that racing like that over and over again caused a 
change in the way other racers treat me, and I started getting 
ever uglier *\handles\*. 
\>Nowadays they call me "the evil sheriff." And that really sucks, 
you know?

### String 3 ###

I'm a perfectionist. So naturally, I want a *\handle\* that fits my
perfectionist nature. I'm gonna win, and keep on winning! And of
course, it's important not to lose, too. 
\>You should also strive　for a perfectionist handle too! Come on!

### String 4 ###

Hitting walls or bumping other cars makes me want to throw in
the towel when I race. 
\>I recommend you beware of doing the same thing yourself too 
much, because you just might get a *\handle\* that connotes such 
tendencies. 
\>You never know when somebody might catch you out. And before you 
know it, you might be a legend, sort of\.\

### String 5 ###

There are *\handles\* for racers who take outrageous risks. What do
you do if you want that kind of handle? Simple: just refuse to
slow down, no matter what. 
\>Now me, I could never get that kind of handle, because my car 
means too much to me!

### String 6 ###

I really like the RB. You know, the Rainbow Bridge. You take the
New Ring Road to the Rainbow Bridge, and cross it to Odaiba!
\>It's the perfect drive for racing couples! Go on! Try it! You'll
see! ... Aw, man! It's times like this I wish I had a boyfriend!

### String 7 ###

Overall, the New Ring Road combines straightaways with a lot of
high-speed turns, so you can't have too much horsepower. 
\>But if you insist on competing with a car with low horsepower--
then your best bet is almost certainly to lure your opponents on 
to the C1 Loop, because it's all about driving technique there.
\>It's tougher than you think. What should you do if you don't
have sufficient driving skills either? Well, then, you're just,
you know, you're gonna have to bring your skills up, that's all\.\

### String 8 ###

Did you know that you can see a Ferris Wheel from the Daiba Rte.
as you head for the Bayshore? It's the Odaiba Ferris Wheel. Its
colors change as you watch it, making pretty patterns. 
\>I might pull off the road and check it out with my girlfriend 
one of these times-- No, I don't actually have a girlfriend, 
but so……。 what! What's wrong with wanting something?

### String 9 ###

My favorite drink is ABS Label! Huh? ABS isn't a brand of drink?
\>It stands for "Anti-lock Braking System"? It's a system for
keeping the tires from locking up and skidding when the driver
hits the brakes? Hunh. So tell me, what good does that do? Oh,
\>so using ABS in an effective manner keeps the brakes from
locking up the tires, which puts stopping power to good use in
\>maintaining the grip of the tires on the road. On the other
hand, applying the ABS lightly causes the tires to lock up,
\>which is conducive to drifting. I don't really get it, but who
cares, as long as the drinks are good? You drive cars, right? So

### String 10 ###

Figures like "L4" or "L6" given for engine types signify that
the engine in question is an in-line engine, the most
standardized design. 
\>The number signifies how many cylinders the engine has. So "L4" 
means a four-cylinder in-line engine. 
\>Also note the term "reciprocal," which refers to the up-and-down
motion of the pistons in the cylinders. Both flat and V-shaped
engines are reciprocal engines\.\

### String 11 ###

If the engine type designation is "V6" or "V8", it means the
engine in question is a V-type. This design was adopted in 
order to get around a limitation of standard in-line engines: 
\>attempting to increase engine performance by adding more 
cylinders demands longer engine blocks. 
\>The V-shaped engine uses a more compact configuration to work 
around this problem, by arranging opposing cylinders in pairs 
across from one another.
\>It used to be that you couldn't build V-shaped engines very
solidly, but that problems seems to have been solved. In 
general, engines with six or more cylinders are 
\>V-shaped engines\.\

### String 12 ###

FDs are in a class by themselves. Once you've tasted that smooth
acceleration, you'll be spoiled for anything other than rotary
engines ever again. 
\>Add in the greater stability that the longer wheelbase offers, 
and you've got a car that was made to race the Metro. Oh, 
and the rounded rear is nice to look at, too\.\

### String 13 ###

You ever heard of the original Cima? It was marketed as the
Infiniti Q45, Infiniti being Nissan's luxury brand, of course.
\>It had no front grille, but used a classic Japanese-style
sunburst emblem. Its interior was eggshell-white, thanks to
titanium enamel painted panels. 
\>It was really amazing. I loved it. Now the new Cima, with its 
black-and-white paneling and white leather interior, really puts 
you in the mind of the Q45, you know? 
\>I liked it right off the bat. And it's got all that V-8 
goodness, too. It's like the second coming of the Q45! 
Yeah, the Cima is a real VIP machine\.\

### String 14 ###

My all-time favorite car is the R-32 Skyline GT-R. I was so
excited when it went on sale, because it was the first GT-R
model in 16 years. And it was so slick, just sitting there. 
\>The aerodynamics wouldn't have worked anywhere else, I think. 
That's how well-designed the chassis was. 
\>Talk about manly! And it performs just like you'd expect a car 
with the GT-R brand to do. The R-32 is the best Skyline GT-R 
model\.\

### String 15 ###

The Crown series has really turned into a feast for the eyes,
especially with the Crown Athlete. Its interior is chic, and
overflowing with sophistication. 
\>My whole perception of the Crown brand changed the moment I laid 
eyes on it. Talk about love at first sight. And test driving it 
was even more powerful.
\>I gunned the engine and the car shook with the resulting
horsepower. I was blown away by just how much the Crown brand
has changed. 
\>The interior is so nice that you're happy just sitting in it, 
and it's also a pleasure to drive. There is no better car\.\

### String 16 ###

Hey, if you want the tires to hold tight to the road when you
drive, I hear one-way is what you want. The LSD doesn't engage
when decelerating, making for smooth handling through the turns.
\>On the other hand, the LSD kicks in at startup, when you need
it, to give you solid traction. 
\>It's not easy to manage, though, because of the difference in 
the way the car handles when you're accelerating versus when 
you're not. 
\>Probably you want to get used to the more stable handling of 
1.5-way LSD before trying your hand at one-way\.\

### String 17 ###

I customized my car so that it would grab the road and not let
go, but now it won't corner hard enough in the turns. I guess
it's true that anything done to excess is a bad idea. 
\>Maybe if I tweak the traction down a little... I think I'll 
start by easing traction control and the ABS... And there's 
the LSD too... How do I balance all of this...?

### String 18 ###

Say, do you alter your gear ratios? I like using
cross-transmissions. What! You haven't heard of
cross-transmissions? 
\>They allow more efficient use of engine power by tightening up 
your gear ratios. 
\>If you don't know anything else, you need to know that. Now that 
means you have to spend more time and effort shifting gears, 
\>but  I think it's cute watching drivers' hands fluttering around 
like that\.\

### String 19 ###

Some rear spoilers are adjustable. By changing their angles,
you can change the downforce impinging on a car. 
\>If you raise the angle, you increase the downforce, which 
presses your car down, which in turn increases your traction, 
and thus, your stability. 
\>On the other hand, lowering the angle reduces the downforce, 
which keeps the car from being pressed down to the ground, and 
thus, increases your maximum speed. Got that?

### String 20 ###

If you're driving around and suddenly feel the car's power, 
\>brake power, and tire grip weakening, you should let the car 
rest. Cars start to wear out after long periods of time as 
well.
\>When that happens, just return to the garage and let it refresh 
for a bit.
It'll be back to it's old self by the next day\.\

### String 21 ###

Why do you think $\Skull Bullet\*'s archrival is staying out of
sight? Does it mean he doesn't think he can beat him in a race?

### String 22 ###

How unexpected for me to lose to you.
It would seem I must reevaluate my opinion on The Metro's 
racers.
\>Even though $\King Speed\* may be gone, it would seem that
his spirit lives and thrives in this place\.\

### String 23 ###

Even $\Skull Bullet\*, who took out $\Snake Eyes\*, was eventually beaten
by someone else, right? Kind of makes you feel sorry for him,
right?

### String 24 ###

So you took down $\Snake Eyes\*, huh? I had a feeling you would, the
first time I laid eyes on you. Say, you want to put a racing
team together? Give me a shout if you decide to do so. 
\>I'll be your right-hand man, no problem\.\

### String 25 ###

You're not the racer who defeated the top three street racers on
the C1 Loop, by any chance, are you? It's an honor to meet you.
You'd best watch your step on the New Ring Road, though. 
\>This place is a whole lot rougher than the C1. The biggest 
threat here is $\Skull Bullet\*. He's a transplant from the US. 
\>I hear he's trying to track down another street racer, and he's 
got three partners helping him. I bet he'll show up if you take 
them all down\.\

### String 26 ###

I feel sorry for Phantom Nine\*'s $\Dark Tengu\*. He's competent
enough, but the rest of the team puts him in the shade. As a
consequence, he gets the cold shoulder from $\Snake Eyes\*. 
\>$\Dark Tengu\* likely also thinks that $\Snake Eyes\* is grooming you to 
take his place, which can't make him any happier. He really 
seems to hate you because of that. 
\>But even so, he's not liable to go after you until you've taken 
down all the racing teams on the new Ring Road. 
\>When he does race you, though, he'll do it as part of a team with 
$\King Sandstorm\* and $\Mad Murdock\*. Watch your back\.\

### String 27 ###

Phantom Nine\*'s $\Mad Murdock\* may not look like much, but you'd be
smart not to take him at face value. 
\>They say no one on the team has more respect for $\Snake Eyes\*, but 
he plays his cards close to his vest. 
\>Rumor has it that he may even be contemplating a takeover of 
Phantom Nine\* one of these days. 
\>He's liable to sit up and take  notice of you too, if you do 
something like take down all of the other New Ring Road racing 
teams. 
\>When he does race you, though, he'll do it as part of a team 
with the likes of $\King Sandstorm\* and $\Dark Tengu\*. Watch your back\.\

### String 28 ###

There's a tale they tell on the Metro, of a personage
that only those who rise above all other street racers may
encounter. 
\>The story goes that he flies along the ground, in a car whose 
speed belies its age. Whether you believe this story or not is 
up to you, but if you want to meet whoever is behind it, 
\>you need to demonstrate your driving skills to every other
street racer on the Metro\.\

### String 29 ###

Did you know that $\Wild Heart\*, the street racer who hangs out at
the Shibaura Parking Area after dark, is really Shuji Kurihara,
the retired baseball player? 
\>He only comes out rarely, but even so, he came out to the Metro 
just to meet me, when he heard that I'd racked up over *\100 wins\*\.\

### String 30 ###

I hear that the $\Masked Stranger\*, who races the New Ring Road
after dark, hates the ordinary. So he's constantly looking for
something different. 
\>I bet he'd be thrilled to meet you if he were driving, oh, say, 
a car with *\gull-wing doors\*, maybe?

### String 31 ###

If you want to race against $\Jet Skater\*, you'd best fit out your
car with *\nitro\*, because apparently, he won't race anything that
doesn't have it. 
\>Aside from that, you can find him on the New Ring Road, 
late at night\.\

### String 32 ###

$\Ono the Technician\*, who hangs out at the Shibaura Parking Area
late at night, just loves to show off his skills behind the
wheel. 
\>So I hear that he doesn't like racing against drivers who just 
go straight for the finish line. 
\>A friend of mine raced against him once, and Ono got really 
pissed because it was all over *\in a couple of minutes\*\.\

### String 33 ###

I hear that Green $\Wild Child\* had a really bad time at the
hands of a driver in a car with a "Naniwa" license plate, and
ever since, he goes after cars with similar license places that
happen to be out on the New Ring Road in the wee hours\.\

### String 34 ###

Head for the Shibaura Parking Area in the wee hours, and you
might meet $\Free Tree\*. 
\>He's a hothead where environmental issues are concerned, and 
he'll only race against cars with *\standard mufflers\* whose 
catalytic converters haven't been removed\.\

### String 35 ###

$\Caffeine X 3\* is really hung up on the number three. 
\>They only visit the Shibaura Parking Area on days of the month 
with a three in them, and they also only race against cars with 
*\"33-33" license plates\*\.\

### String 36 ###

$\Inferno Machine\* is apparently in dire financial straits, which
helps to explain why they go after anybody who looks like
they've got money. 
\>A friend of mine with *\10 million\* in commercial paper said they 
tried to race him when he showed up at the Shibaura Parking Area\.\

### String 37 ###

$\Dauntless Alexander\* apparently only races drivers who look
to be better than he is. They say he lies in wait near the
*\Rainbow Bridge\* for street racers to come by who've had at least
*\three wins\*, and challenges them to race\.\

### String 38 ###

Like Rolling Guys\*, the R Gang\* is made up of AE86 drivers. They
have a hard time with their underpowered cars, but they just
won't give up their beloved AE86 models even so. 
\>They've had dropouts over time, but they're still as agile on 
the road as ever\.\

### String 39 ###

Cupid's Arrows\* was the first all-female street racing team on
the Metro. They're a very cohesive unit, despite the
fact that they run the gamut from housewives to businesswomen.
\>The team's culture seems to have changed somewhat, though, since
$\White Faery\* became its third and current leader\.\

### String 40 ###

Strong Formation\* is apparently made up of American Football
players. They're best known for their sheer numbers. They use
the teamwork they've learned in football to race in formation.
\>I hear they can be found at parking areas milling around in
uniform. They shouldn't be hard to spot\.\

### String 41 ###

Second Chance\* is made up of people who race the Metro
in an attempt to overcome setbacks in their lives. Don't
misunderstand, though: they're not simply looking for sympathy.
\>It's powerfully moving to watch them try to overcome their
problems through racing. In fact, such sentiments might well be
the reason why they go so fast\.\

### String 42 ###

Far Away\* is made up of troublesome guys who don't like the idea
of young people being better than them behind the wheel. 
\>Not only are the drivers all veterans, their cars are 
understated in their power, including such 1990s models as 
R-32s and 70 Supras, all of which are thoroughly customized for 
\>street racing. 
That means they can go the distance, even against the latest 
and greatest thing off the factory floor\.\

### String 43 ###

Red Pollution\* is made up of foreigners who enjoy redlining it.
Other teams are scared of them because they race dirty. Their
motto is, "We only obey rules if they help us win." 
\>I hear there are some members who race clean, though. Apparently 
they joined the team without knowing what it was really about, 
and now aren't sure what to do about it\.\

### String 44 ###

Looks like Another Star\* and Top Level\* are still going at it
hammer and tongs. 
\>After all the time they've been racing the Metro, you can't help 
but wonder when they'll finally have it out, once and for all. 
\>That's not to say that anyone else who profanes their territory 
won't get the full treatment either, because I'm sure they will\.\

### String 45 ###

Rumor has it that there's a street racing team on the Metro
Expressway that's made up of agents from various national
intelligence agencies. It's called "Secret Code\*". 
\>Figures, doesn't it? They've all had expert-level driver 
training,  and there's no way they'll let you give it the gun at 
200mph. 
\>If you do something stupid, like beat them, you might just 
disappear (laughs)\.\

### String 46 ###

Have you heard of the all-female Juicy Heaven\* street racing
team? They're all hot babes who could probably have any man they
wanted eating out of their hands. 
\>And they're also pretty good behind the wheel. Take them for 
granted, and they'll take you out before you know what hit you. 
The loveliest rose has the sharpest thorns\.\

### String 47 ###

There's a rumor going around that $\Io\*'s back racing the Metro
Expressway again, after having been brought out of retirement 
by Tokio Jungle\*. 
\>Apparently Io lost interest when the Phantom Nine\* came along, 
but was provoked by $\King Speed\* into racing again.
\>Now, doesn't the thought of seeing an Impreza being driven 
like that give you a thrill?

### String 48 ###

I heard that Racing Storm\*'s $\Bargain Dot Com\* and $\Claim
Breaker\* work in the same department store.
\>Apparently $\Claim Breaker\* invited $\Bargain Dot Com\*, 
who was transferred to Tokyo from Nagoya, to join the team.
They've been battling as a pair ever since\.\

### String 49 ###

There's a group called "Offense 5" inside the team called 
Strong Formation\*.
\>$\Offensive Lineman\* and $\Energized Quarterback\* challenge
people to battles as a pair.
\>Both of them are incredible drivers.
Don't let your guard down around them\.\

### String 50 ###

Kyushu guys take their friendship seriously. $\Hayato Satsuma the
Wild Man\*, and the $\Roaring Volcano\* are both from Kagoshima
Prefecture, which apparently forges solid bonds. 
\>So if $\Hayato\* is in trouble, $\Volcano\* will come to his aid. 
You can count on it\.\

### String 51 ###

I look up to $\Blue Speed\*, for giving me the chance to race here.
And I'm determined to come to his aid if he's ever in danger of
losing a race, even if he doesn't want my help\.\

### String 52 ###

$\Mad Tripper\*, $\Heart of Pop\*, and $\New Wave Forever\* are known as the
most intense members of Aquarium\*, because they want to get
married more than any other member of their team. 
\>They always come on to a woman as a group, though. $\New Wave 
Forever\* makes the fast break, while $\Heart of Pop\* watches out for 
him as he follows in his wake, 
\>and $\Mad Tripper\* cautiously brings up the rear. Invariably, 
though, they all collectively wipe out. 
\>At some point, they began hanging out together a lot as a group, 
and apparently adopted this sequence when racing too\.\

### String 53 ###

Knowing that there are still some street racers on the Metro
Expressway makes me happy. I'm glad I kept on racing when I
was on the verge of quitting. 
\>I look forward to racing you again sometime\.\

### String 54 ###

Here I thought you were just a good-time guy, but there's more
to you than meets the eye. I still don't think you've completely
beaten me yet. 
\>I'll race you again if the opportunity presents itself\.\

### String 55 ###

Aw man! I worked on these settings for three solid months! 
And you took me out as if it were nothing! I won't accept this! 
When next we meet, I'll beat you!

### String 56 ###

I'm totally blown away, and there was an instant when
even I got a chill. This has been the most fun I've had racing
in a long time. Until we meet again!

### String 57 ###

You're really fast! I'd like to see you race against my bro!

### String 58 ###

You've shown me that there are any number of racers out there
who are faster than me. But you didn't see what I'm really
capable of. Keep that in mind\.\

### String 59 ###

I've seen hardly any drivers of your caliber even among the
pros. If I were an active player, I'd invite you to join my
team. 
\>I'm thinking of asking my leader for his thoughts about
racing you\.\

### String 60 ###

Wow. I had no idea that that car could be driven like that.
You've taught me a lot. Will you race me again sometime?

### String 61 ###

I'd say this race was down to about 90％ luck, with the other 
10％ being your driving skill, though there's no doubt that that 
10％ made all the difference\.\

### String 62 ###

Heh heh. You're fast. How did you manage to get so fast? Is it
because you drive like you mean it, as our team's leader says?

### String 63 ###

I wonder what the problem was......
Pace distribution? Cornering? My gear ratio settings?
\>There's no way that can be the end.
This will affect the dignity of the "Offense 5" at this rate!

### String 64 ###

I'm a star player! How could I lose in such a fashion! My fans
won't stand for this! We will race again, I promise\.\

### String 65 ###

I've crushed most of my opponents to date by sheer brute force.
You're the only one who's withstood that approach. But someday,
I will have redress for this insult!

### String 66 ###

Don't get to thinking you're such a big deal, just because you
beat me! I just didn't take you seriously enough. But next time,
I'll take you down! That's a promise!

### String 67 ###

Our reputation has fallen now that we've lost to you.
\>As a member of "Offense 5", I cannot let you go.
Be happy while you're still able\.\

### String 68 ###

It's been a long time since I was so upset by a race. I lost,
but I don't think there's much of a gap in our ability. 
\>I wouldn't be surprised whether you win or I do the next time we
race\.\

### String 69 ###

You beat me in that? I'm a tad amazed. But it was pretty fun,
too. Take it easy on me the next time we race, OK?

### String 70 ###

Was I driving erratically? My team leader often warns me about
that, but I get carried away so easily... Drivers really must
follow the rules of the road. 
\>I hope you'll decide to race me again sometime anyway\.\

### String 71 ###

You're just about the only racer who hasn't fallen for my
provocations. What do you mean, when did I try to provoke you?
I was trying the whole time. 
\>You're not very nice, you know that?

### String 72 ###

Mind if I have a look at your car? I'm wondering how you've
customized it. Oh, so you haven't really made any particular
alterations, and yet, you still drive as fast as you do. Hmm..\.\

### String 73 ###

I'm really grateful that you agreed to race me when my driving
is so dull. I know I have no right to ask, but would you race me
again?

### String 74 ###

Hey, did you need a laugh that badly? Well, go ahead. My own son
beat me just the other day, albeit in a computer racing game\.\

### String 75 ###

I haven't raced that intensely in a long while. I dashed
straight for the restroom when it was over, which I never used
to have to do. Must be getting old\.\

### String 76 ###

I honestly didn't think you'd beat me. I mean, I've been racing
around here for many years now. Having a newbie like you beat me
will make me a laughingstock\.\

### String 77 ###

That was pathetic. I came all this way from Kyushu, only to get
beaten... 
\>I've made up my mind that I'm not going back to Kyushu until 
I conquer the Metro and get a Tokyo Girl for myself!

### String 78 ###

Whew! I haven't gone all out like that in a long time. But I was
afraid I was gonna have a blowout there. After all, I need to be
useful when it counts, or I'll just drag the team leader down\.\

### String 79 ###

I lost because my skills were inadquate. 
\>You saw it too, right? Just a little more racing won't make that 
much difference, but I need all I can get if I'm ever to 
beat the best racing team on the Metro!

### String 80 ###

I just can't get in the groove. Is this typical of the driving
ability of street racers on the Metro? It's all I can
do to remember the layout of the road\.\

### String 81 ###

It's not because I wasn't any good that you beat me, but because
one of the monkey statues fell off my dashboard during the race.
That's why I lost, I think\.\

### String 82 ###

I've met lots of people in Osaka and on the rally circuit, but
never before have I met a driver like you. 
\>But don't be with what you've achieved so far, 
or you'll be dead. Always strive to be better\.\

### String 83 ###

I wasn't of any use at all. Bummer. I never thought that $\Blue
Speed\*, of all people, would be beaten. Who the hell are you,
anyway?

### String 84 ###

Man. I never thought you'd beat me. A miracle happened. That's
the only explanation I can think of. But the thing that makes
miracles miraculous is that they almost never happen. 
\>So I'll beat you next time. Nothing personal, you understand\.\

### String 85 ###

Hahh hahh... My throat is shot from shouting throughout that
entire race. That's how worked up I got: I completely forgot
myself\.\

### String 86 ###

Who are you, anyway? No one's ever beaten me on a 200bpm song
before. I'll have to get rid of all my audio gear now!

### String 87 ###

Oh my... You were going so fast that I nearly used my
emergency hyper-booster. And I'd have had to have left the
country in that event\.\

### String 88 ###

I never thought I'd meet someone whom my Z couldn't beat. The
Metro is truly a terrifying place! 
\>But I know that you must have a vulnerability. Once I've found 
it, I will take you down!

### String 89 ###

I investigated you and your car, and made a frightening
discovery: your car hasn't been specially customized, and you
yourself are the epitome of everyman. 
\>Given these findings, how  you could drive so fast is thus
 a mystery\.\

### String 90 ###

What outfit do you belong to? I absolutely refuse to believe
that an ordinary person could drive like that!

### String 91 ###

I acknowledge your amazing driving ability. It is also true,
however, that luck was on your side. You need to do more driving
if you seriously intend to be the best. 
\>You'll never win the title of fastest racer if you keep giving 
openings to your opponents\.\

### String 92 ###

I admit it: I was distracted, because I've just gotten engaged.
But that wasn't the only reason why I lost. The ability gap must
have also had something to do with it. 
\>Your driving is in a whole different class from the run of 
the mill racers around here\.\

### String 93 ###

At last, I've met the car of my destiny! I would pay any price
to follow you. Be warned: I'm pretty persistent\.\

### String 94 ###

How? How can you drive so fast? I feel certain that some part of
me will be transformed once I utterly defeat you!

### String 95 ###

Uh, hello? It's Papa. I'll be back in Nagoya soon. Be good, and
do what Mother tells you to\.\

### String 96 ###

We've been racing around here for a long time now. Back when we
started out, all-female racing teams were a rarity. 
\>Nowadays, however, I'm surprised at how many there are, even 
though Cat + Cat\* and Team Desire\* are really just cheesecake, 
when you come right down to it. 
\>I guess we're the only serious all-female racing team\.\

### String 97 ###

This guy I met at this mixer was a real piece of work! All I did
was ask him why he stuck to driving only an AE86, only to have
him suddenly fly into a violent rage! 
\>I think he should work on his driving skills before he tries to 
get himself a girlfriend\.\

### String 98 ###

Heartbreak is nothing to me; I'm used to it. That's why I've
dedicated myself to street racing\.\

### String 99 ###

If you're serious, sedans are the way to go. You get the
pleasure of having a big engine to move a big chassis. 
\>This is what racing is all about, I think, though I admit that 
my old AE86 was fun too, in its way\.\

### String 100 ###

My car just doesn't perform as well since I started using the
oil additive that I got from $\Chemical Ito\*. 
\>Anything free really is worth what you paid for it, I guess. 
Here's your chance to learn from my errors\.\

### String 101 ###

Try my oil additive. It's really good, I tell you! It's safe. It
won't blow up or anything\.\

### String 102 ###

$\King Speed\* has a special meaning to me. Seeing him race
convinced me to try once more to make something of my life. 
\>And even after he went away, the way he drove would still be
engraved on my heart\.\

### String 103 ###

I'd hit rock bottom when I first heard about him. 
\>He hadn't been all that noteworthy when we were in intermediate 
school together, so I never imagined he'd grow up to be the 
fastest street racer on the Metro. 
\>It's been three years now since he quit the Metro, but I'm still 
convinced he'll be back someday\.\

### String 104 ###

There are no guarantees that anyone can get real speed out of
cars that I've customized. 
\>I do feel, however, that they'll perform as intended if 
driven by someone who knows how to drive.
\>I have to wonder how many other customizers on the Metro
Expressway can make that claim\.\

### String 105 ###

I'm no car expert, but I really like the customized cars that
our team leader produces. If you asked me, though, I couldn't
tell you just what aspects I like\.\

### String 106 ###

Having our racing team wiped out changed him completely. I
broke up with $\Platinum Prince\* out of fear, not hate. 
\>The Metro Expressway is the only connection left between us 
anymore, which is why I keep racing\.\

### String 107 ###

I only just found out that $\Naturally Downtown Boy\* is actually
$\Risque Cat\*'s brother. Seems she's been racing the Metro longer
than him, though. 
\>He invited her to join his team, ASF\*, when her own team was 
disbanded\.\

### String 108 ###

$\Love Fantasy\* seems unhappy about being used more
casually than $\Spring Memory\*. He's been with the leader longer,
so I can't say I'm surprised at such anger.
\>It's also true, though, that $\Spring Memory\* is the better driver.
So what are you gonna do?

### String 109 ###

I found this really good ramen shop a while back, a place called
"Twilight," over by Ring Road 7. The owner is also a habitue of
the Metro, driving a Nissan Silvia. 
\>Seems he's out trying to find a street racer who saved his life\.\

### String 110 ###

I'm worried about my sister. She drives around like a woman
possessed, ever since her divorce. She joined my team so she
could keep racing. 
\>Lately, though, it's finally become clear to me that 
I can't help her anymore. I just have to hope that one of 
these days, she'll find what she's looking for\.\

### String 111 ###

Did you know that $\Platinum Prince\* is $\Risque Cat\*'s ex-husband?
\>They used to be on a team together, but got divorced when it was
disbanded. If it were me, I'd never leave him, seeing as how
he's rich and all\.\

### String 112 ###

$\The Doyen of the New Ring Road\*, A.S.F.\*'s leader, used to be on 
the car club team at a private college, and $\Love And Fantasy 
Erotica\* was an underclassman on that team. 
\>The story is that he begged $\the Doyen\* mercilessly to join $\the 
Doyen\*'s current team, until $\the Doyen\* finally gave in, against 
his better judgment\.\

### String 113 ###

Young drivers today have no class at all! And it's the fault of
the grown-ups who let them get away with it. Wouldn't you agree?

### String 114 ###

I'm sorry Harumi, but I've made up my mind: I'm not coming home
until I get to the top in this place\.\

### String 115 ###

$\Mad Stranger\* has been getting too big for his britches lately.
I may just have to take him down a peg, to teach him once more
just who it was who made him team leader\.\

### String 116 ###

Huh? Were you talking to me? You must be special, if you noticed
me\.\

### String 117 ###

There's this driver who's been pestering me lately to race him.
And I can't talk to my boyfriend about it, because he doesn't
know that I borrow his car to come here. 
\>So I've asked $\Speed Box\*, who's helped me out before, to help me 
out again if anything happens\.\

### String 118 ###

When my boyfriend died, I was thrown for a loss. Finding this
car has helped me get over it. Sometimes, when I drive down the
New Ring Road, I feel as if he's still there\.\

### String 119 ###

$\Tarmac Suzuki\* is an extraordinary driver. I realized it when he
was on the rally circuity, but it's even more obvious now that
he's racing the Metro. 
\>I'm looking forward to seeing how far he can go. That's most 
likely why we're on the same team together\.\

### String 120 ###

It's been seven years at least since I first hoped to be better
than $\Tarmac Suzuki\*. I figured that I'd beat him on the Metro
Expressway, if I couldn't beat him on the rally circuit. 
\>But he's got what it takes to drive fast anywhere\.\

### String 121 ###

Around these parts, a momentary screwup can mean defeat. You
need to be prepared for all contingencies, at all times. 
\>The Metro doesn't care whether you regret a mistake that costs 
you a race or not\.\

### String 122 ###

Five years ago, there was this street racer who hired me to
paint "One Hit And Away" on his R34 Skyline. That's how I got
into this line of work\.\

### String 123 ###

When I was driving around by myself, not part of any street
racing team, the racer who is now the leader of my current team
invited me to join him. 
\>He had to come looking for me three times, though, because I was 
either not at home or else asleep. But how could I say no to 
that kind of persistence?

### String 124 ###

I guess I got a little puffed up five years ago, but that all
changed with the advent of $\King Speed\*. I didn't come back to the
Metro until after he was defeated. 
\>Once I did, though, it didn't seem to have that same glow 
anymore. To tell the truth, I wasn't at all sure whether to 
accept $\Supersonic Napoleon\*'s offer to join his team or not. 
\>Now, however, I'm glad I did\.\

### String 125 ###

I did my best not to think of the Metro once I moved
to Hokkaido, but $\Supersonic Napoleon\* changed my mind. 
\>I was thrilled to think that someone would actually need someone 
like me, and everyone on this team dates back to when I last 
raced the Metro. 
\>The only thing that could make this any better would be if $\King 
Speed\* were to start racing again\.\

### String 126 ###

We're in the Nitro Age now! If you want it cheap and good, come
and talk to me. I get the best nitro, from the US!

### String 127 ###

I put together a team once, but I never imagined I'd join a team
myself to go street racing. I think $\Bloodhound\* is really
something in that regard, because he races alone\.\

### String 128 ###

Why did I decide to start racing again? Simple: I want to
straighten out my idiot protege. 
\>He thinks he's a big deal since people started calling him the 
fastest street racer on the Metro Expressway. 
\>But you seem to have put some spark back into him.
Do me a favor, would you? Stay on his case for me. Thanks\.\

### String 129 ###

None of us are getting any younger. Five years ago, we were all
in our prime. Now we're all turning into fuddy-duddies. I quit
the Metro for the research purposes. 
\>Things have changed completely since then. I mean, even $\King 
Speed\*, who ran us all off the Metro, is gone. 
\>But I'm just getting started, though I don't expect anyone from 
the old days is left to. remember me. So I'm embarking on the 
creation of a new legend, that of $\Radical Newton\*\.\

### String 130 ###

Hey, Yoichi, can you see how fast I'm going in the RX-8 you gave
me? It's like our child. And I'm going to keep on racing it\.\

### String 131 ###

I was dating this girl three years ago, you see, but my work
wasn't going well and I got deep into debt, which I ended up
saddling her with. I'll apologize if I ever see her again\.\

### String 132 ###

I feel sorry for him. Who? 
\>Oh, $\Mad Tripper\*. You see, he's over the moon about 
Juicy Heaven\*'s $\Seductive Amethyst\*, but it seems that
she's on the verge of getting engaged to Nomoto, 
\>another guy on our team. 
\>I know I should tell Mad Tripper about it, but I just can't bring 
myself to break it to him\.\

### String 133 ###

The other day, another street racer came up to me and said, "It
takes two to make a kid, but not necessarily for that kid to
grow up." 
\>I may just go to the publishing unit and put together
a collection of quotable street racing team leader quotes\.\

### String 134 ###

There are some hot single babes racing on the Metro!
There's $\Midnight Cinderella\*, $\Impatient Speed Princess\*, and
$\Black Cat\*, too... Sigh. 
\>I'd be able to race them if I were just a little bit better 
behind the wheel…

### String 135 ###

In other words, $\King Speed\*'s return to street racing was
predicted by Nostradamus! Oh my! Oh, uh, sorry about that. I
just wanted to get that out of my system. I regret it already\.\

### String 136 ###

Say what? Oh, no, I'm not shooting rays, or making cross chops.
I just naturally assume this posture whenever I talk to someone.
Think nothing of it\.\

### String 137 ###

Everybody gets all worked up about street racing, but just
seeing the beautiful sight of the Metro by night
always makes me feel better. Do you know what I'm talking about?

### String 138 ###

I was amazed to see hardly any racing teams from when I used to
race the Metro. 
\>Then I saw teams like R. Gang\*, Cupid's Arrows\*, and SS Limited\* 
out there, which made me feel better. 
It's been three long years since I last got out there\.\

### String 139 ###

Some girls say that guys who drive stickshift are cool. Well, I
like girls who drive stick myself. 
\>There's just something fascinating about a small, feminine hand 
pushing that gearshift around, you know?

### String 140 ###

I recommend that you do your homework when buying used cars. 
\>A friend of mine says that when he hit a speed bump in a
restaurant parking lot in a used car, the air bag opened and
caused a panic\.\

### String 141 ###

I--I went on a date... with a man... the other day... We went
driving... in Hakone... in separate cars, but still... 
\>He was driving an AE86, and before I knew it, I'd left him in 
my dust... I kind of feel bad about the whole thing..\.\

### String 142 ###

I think it's about time I changed my tires. Soft-grip tires wear
more rapidly, which makes them more costly. I suppose the way I
drive might have something to do with too, come to think of it\.\

### String 143 ###

