### String 1 ###

Hey, you're a street racer, aren't you. Have you heard of The 
*\Wanderers\*? They're... how should I put this? Think of them as 
kind of having a price on their heads. 
\>They're hard to find, but there are some apparently credible 
rumors that they can sometimes be found in or near the parking 
area. 
\>If you're thinking of racing against them, I'd suggest you start 
by gathering information on them at these places. 
\>I just bet you'll pick up a useful tip or two as to how best to 
take them on\.\

### String 2 ###

Listen to me. The other day, there was guy who looked weak, so I 
challenged him to race, figuring he was an easy mark. I was sure 
I'd coast to the finish line, no problem. 
\>But when the race started, I realized I had three opponents, not 
just one. I barely had time to think that this was cheating, 
when one of them blocked me to let another get ahead.
\>I never stood a chance. What a bunch of cheaters. Watch yourself 
when you race, because there's people out there taking racers on 
in groups likethis\.\

### String 3 ###

Have you tried it yet? What do you mean, "What?" I'm talking 
about *\time trial racing\*, that's what. 
\>You know how the usual race just has you and your opponents 
driving until one of you gives out? 
\>There's no start or finish line, no nothing. Well, there are 
some races where you do have a finish line, and the winner is 
whichever racer gets there first. 
\>So you might try it that way if you get tired of regular street 
racing\.\

### String 4 ###

Taking a nap is the thing to do when you're feeling tired. Would
you mind waking me in 20 minutes?

### String 5 ###

I bet you've got a handle, like the rest of us do. 
Tell me, does it bother you? 
\>If so, then you need to watch your driving, whether you're 
actually racing or not. If you hit other cars, you'll get a 
corresponding handle, for example. 
\>Your handle also changes according to your speed and your win 
rate.  Oh, and there are some handles that you can get for 
driving in odd ways, too. 
\>It's pretty tough to control what kind of handle you have, 
though, because it's what other people decide to call you. 
\>If it still bothers you, though, then you need to be as careful 
as you can about how you drive\.\

### String 6 ###

I'm studying handles rather than racing itself. 
Are you interested in *\handles\*? 
\>Many people still think that these are just nicknames 
used among street racers themselves. 
\>Analyses based on my investigations show, however, that that 
isn't necessarily true. Apparently, handles change depending on 
what you do, especially during a race! 
\>In simple terms, things like how many races you've been in and 
how many wins you get affect your handle, as do embarrassing 
things like how many times you hit a wall. 
\>That's pretty much what I've figured out so far\.\

### String 7 ###

I always get nervous before a race, and end up having to go to 
the bathroom. I hold out until I can't fight it anymore. 
\>I've had to quit so many races because of this problem of mine 
that now everybody calls me chicken. So you be careful if you 
quit before a race is over! 
\>Or to put it another way, quit a lot of races before they're 
over, if you want people to call you chicken. I can't imagine 
anyone would want that, though\.\

### String 8 ###

The Gallery is not only for reviewing wins and losses, but also 
for checking how you manage to run races without colliding with 
other cars on the road. 
\>There's just something too cool for words about that instant 
where you thread the needle between two other cars when you're 
all going like a bat out of hell. 
\>And if you can drive like that, you're sure to get a really 
sharp, cool *\handle\*\.\

### String 9 ###

I hear that there's some kind of Legend-type *\handle\* out there. 
I don't know anything specific, but... Let me see... Well, the 
first thing to do is to just ask around the parking area! 
\>And then you have to win races like crazy--oh, and stay away 
from walls as much as possible! If you can do all of that, then 
people will start calling you by this special class of handle.
\>It's not easy, but it's worth the effort!

### String 10 ###

I'm in trouble. Lately I haven't been able to get myself 
together, so I've just been driving and letting the races pass 
me by for the past several days. 
\>And it seems that if you do that, you get a special kind of 
*\handle\*. You weren't thinking of trying that out, were you?

### String 11 ###

Sometimes it happens, you know? I mean, you come across drivers 
who make you say, who's that? 
\>I mean, they come out on the course without hardly racing, and 
they don't talk to anybody at the parking areas either. 
\>I hear that there's a particular *\handle\* for people like that on 
the Metro\.\

### String 12 ###

Do you know your way around the Edobashi Junction? If not, you'd 
be doing yourself a favor to take some practice runs over there. 
\>You see, it's got some tough curves, but if you can manage them, 
you can really differentiate yourself from the competition 
there. 
\>And if you really can't deal with it, well, about the only thing 
I can suggest is that you stay away from there, at all costs\.\

### String 13 ###

The C1 Loop is a strange place. I mean, the inside and outside 
lanes theoretically have the same shape, and yet, they seem 
completely different when you actually drive on them. 
\>In particular, it seems easier to get up to speed in the outside 
if you know what I mean. And yet, they're no wider than the 
inside lanes, so I'm too spooked to try it. 
\>What do you think?
In any case, if you're gonna race, you need to pick the places 
that work best for you personally\.\

### String 14 ###

That stupid cat! It went and left scratches all over the
freshly waxed hood of my car!
\>And that's on top of using my tires to sharpen its claws! 
I'm gonna give its owner a piece of my mind!

### String 15 ###

If there's an opponent you just can't beat, you might want 
to try thinking more about where you initiate a battle with them.
\>Everyone has a place where they're weak, no matter how fast 
they are.
For example...what about a toll booth?
\>You need a lot of courage to pass through one of those at high 
speeds\.\

### String 16 ###

So "understeering" means not turning tight enough when 
cornering, and crossing into the outside lane? 
\>I thought it was the other way round: you turn too tightly 
enough, and cut over into the inside lane! 
\>Hmm. So "understeering" happens when you don't steer hard 
enough. Now I get it! Thanks for the tip!

### String 17 ###

NA tuning is no easy thing. The process of maximizing 
the properties of an engine is the same as what it takes to 
strengthen a top athlete's physique. 
\>Tuning the engine's innards means power that only the driver can 
understand. No one on the outside looking in will get it. It's 
just you and that engine, in splendid isolation. 
\>You just keep working away at it. 
What do you say? Does NA tuning, or should I say, 
the way of NA, appeal to you?

### String 18 ###

I really like four-wheel drive vehicles. That burst of 
acceleration you get as you come out of a turn is terrific. I 
mean, they just grab the road and won't let go. It's the best!

### String 19 ###

Sports cars? Front-wheel drive, naturally! The RX-7! I get 
emotional just thinking about the sheer power that comes out of 
that sequential twin turbo high RPM rotary engine. 
\>And then there's those uniquely stylish, almost liquid body 
lines. 
\>Plus, it's got a low center of gravity, and its weight is 
equally balanced front and rear, which means it really  handles 
well, too. 
\>When it turns, it really turns sharp. It's the ultimate sports 
car\.\

### String 20 ###

The first rule is, how does it look? That's how I picked out my 
cars. I mean, I don't know anything about cars, and I got a 
thrill the moment I laid eyes on the 180SX. 
\>Afterwards, I came to appreciate its charms. It's perfect, no 
matter where we go: whether I'm on a date, or on the racing 
circuit. 
\>It's got a compact rear-wheel drive engine with solid output, 
and handles well too. It's a real pleasure to drive. Before I 
knew it, we'd spent more than decade together. 
\>I don't drive it anymore, but I would get behind the wheel again 
in a heartbeat if I could\.\

### String 21 ###

Sports cars? I'd have to say the R-34, the Skyline GT-R. I think 
we're in the twilight of the age of the sports car. 
\>The RX-7 and the Supra were hits during the height of the sports 
coupe's popularity, when all the car manufacturers were fixated 
on speed. And I feel that the GT-R was the real standout. 
\>Nowadays, environmental friendliness is what everyone's talking 
about. And sure, that's important, but I hope people won't 
forget about the adventure of higher speeds in the process. 
\>I personally plan to always drive a GT-R\.\

### String 22 ###

This is the best car in the world. It convinces you that Japan 
has the best technology anywhere. The Celsior is one of the 
finest sedans ever to come out of Toyota. 
\>Luxurious and classy on the one hand, quiet and powerful on the 
other, with terrific performance. It's a lot like me. I wouldn't 
have a chauffeur driving it for me. 
\>This is one of those cars that one has to drive personally. 
I really love to drive this car\.\

### String 23 ###

I saw these cars that crashed on the Metro, y'know? They were 
all crunched up. Too bad, y'know? But my car's tough. So I'm 
safe, y'know? 
\>It's got reinforced riveting, tower bar, strut bar, and lower 
arm bar. It's got more bars than you can shake a stick at, 
y'know? 
\>Even if it rolls over, I'll be fine. A solid body is more 
important than anything else, uh-huh\.\

### String 24 ###

I customized my car thoroughly tfor drifts, but it drifts all 
over the place. I can't control it. I guess moderation in all 
things really is important. 
\>I'll have to try being a bit more restrained in how I customize 
my car from now on, I guess.
\>Maybe I could start by upping the traction control and ABS 
systems... And then there's the LSD too... Where do I start?

### String 25 ###

You're not a real racer if you only drive cars that have high 
performance in their initial parameters. Try gear settings 
matched to the torque levels at various RPMs. 
\>If you can shift gears under those conditions, then you can 
really show what that car can do. It's not easy, though. 
I can't do it!

### String 26 ###

The camber angle increases the ability of tires to hold the road 
when taking a corner. 
\>You see it with people too: you can brace yourself better by 
spreading your legs a little, but if you go too far, you lose 
stability, and suffer weakness in straight-ahead traction. 
\>Tau would refer to balance, I guess.
With a negative camber angle, you only need a little Tau output 
to keep your balance. 
\>There are also some people who max out their camber angles, 
caring more about appearance than balance\.\

### String 27 ###

Pitch refers to when a car shakes backwards and forwards. Yes.
Stepping on the brake tilts the car forward, and the shaking
around that time is called pitch. Yes.
\>When braking at corners, weight is put on front pitching and the 
front tires. Turning the wheel in this condition increases the
\> 
front tires' grip thanks to the extra weight and makes it easier 
to turn. Yes.
\>It's a good idea to drive while thinking about pitch, weight 
placement,
and movement in this manner. Yes.
\>Understood? Yes\.\

### String 28 ###

You're that breakout racer, right? 
I saw you race against $\Bloodhound\* the other day. 
You were teriffic! I might just become a fan!

### String 29 ###

Eh? Someone beat the $\Platinum Prince\*? No way! 
I might have to  worry about the racer who took him 
down, though\.\

### String 30 ###

Congratulations on taking out $\Snake Eyes\*. I had a 
feeling you'd be the one to do it. I'm proud to have 
had the chance to race against the likes of you\.\

### String 31 ###

Have you heard of the *\Thirteen Demon Lords\*? 
There used to be a gang by that name on the Metro, 
a team of 13 amazing street racers, led by $\King Speed\*. 
\>They used to rule the Metro, but they've long since broken up, 
it seems. 
\>And that's without taking into account the apparent fact that 
they didn't travel in a pack to begin with, or so I hear. 
\>I guess $\Bloodhound\* is the only member of that gang who's still 
racing anymore. That fellow is something else. 
And at his age, too\.\

### String 32 ###

There's a street racer called the $\Platinum Prince\*, who's said to 
be the fastest racer on the early  morning C1 Loop. 
\>I hear he's supposed to have been the leader of some racing team 
or other, at one time, until another racer wiped them out. Now 
they say that the Platinum Prince races to avenge that defeat. 
\>And if you prove yourself on the C1 Loop at night, he might just 
challenge you to a race\.\

### String 33 ###

Have you heard of the Three from Kurosaki? 
They're a trio of brothers who race on the C1 loop as part of 
Phantom Nine\*.
\>They say that $\Golden Wisdom\*, the middle one, is pretty wild. 
I hear he brings up the rear when they race\.\

### String 34 ###

The other day, a friend of mine said he'd seen $\King Speed\* on the 
C1 Loop, but I don't believe it. I mean, I saw his car go up in 
flames. I saw it with my own eyes\.\

### String 35 ###

There's a guy called $\Lonely Wolf\*, who goes to the Shiodome 
Parking Area at night. 
\>I hear he's been driving around here for a long time now, and he 
snubs newbie street racers because of that. 
\>My pal said that he asked Lonely Wolf to race him any number of 
times, but only got an offer after he'd competed in at least *\100 
races\*\.\

### String 36 ###

There's a guy called $\Lonely Wolf\*, who goes to the Shiodome 
Parking Area at night. 
\>I hear he's been driving around here for a long time now, and he 
snubs newbie street racers because of that. 
\>My pal said that he asked Lonely Wolf to race him any number of 
times, but only got an offer after he'd competed in at least *\100 
races\*\.\

### String 37 ###

The $\Rolling Master\* who races the C1 late at night 
was the origianl leader of Roling Guys\*.
\> 
He's long retired but I hear he shows up if you're driving
*\Rolling Guy1's car\*\.\

### String 38 ###

$\Yellow Desperado\*, who hits the Shiodome Parking 
Area late at night, has some very unique preferences
\>He absolutely refuses to race against any car that 
looks as though it could go more than *\124mi\* at a 
stretch\.\

### String 39 ###

The other day, I ran into $\Cutey Hips\* in the wee hours at the 
Shiodome Parking Area. 
\>I bragged about my brand new *\rear spoiler\*, but she got really 
annoyed and refused to race against me. I wonder why\.\

### String 40 ###

I met up with $\Shonan Affair\* on the C1 Loop at 
daybreak, but he wouldn't race me. Seems he only 
races against cars with rotary engines\.\

### String 41 ###

$\Speedy Fanfare\*, who hangs out at the Shiodome Parking Area, 
seems to hate racers who lack vision. He won't race you unless 
you've bought at least $\three cars\* already\.\

### String 42 ###

Do you believe in ghosts?
\>Theres this car that had a big crash a while back.
The car's been seen around lately.
\>Isn't that scary?q

### String 43 ###

Do you want to race against $\Jump Start Maki\*? 
Then you want to go to the Shiodome Parking Area. 
\>I'll warn you, though: he may not race you if your car is 
equipped with *\nitro\*, because it'd upset his trademark burst of 
speed off the starting line\.\

### String 44 ###

There aren't as many guys racing the Metro as constantly as 
there used to be. We keep getting new racing teams popping up 
all the time. 
\>In that sense, the Rolling Guys\* are really something...
even if they aren't very good\.\

### String 45 ###

I've been racing the Metro for five solid years in an AE86, 
and the Rolling Guys\* still haven't asked me to join them. 
I just don't get it\.\

### String 46 ###

Speed Planet\* formed in a college car club, which explains the 
low average age. Their youth is their biggest advantage. 
\>On the other hand, they're seriously lacking in funds for tuning 
their engines, compared with other racing teams. 
\>Another problem is the apparent disparity in driving ability 
among their members\.\

### String 47 ###

M-O-E\* is made up of computer geeks. 
They're informed about cars and racing, as well as computers, 
all of which makes them unusually speedy.
\>I hear they practice on faithfully rendered simulators of the 
Metro too\.\

### String 48 ###

The duo of CAT X CAT\* is getting a lot of attention from male 
Metro street racers. 
\>There's $\Black Cat\*, a hot, mature-looking babe, and $\White Cat\*, a 
cutey who's going to a community college. I hear they're good 
friends, and always race as a team\.\

### String 49 ###

Together with SS Limited\*, Max Racing\* is one of the 
most renowned sedan racing teams on the Metro. 
\>They get performance out of these cars on a par with sports cars 
by customizing them in ways that compensate for their 
traditional weaknesses.
\>Something else they're renowned for is the fact that those 
perennial also-rans, the so-called "High-speed Three 
Musketeers," are also part of their outfit\.\

### String 50 ###

Family Business\* is an unusual racing team, in that its members 
are all related to one another. 
\>At 62, their leader, The $\Godfather\*, is still very active behind 
the wheel, along with his son and grandson. 
\>I hear they've got various problems at home, but they're pulling 
themselves together through street racing\.\

### String 51 ###

The Twisters\* are hung up on rotary engines. 
They've been racing the Metro for quite a while now. 
\>They've changed cars over time, but their lineup itself seems 
practically unchanged from the time they established 
themselves.
\>They make a big deal of being old-school street racers, and it 
shows in the sense of rivalry that they seem to have with newer 
racing teams\.\

### String 52 ###

Tri-edge\* uses all Mitsubishi cars. They have less experience 
than Top Level\*, but their cars as every bit as customized. 
\>Their leader is also very charismatic, commanding tremendous 
morale from his teammates. Rumor has it that he's had a rivalry 
going with the leader of The Pleiades\* since\* their college days\.\

### String 53 ###

A number of street racing teams have some history, of which the 
one that's supposed to have the most talent is Rings\*. 
\>Some say that they're not as good as they used to be since their 
current leader, the sixth, took over, but they still rule the C1 
Loop.
\>They've cut back on new members to try to keep their skills up, 
a move that's backfired on them, because they're not as open as 
they might otherwise be\.\

### String 54 ###

I went to a hospital near where I live the other day because I 
wasn't feeling too good. 
\>And in the parking lot back of the hospital were a bunch of 
customized cars that looked like they could go really fast. 
\>I wonder if the hospital staff are themselves street racers on 
the Metro, you know?

### String 55 ###

I don't recommend just cruising the C1 Loop in the wee hours 
right now, because you just might get dragged into races between 
Freedom Light\* and Blood Tears\*. 
\>And you see, no matter how much Freedom Light\* wants to run clean 
races, they won't give an inch to Blood Tears\* . 
It comes down to a showdown  between rival powers. 
\>Though you might stand a chance if you were a better driver than 
the both of them, possibly\.\

### String 56 ###

I hear that Departure\*, a team which had hung it up, is back in 
action. 
\>$\Happy Chappy\*, their leader, is one sharp cookie, so I bet he'll 
try to avoid getting mixed up with dangerous groups such as the 
Phantom 9\*. 
\>They didn't used to have much teamwork at all, but now, I get 
the sense that they finally are getting their act together in 
that regard, you know?

### String 57 ###

One popular team on the Metro right now would be Cat + Cat\*, 
which was formed when $\Black Cat\*, who used to be known as 
Glamorous Mami, invited $\White Cat\* to team up with her.
\>They've not only got the looks, they've also got the racing 
ability to go with it. So it's tough to take them down. You need 
to beat them both to the finish line. 
\>Beef up your driving skills and customize your car to the 
utmost\.\

### String 58 ###

Two Limit\*'s $\Red Lotus Fang\* and $\Excellent Pleasure\* have been 
friends since their college days, and often race together.
\>$\Excellent Pleasure\* is often late to the race, though, which 
means that Red Lotus Fang\* has to race by himself until $\Excellent 
Pleasure\* gets there, which he invariably does, 
\>just in the nick of time. And oddly enough, $\Red Lotus Fang\* 
apparently never gets angry or upset about this\.\

### String 59 ###

When you beat me, I figured it was about time for me to 
hang 'em up, and turn things over to my successors\.\

### String 60 ###

I never thought anyone would beat me. 
My pride is in tatters.
I wish we'd had someone like you on our management team\.\

### String 61 ###

I was already thinking of quitting the car club, 
because I never really liked driving anyway. 
\>After racing you, though, I think I'm finally starting to see a 
glimmer of what makes street racing so exciting\.\

### String 62 ###

To tell you the truth, coming to the Metro from Nagoya really 
hasn't been all that much fun. Meeting you has made me want to 
stick around, though. We'll race again sometime\.\

### String 63 ###

Aw man, how could you beat me? 
This is worse than the time I scored only 40 out of 100!

### String 64 ###

I was naive to think I could beat you. 
I'm going to better myself now!

### String 65 ###

I never imagined you'd be so fast. 
Now I'll never be able to keep my team in line!

### String 66 ###

I can't see why I keep losing. 
What did you think of my driving?
Please, tell me what you really think\.\

### String 67 ###

Yo! You're pretty good! 
You might even be good enough to take on the Japanese race 
driver I ran across in the US\.\

### String 68 ###

I need to be better than my bro! 
To do that, I need to take you out first\.\

### String 69 ###

My sideburns are hanging limply because you beat me.
I'll beat you the next time we meet!

### String 70 ###

Aw, come on! My former leader will lose face because of this! 
Race me again! Please!

### String 71 ###

Losing out to you has affected my chances of becoming the next 
leader of my team. I need to do a lot more racing\.\

### String 72 ###

Wow. I figured you had to be a famous Nagoya street racer, you 
were going so fast. I've been so antsy lately because I've been 
spoiling for a race, and I misread you\.\

### String 73 ###

I have to win if I'm going to pay off my engine tuning bills! 
Race me again\.\

### String 74 ###

Ugh! I can't maintain my concentration! 
I was so sure I had sufficient experience! 
How did you manage to beat me?

### String 75 ###

I guess it was dropping my horsepower that did it. That improved 
the handling, but at the cost of acceleration. I guess I'd 
better boost the horsepower again\.\

### String 76 ###

Good grief. If only $\Blue Rider\* was as hard-nosed 
as you are.
Love isn't as easy to understand as street racing\.\

### String 77 ###

I don't feel I can beat $\Sweet Blues\* yet. I'll build up 
my confidence by taking you down for a start\.\

### String 78 ###

At last, I have a new target! You! 
We'll race again sometime\.\

### String 79 ###

I sunk a lot of money into my car. But I've invested far more 
love than money in it. The ultimate sentiment that one has for 
one's car comes down to the question of victory or defeat\.\

### String 80 ###

I'd have caught you if I'd customized my car even a 
little bit more. The compressor really does matter, 
I guess\.\

### String 81 ###

We lost because I couldn't provide sufficient 
support to our leader, I suppose. 
\>You would never have beaten us if I'd done a better 
job. That said, such talk is merely sour grapes. 
\>It would be more constructive to work on my skills, 
so as to avoid future defeats\.\

### String 82 ###

Your defeat of me means we must now race one another again. 
In other words, we must dispose of the pollution that this first 
race represesnts. My heart aches…

### String 83 ###

I should have put my glasses on before the race. The data I had
on the race course was no match for your driving skill\.\

### String 84 ###

I held back from my usual way of driving all over the place.
\>What do you say? If you still think I was driving like a madman, 
then complain to my passengers, not me! 
They wanted it that way!

### String 85 ###

I should know better than to race after a full night's 
work... I'm not making excuses, though. I'll take you 
down next time for sure!

### String 86 ###

Did we lose because I was late to the race? 
I'm doing the best I can, you know. I just don't know
why I don't get there on time\.\

### String 87 ###

Have you raced against our leader? He's a real racer.
So don't think you've made it just because you beat 
me!

### String 88 ###

I can't win! My secret training regimen is useless! 
I may as well quit the team\.\

### String 89 ###

Cars are hard to figure out! But I feel like I can win
next time. Wait--haven't I said that before?

### String 90 ###

The kids who come to the shop look up to this car. 
So it kills me to lose like this. It's like trampling on 
their hopes and dreams\.\

### String 91 ###

There was no uncertainty in the way you raced. 
That would explain why you were so fast. 
That's the only car I know that's like that\.\

### String 92 ###

I've hung by my fingernails off a cliff hundreds of meters in 
the air. Racing you was even more intense than that. 
\>I'm willing to believe that you took down $\Skull Bullet\*, all 
right. You hung on from start to finish, and when all was said 
and done, you won\.\

### String 93 ###

I can't believe I lost in such a lame way! If my bro had seen 
that, I'd die of embarrassment. I think I'll go pick on the 
Rolling Guys\*, to try to make myself feel better\.\

### String 94 ###

I double-checked my data. It was perfect. I was 
driving better than usual. And yet, you beat me. 
What's that supposed to mean?

### String 95 ###

I was so sure of this car, and yet, I lost anyway. 
I guess the problem isn't with the car after all\.\

### String 96 ###

It's been three years since I took over as leader of this team 
I know we're still considered the wimps of the Metro, but we're 
proud of our unwavering love for racing here. 
\>And that will keep us going forever\.\

### String 97 ###

This'll knock you out: we're on the verge of having a mixer with 
Cupid's Arrows\*! Our leader is really well-connected. 
I should have some really good news to report soon. Stay tuned\.\

### String 98 ###

$\Rolling Guy No. 2\* sure is excited about this mixer 
that 's coming up. I hope he doesn't end up spinning 
his wheels over it\.\

### String 99 ###

Word has it that there's a racing team on the Metro that's made 
up entirely of electronic game developers. 
\>I'd be lying if I said I didn't want to race on that team, but I 
love my AE86 and this team I'm on that much more\.\

### String 100 ###

Yo! How's it going? You might be interested to know that we 
design logos for other street racing teams. If you like, we'll 
do a design for you too, maybe a silhouette or something?

### String 101 ###

I have a premonition that something big is going to happen on 
the Metro in the not-too-distant future, like that time five 
years ago, when that legendary street racer came along. 
\>This is my intuition, anyway. Let me know if you hear anything\.\

### String 102 ###

It's been three years since we last saw that legendary street 
racer. This has become a whole  different place since then.
\>We've seen some new racing teams pop up, and some other teams 
fade away. Some teams have seen their members join  other teams 
and go on racing after breaking up.
\>I personally experience the drama of this place by racing these 
streets myself\.\

### String 103 ###

When is a car at its most brilliant? Why, it's when you meet 
someone who's faster than you are, and put him away. 
\>That's when you get to see a car at its most beautiful. 
I want to capture that moment on film\.\

### String 104 ###

I'm very grateful to our leader
After all, he took me in when I was despairing after my
last team was crushed.
\>I want to pay him back someday\.\

### String 105 ###

Oh no! I screwed up at work again! 
The editor-in-chief is gonna be mad at me. 
I know! I'll go street racing to make myself feel better! 
\>Oh wait, the editor-in-chief races on the Metro Expressway 
a lot too..\.\

### String 106 ###

Computers are too hard to figure out these days. The IT 
revolution hasn't done much to lower the barriers to entry to 
people who aren't computer experts, like me\.\

### String 107 ###

$\Rising Bear\* is my mentor in both writing and street 
racing. I hope someday to be a good enough racer that 
he'll recognize me\.\

### String 108 ###

Do you know about Jun, from Team Desire\*? I'm really hot for her.
Sigh... I wonder what she's doing right now. 
I want to drive a 180SX so she'll pick me up\.\

### String 109 ###

Our leader seems to believe that $\Canopus the Heretic\*,
from Team Desire\*, is a woman. 
\>It pains me when I see him like that, but when I think of what 
it would do to him if he knew the truth, I haven't the heart to
tell him that Canopus is actually a guy.
\>Sigh... It's like pieces of a jigsaw puzzle that won't fit 
together, no matter how hard you try\.\

### String 110 ###

Sigh. I lost again. And I could have won if we'd been 
driving trucks instead\.\

### String 111 ###

Aw, man, Tsuchiya always treats me like a kid. 
It's high time he recognized me as a racer. 
Man oh man..\.\

### String 112 ###

My great catch banner has been covered in mud. How can I face
Tsuchiya like this?

### String 113 ###

Contests are harsh, whether in sumo or street racing\.\

### String 114 ###

I hear that $\Black Cat\* used to go by the handle of 
Glamorous Mami, and picked up her current handle 
when she formed Cat + Cat\*. 
\>My personal opinion, though, is that she was never really all 
that "glamorous," i.e., built, which is why everybody calls her 
by her current handle. But don't tell her I said so!

### String 115 ###

I've never said so to his face, but I have great 
respect for $\Flying Octopus\*. 
I think our team's success is all down to him\.\

### String 116 ###

Mamoru's been getting a lot better lately. 
He's my brother, so I'm glad on that score. 
It's still got me on edge, though\.\

### String 117 ###

To tell you the truth, I've had it with this "High-speed Three 
Muskeeters" crap. Maybe $\High-speed Blue Thunder\* gets excited 
about it, but we never get any attention from it. 
\>I say enough is enough\.\

### String 118 ###

Hmph! Who does Jun think she is!?
\>What does she mean "It'll take you longer to get
married if you waste your time battling"!?
What gives her the right to interfere with my life like that?
\>I mean, take a look at your dress!
......That's what I'd like to tell her!

### String 119 ###

Do you know why $\Canopus the Heretic\* wears that get-up?
\>It started because, when he tried to join that team, $\Betelgeuse 
of the Night\* teased him by saying that he'd have to look like 
the other members of the team. 
\>So he went along with it, reluctantly. Now, however,
he really seems to like it for its own sake\.\

### String 120 ###

Shinsuke is such a wimp, it drives me up the wall. 
He's worked for 15 solid years, and has the 
performance to prove it. 
\>And was it for the good of the company? It was for the sake of 
the family, right? He should be more proud of the fact. But no, 
he's an idiot. 
\>And the family is falling apart precisely because he's so 
spineless\.\

### String 121 ###

I envy Misa. Whatever she may say to others, she 
knows and accepts Shinsuke the way he is. 
My man, on the other hand--Mutter grumble..\.\

### String 122 ###

I wasn't sure what was going on when the old man 
said we should get into motor sports. 
\>Now, however, I'm genuinely satisfied with the way things are 
turning out. I guess Father really does know best\.\

### String 123 ###

This is causing my brother in law all kinds of grief. I hear 
he's separated from wife because of this racing team. He's such 
a nice guy, too. I feel bad for him\.\

### String 124 ###

For crying out loud! Where are you, Hiromi? 
And after you went and said we'd be together forever after our 
next win--if I find you, I'll trash you but good, I will!

### String 125 ###

It's my fault that the family's gone all to pieces. 
So it's my responsibility to put things back together 
again\.\

### String 126 ###

I don't trust $\Manhattan Dreamer\*. 
I just know he's plotting to overthrow our leader and 
take over our team one of these days.
\>I owe our leader a debt, which is why I want to stop 
Manhattan Dreamer, if nothing else\.\

### String 127 ###

"The way is not laid out ahead of oneself; rather, it 
is that which you leave in your wake." 
\>A certain someone said this to me. And it seems to me that if 
one drives around these parts, one eventually finds oneself able 
to judge matters only in terms of "victory" or "defeat". 
\>I know because I was like that myself, once upon a time, 
\>until this certain someone taught me that there is another realm 
of being, which led to me becoming the person you now see before 
you. 
\>And I say to you too: if you lose your way, return to where you 
began, and you will find that which you had lost sight of\.\

### String 128 ###

Our leader has said that "theory evolves through 
exposure to reality, not through blind adherence." 
\>I once built up theories of my own, which I was convinced were 
perfect. And I did not permit myself to recognize any other way 
of thinking. 
\>My theories, however, were ultimately just that: theories, with 
no practical application. 
\>But it wasn't until I joined my current team that I discovered 
the difference between theory and practice\.\

### String 129 ###

When I first started racing the Metro, there was always 
something nagging at me. 
\>Then I met the leader of my current team, who told me that "one 
must use one's rage to give one the winning edge; anger is not 
something to inflict upon others." 
\>The next thing I knew, I was sobbing like a baby, and begging to 
join his team. I recall those words whenever I get upset at 
racers who have no sense of order or self-control\.\

### String 130 ###

I can remember days when I'd drive all night long without being 
passed even once. I considered joining a racing team of others 
who, like me, didn't make much of an impression on people. 
\>Thing was, I went unnoticed even by them, which was depressing. 
\>Then our leader came along and said, "Presence is something that 
one actively imparts; it is not something that others passively 
absorb." 
\>When I heard these words, the scales fell from my eyes, and I 
understood. Rather than making any constructive efforts on my 
own behalf, 
\>I had assumed that others would simply "absorb" the nature of 
who and what I am. The words of the $\Leader of the Lost\* are 
profound indeed\.\

### String 131 ###

I'm really glad I joined this team. You see, I hadn't been able 
to get along with anyone else, no matter where I went. And the 
leader said to me, 
\>"Mutual understanding and acceptance, not length of time 
spent, is what matters among comrades." 
\>Isn't that great? I finally felt that I was where I needed to be 
when I heard those words\.\

### String 132 ###

Seems there's a team made up entirely of Subaru Impreza drivers 
on the New Ring Road, called Another Star\*. 
\>The fact that they all drive the same make of car is the main 
thing they have in common. But on the Metro, we have no use for 
more than one team with a given concept. 
\>The time is gonna come when we're gonna have to see which of us 
is faster: us or them\.\

### String 133 ###

There was a period of a few months when we had a CT9-A driver on 
our team. He quit because he just didn't fit in. 
\>Looking back, though, I think it was our loss, because he had a 
style all his own. 
\>It's not as if he was incredibly fast or anything, but when he'd 
race, he could bring this weird kind of pressure to bear on you. 
\>Anyway, I hear he started his own team on the C1 Loop. I just 
bet it suits his particular temperament\.\

### String 134 ###

Hamada really bugs me, because he thinks nothing of 
tuning everybody's cars, not just ours. And he does it 
on the side, not as part of his business. 
\>I have to admit, though, that that lack of concern on his part 
is actually part of why people like him\.\

### String 135 ###

Seems like the racers formerly known as the *\Thirteen Demon Lords\* 
and the *\Twelve Ruling Saints\* have shown up on the Metro 
Expressway again, just under new names. 
\>Somebody seems to have turned them into a new racing team. 
\>Granted, they all have legendary status in the street racing 
community, so it would not be all that surprising if they were 
to come back after even a prolonged absence, 
\>do a little racing to get their instincts back, and get back on 
top on the Metro before too long. Being an old-school street 
racer myself, I need to keep on top of this situation\.\

### String 136 ###

I can't get complacent, not with the recent surge in really 
skilled customizers running around. 
\>There's ASF\*'s leader, the $\Doyen of the New Ring Road\*, and $\Garage 
Haruo\*, who's launched his own brand, just for starters. 
\>It might just be time for me to close up my curry shop and go 
into the customizing business full-time\.\

### String 137 ###

Say! Hamada went and put some oddball parts on my car again!
Sure it handles better than before, but it doesn't put out as
much horsepower! Now I'll never beat the Phantom Nine\*!

### String 138 ###

I used to think our leader wasn't good for much, but now I see 
that he's really pretty sharp. I think it's fair to say that 
it's because of him that our team hasn't been wiped out. 
\>I do my best to ensure that I don't trip him up. I don't want to 
find that I've suddenly become a burden on him\.\

### String 139 ###

I really wish Mita would wise up already. No matter how many 
times I repeat myself, he never gets what I'm saying. I think 
Murakami has much more potential\.\

### String 140 ###

In Slow, Out Fast! In Slow, Out Fast! In Slow--
Oops! Sorry! I'm just making sure that I remember 
what other street racers have told me\.\

### String 141 ###

I think Gotoh is capable, if a little gloomy. 
What really gets to me to me is that know-it-all 
expression on his face\.\

### String 142 ###

I've had a rivalry going with Freedom Light\*'s leader, 
$\Harvest Waltz\*, since we first started racing around 
these parts. 
\>We started teams around the same time, and have 
competed ever since to see which of us will be the 
fastest racer on the Metro Expressway. 
\>I want nothing better than to see him eat his heart
out when I've beaten him\.\

### String 143 ###

Freedom Light\*'s leader, $\Harvest Waltz\*? 
He doesn't hold a candle to our team's leader. 
\>The day will come when our team, Blood Tears\*, will be respected 
by all other street racers for being the fastest team on the 
Metro. Now's the time to get on board\.\

### String 144 ###

I'm not interested in who's got the best racing team 
on the Metro. It just so happens that the Blood Tears\* 
team holds that title, that's all\.\

### String 145 ###

It takes more than just a few competent street 
racers to make the fastest team on the Metro. 
\>You need to get all the members on your team up to 
speed, so to speak, if you want other teams to 
respect you. 
\>Freedom light\* isn't even worth talking about on that 
score. They've got one, maybe two really fast racers
aside from their leader, $\Harvest Waltz\*. 
\>It's really overreaching of them to see our team, 
Blood Tears\*, as rivals\.\

### String 146 ###

Do the C1 Loop in five minutes? Are you nuts? Four and a half 
minutes is the standard, didn't you know that? I'm telling you,
Freedom's Light\* doesn't even bear thinking about. 
\>It'd take them a hundred years before they'd be up to par!

### String 147 ###

I just can't seem to get the settings right. 
\>I come out of the garage thinking I've got it this time, only to 
feel it's still not right once I hit the road. Maybe the problem 
is with me, rather than my car\.\

### String 148 ###

Sigh. I just thought of the perfect name while I was 
racing, but I just can't remember it now! 
I guess I'll hit the road again\.\

### String 149 ###

When you pull into a parking area, the first thing 
to do is hit the restroom! The restroom, I tell you!

### String 150 ###

People seem to think there's something pathetic about game 
development. The typical concept is one of staying late or even 
overnight at the office. 
\>But the fact is, conditions that harsh hardly ever occur. 
I think people just like letting their imaginations run away 
with them. 
\>Of course, that's not to say that such conditions don't
ever occur. You know you're in trouble when you find
that you can't recall when you last slept at home. 
\>But like I said, that sort of thing hardly ever happens,
you know?

### String 151 ###

The thing to do is drive as fast as you can while still
maintaining control. 
\>I know how good it feels to go fast, but if that's all 
you think about, you could well get a bad handle as a 
result of driving into walls or bumping other cars\.\

### String 152 ###

Hey! This isn't my car! 
That's what happens when you use popular colors..\.\

### String 153 ###

Modern car navigation systems are really useful. 
\>Older systems would break down if you got into the 
mountains, but today's car navigation systems never 
seem to lose their way. 
\>They also get realtime traffic info, which helps keep 
us out of traffic jams when we're racing at speed\.\

### String 154 ###

Even if I say, "Sorry, but I gotta go! I've got a report to 
write," I still want to race even just a little longer. At this 
rate, I really might end up repeating this year!

### String 155 ###

Some car designs are just plain out of style. 
It wasn't that long ago that rounded corners were really in. How 
are things nowadays, do you suppose?

### String 156 ###

If there's somebody you just can't beat, one trick 
you might try is race a bunch of times against 
someone you can beat, and rack up funds that way. 
\>I'm not saying it's very nice to pick on
somebody who's weaker than yourself, mind you\.\

### String 157 ###

My car's going to be featured in an upcoming issue 
of Changing Stage Magazine. This could just be my 
ticket to fame!

### String 158 ###

Look at this magazine! They featured my car, but only
so they could write trash about it. 
\>I'm crushed! I'll get that writer Tamura if it's the last thing 
I do! We'll have this out on the road!

### String 159 ###

Somebody came up to me at the parking area the 
other day and attacked me, saying that an article I'd 
written was trash.
\>I guess he didn't like the fact that I wrote up his car in 
Changing Stage as being all show, no go. So we raced, and I blew 
him away. In other words, I was right about his car all along\.\

### String 160 ###

Looks like $\Rolling Guy No. 2\* had a mixer with members of the 
Cupid's Arrows\* street racing team. His manner strongly suggests 
that he didn't last very long, if you ask me\.\

### String 161 ###

The party with Cupid Arrows\* was absolutely terrible. 
They called us the weakest team on The Metro and acted 
surprised that we were still around...
\>Next we'll have a party with the girls from Juicy Heaven\*.
We'll make sure to make it go well this time!

### String 162 ###

Looks like $\Rolling Guy No. 2\* had a date the other day 
with Juicy Heaven\*'s $\Voluptuous Aquamarine\*. Looks 
like he also got put away again, too. 
\>He looked pretty depressed as he said, "I'll stick to
racing for the time being."

### String 163 ###

Oh, uh, it's you. You haven't been hanging out with $\Midnight
Cinderella\* by any chance, have you? She's just too much for 
me, I tell you. Don't tell her I was here\.\

### String 164 ###

A local guy shouted at me something fierce the other day. 
\>He was going on about silly little things like how my cat, King 
Speed, left scratch marks on the hood of his car and sharpened 
his on his car's tires. 
\>I don't see what all the fuss was about.
After all, it was a lame-ass car, so why should I 
give a damn?

### String 165 ###

