### String 1 ###

Listen to this: last week I went racing, but my radiator hose
snapped, and I spent the whole day with steam billowing up in my
field of view as I drove. 
\>And as a result, I got stuck with a *\handle\* that means I'm a 
reckless driver! 
\>Maybe they mistook me for someone who uses too much nitro or 
something. But it's rude to treat a lady like that, no matter 
how you slice it!

### String 2 ###

Why are you racing the Metro? I want to be known as
the King of the Metro! Rumor has it that the main thing you need
to do to get that *\handle\* is win races, basically. 
\>But more than that, you need to have as few losses as you can 
manage. It's not easy, but if you can get that handle, it's 
worth it! 
\>My determination to succeed keeps me hitting the road in search 
of this goal! 
\>And I say to you that if you have a tangible objective, and 
don't simply race for the sake of racing, then you'll be a 
better driver and competitor!

### String 3 ###

Seems there are some *\handles\*, the mere sound of which will make
you quiver all over. You get these by by hitting racing 
opponents with sedans. 
\>Oh, and you need commensurate driving skills, too\.\

### String 4 ###

Hey, since when has there been a driving school on these
streets? 
\>Look at this street racer who not only weaves all over the 
place, but keeps crashing into walls and other drivers to boot! 
\>That wasn't you, was it? If it was, you'll get yourself a
special kind of *\handle\* for your trouble\.\

### String 5 ###

There's a rumor going around that says you can get different
*\handles\* depending on what times you frequent the streets. 
\>Me, I'm sticking to the late night hours, because that's the 
kind of handle I want. I hope it won't be too long before people 
start noticing\.\

### String 6 ###

Another pleasure of the Metro has to do with pulling onto the 
shoulder and just watching the view from the Metro Expressway 
by night. 
\>If you do it too much, though, you could end with a funky *\handle\* 
before you know it, because people will wonder, what you're 
doing there. Makes no difference to me, I admit\.\

### String 7 ###

Have you familiarized yourself with Shibuya Rte. 3 yet? The
critical thing to remember here is making U-turns on the
underpass. 
\>You, see you take the Shibuya Exit at speed, only to
hit a sharp curve. It takes real skill to get through that
smoothly. 
\>It's pretty rough until you get used to it, but your win/loss 
record is sure to improve if you can only learn how to do it\.\

### String 8 ###

The highlight of Rte. 3 has got to be the Hills, Roppongi Hills.
I envy the people and companies that have offices there. 
\>I don't fully know just what they're doing there, except that 
they're making money hand over fist in IT! They buy expensive 
condos and zoom around in luxury cars! 
\>Sigh. I wonder if there are any unattached guys in that 
category... Eh? Oh no, no street racers.
Just forget it, right now\.\

### String 9 ###

Terms like "FF" and "FR" are frequently tossed around in
reference to the type of drive train a car has. 
\>"FF" means front mounted engine with front-wheel drive, while 
"FR" means front mounted engine with rear-wheel drive, and 4WD 
means four-wheel drive, of course. 
\>Other abbreviations you may hear are "MR" and "RR"\.\

### String 10 ###

Used to be that I didn't know the first thing about cars. 
\>I even thought a sedan was a make or model, when it's really any 
car that can be divided into a four-door passenger compartment, 
an engine, and a trunk, like a taxi. 
\>I'm still not clear on the difference between sedans and coupes, 
though. 
\>The way I understand it, a sedan has a reasonably roomy back 
seat, whereas a coupe has little or no back seat at all, but it 
can be hard to draw the line in some cases. 
\>For the most part, you can say that if it has two doors, it's a 
coupe, and if it has four doors, it's a sedan. Sure there are 
exceptions, but you just have to memorize them.\\

### String 11 ###

If you're gonna drive a Fairlady Z, the one you want is the
Z-32. Even now, I consider it the ultimate sports car. 
\>It was the first 280PS made in Japan, with front engine, rear-
wheel drive. 
\>Everything about it is beautiful and a solid performer, whether 
it's the engine, the suspension, or the chassis. If the Fairlady 
Z is poetry in motion, then the Z-32 is its finest example\.\

### String 12 ###

This rhythmical controllability is one of the GC8 (Impreza) best 
points. It responds directly just as you control it.
\>And depending on how you control it, it reveals various sides.
Each of them has their own meaning, and the more you drive it
the more you come to understand various things.
\>Dialogue between a person and a car. If one were to ask the GC8 
why it moves the way it does, it's sure to reply. And if you 
keep talking to it, you come to understand various things.
\>I fell for this car totally while I was doing that.
I think I'm going to keep talking with this car forever\.\

### String 13 ###

The chassis of the Toyota 80 Supra is like a big, beautiful
dolphin. It imparts a tremendous sense of luxury and excess. 
\>Its mischievous high-powered rear-wheel drive reinforces the 
playful dolphin image. 
\>Drive it in a relaxed way, and you might even feel as though you 
were, in fact, swimming through the deep blue sea. 
\>Give it a little gas, and you can cut loose with overwhelming 
power, which is lots of fun. You could get hooked on this car\.\

### String 14 ###

Say what you will, it's hard to get real speed. 
\>Tightening up the suspension means a less comfortable ride, 
while customizing the engine makes more of a job of 
maintenance, 
\>so factory settings are probably best if you just want to drive 
in regular street-legal fashion. 
\>On the other hand, there's also an indescribable pleasure in 
these sorts of maintenance-related hassles as well. 
\>All of a sudden, I want to go fiddle with my car some more. 
Maybe I'll add an oil pressure meter or something\.\

### String 15 ###

Knowing when and how much to apply the brakes is crucial; that
is, finding the "braking point," if you will. 
\>If you can't figure out at what point you need to hit the brakes 
to reduce your speed in time, you're gonna run into walls, real 
quick. 
\>The way I do it is, I make note of buildings and billboards in 
the vicinity, and use those as my guideposts, my "braking 
points," at every turn. 
\>It's not easy to make note of all of these points along the 
entire length of the Metro, but there are enough guideposts to 
make it manageable. 
\>All you can do is just drive the roads and commit them to 
memory, a little at a time\.\

### String 16 ###

Listen, about Initial Torque--Huh? No, I'm not talking about a
sequel to the automobile manga. 
\>Rather, initial torque: you know how the car suddenly starts 
handling differently when the LSD kicks in, and the car becomes 
harder to control all of a sudden? 
\>The way to ease effect that is with the initial torque. I hear 
you can get by with doing it just a little bit at a time. I 
still don't fully comprehend it yet, though. 
\>I've also heard that lowering the initial torque will make the 
LSD kick in rapidly if you start to drift, and thus make the 
tires go around. That also sounds pretty complicated, though\.\

### String 17 ###

You say you don't know how to configure your car's settings?
\>Hmm. Well, first of all, you should pick one car to drive
extensively, and keep driving it in accordance with its baseline
settings. 
\>If you try to adjust more than one setting at a time, you'll be
hard-pressed to figure out what's changed, or how. 
\>Try lowering the chassis as far as it will go, for a start, and 
see what that feels like. Then make fine adjustments until 
you're satisfied.
\>What matters is configuring these various settings one at a 
time, with care. Take it slow, because you can mess up the car's 
behavior if you're not careful\.\

### String 18 ###

I hear $\Snake Eyes\* was finally beaten. I wonder who took him
down. Eh? It was you? So you're the street racer who took down
$\Snake Eyes\*. I'm glad to meet you like this!

### String 19 ###

$\King Speed\* is ancient history now. I mean, $\Snake Eyes\* is the
current fastest street racer on the Metro, right? The
team he leads, the Phantom Nine\*, sure seems fast enough too. 
\>I'd like to race them myself one of these days, but I bet they
wouldn't have anything to do with a beginning street racer like
me\.\

### String 20 ###

$\Dirty Fox\*, the sole female member of Phantom Nine\*, may look like
a sweetheart, but don't let that fool you. She's a total vixen,
just as her handle suggests. 
\>It doesn't matter whether she really hasn't realized what $\Snake 
Eyes\* wants to do with her, or is just pretending she doesn't 
know; she's a tease in either event. 
\>She might challenge you to a race if you demonstrate the
kind of skill necessary to take down all of the street racing
teams on Rte. 3\.\

### String 21 ###

I hear that $\Melancholy Angel\*, formerly one of the Thirteen Demon
Lords, is racing the Metro once more. She was
supposedly spotted driving down Shinjyiku Rte. 4 the other day.
\>The Metro has special significance to her. She may come looking
for you if you defeat all the street racing teams on Rte. 4\.\

### String 22 ###

$\Hopeless Home\*, who hangs out at the Shibuya Parking Area, is a
feng shui enthusiast. I hear he only races against drivers who
live in what, to him, are lucky directions. 
\>He says that roads heading for *\Shibuya\* are lucky\.\

### String 23 ###

Word is that $\Touch-Me-Not Eternity\*, who races on Rte. 3, is the
successful proprietress of a very exclusive club on the Ginza.
\>Apparently, she can only go racing on the Metro on *\Mondays\*, 
because that's when the club is closed\.\

### String 24 ###

The other day at the Shibuya Parking Area, I invited Impatient
Speed Princess to race me, but she turned me down, saying, "Some
other time. You look tired." And I admit I was tired, because
\>I'd already driven 13mi that day. So I was moved by the
consideration she showed for me, a potential opponent!

### String 25 ###

If you're looking for $\Iron Triangle\*, head over to Rte. 3. It
won't do you any good, though, because he only races against
*\Mitsubishi cars\*\.\

### String 26 ###

$\Shepherd Nekozawa\*, who drives Rte. 3, is a real chicken.
\>Apparently, he's so afraid of losing, that even if you challenge
him to a race, he'll turn you down. He only accepted a
challenge from me after *\passing me on the road three times\*\.\

### String 27 ###

$\Raspberry Kiss\* seems to be avoiding most race challenges 
nowadays, because she's afraid of being accosted by weirdo 
street racers ever since she was featured in a car magazine. 
\>The other day, though, she agreed to race me because I'd put a 
*\carbon\* hood on my car, and she apparently thought it made me 
seem like a real street racer! 
\>It was worth paying for that particular part replacement 
after all\.\

### String 28 ###

Potters really are concerned with the shape of things. Take
$\Craftsman Manabe\*, who races down Rte. 3. I hear he only races
drivers who've *\modified\* the aerodynamics of their cars\.\

### String 29 ###

$\Midnight Silver Wolf\*, who races down Rte. 3, is apparently
completely uninterested in cars sold in the year 2000 
or later.
\>If you want to race him, you'd do well to get yourself *\a car
made in 1999 or earlier\*\.\

### String 30 ###

If you want to battle $\Shimokitazawa 2000cc\* you should try visiting
the Shibuya line on *\weekend dawns\*\.\

### String 31 ###

$\Illusion B\*, who races down Rte. 3, is apparently very concerned
with how best to pull tailslides. For this reason, he says he's
only interested in racing drivers who've modified their cars'
*\taillights\*\.\

### String 32 ###

$\Matterhorn\*, who hangs out at the Shibuya Parking Area,
comes by his fondness for the Fairlady Z honestly: his father
was also fond of them. 
\>Apparently, this is why he only races against other drivers who 
also appreciate similar *\Z-series\* cars\.\

### String 33 ###

If you want to race $\Tomorrow Again\*, put *\the best muffler\* you can
buy on your car, and head for the Shibuya Parking Area. 
\>He'll ask to record the sound your car makes with that 
particular modification\.\

### String 34 ###

Looks like $\Storm Streamer\*'s come to the Shibuya Parking Area. He
only races drivers with confidence enough to put *\standard tires\*
on their cars, just so you know\.\

### String 35 ###

The other day, I was driving down Rte. 3, when $\Glitter Eiji\*
surprised me by suddenly challenging me to a race. 
\>Apparently, he mistook my frequent *\daybreak\* driving to mean that 
I was a confrere, and therefore, that he'd have to take me down\.\

### String 36 ###

$\Shinji the Harbinger\* really seems to be looking out for his
protege, $\Glitter Eiji\*. It's the only explanation for his coming
to $\Glitter Eiji\*'s aid when Eiji's in trouble. 
\>If word of that sort of thing gets out, he's gonna find more 
fans among female street racers. That sucks\.\

### String 37 ###

Moon Tribe\* is made up of good-looking young esthetic men, which
makes them popular with female street racers. Apparently, looks
aren't the only thing they have going for them, either. 
\>They seem to take their driving pretty seriously too. And they 
also pay pretty close attention to how they dress\.\

### String 38 ###

Hey! How's it going? The night is young, you know. I wonder if
Moon Tribe\* is racing tonight\.\

### String 39 ###

Burnism\* is made up entirely of musicians, I hear. And they're
pretty good behind the wheel as well a with their instruments.
\>You can really get a rocking feeling just from the way they
drive. They're doing more street racing than anything else,
though. 
\>There's no indication that they're going to be giving any 
concerts or making any new CDs any time soon\.\

### String 40 ###

Burnism\*'s members say that they hit the Metro when a
studio session isn't going well. 
\>Given how frequently they've been racing the streets lately, 
I guess they must be having real problems in the studio 
right now\.\

### String 41 ###

I hear that actor Takashi Tobikawa founded a team called "The
Bone\*," whose members are all in the industry, and pretty fast,
too. If you race them, be sure to get their autographs\.\

### String 42 ###

Have you heard of this quirky restaurant in Yokohama? It's 
called "La Liberte," and it seems to get a lot of street racers. 
\>Its owner is also the leader of a street racing team called 
"Knife and Forks\*." Apparently, he's started offering discounts 
at his restaurant to drivers who beat them on the road. 
\>Why not head over to Rte. 3 and challenge them?

### String 43 ###

Don't rest easy if you take $\Hesitant Stoneface\* down, because
$\Insomniac Crow\* will come around if that happens, which means
you'll have to run two consecutive races\.\

### String 44 ###

$\Guilty Phoenix\*, who works as an assistant director at one of the
big TV stations, can always be found hanging around $\Dancing
Devil Dog\*, who's a director there. It's the same on the Metro
\>Expressway, too. $\Guilty Phoenix\* is very pro-active when $\Dancing
Devil Dog\* is challenged to a race. $\Dancing Devil Dog\* treated him
as a nuisance at first, but now he seems to be used to having
\>$\Guilty Phoenix\* around, and relies on him when he's racing\.\

### String 45 ###

This is martial arts on asphalt. Talk about getting the
adrenalin pumping! You will give me a chance to get even, right?

### String 46 ###

I'm gonna have to get serious about this pretty quick. Next
time, we'll see what's what\.\

### String 47 ###

I've become overly dependent on $\Insomniac Crow\*. I really need to
improve my driving skills if I want a realistic shot at being
the fastest driver on the Metro\.\

### String 48 ###

Yoshi told me that I need to improve my skills before I start
trying to cop an attitude. After racing you, I think I'm slowly
starting to understand what he meant. 
\>Street racers with real style also have the driving ability 
to back it up\.\

### String 49 ###

I had no idea that there were any racers left on the Metro
Expressway who could still give me a real run for my money. And
just when I'd been thinking of quitting street racing, too. 
\>But now, I'm personally going to observe your street racing 
career\.\

### String 50 ###

I don't get it. I thought I had all the settings configured
perfectly. Race me again after I do some reconfiguring, OK?

### String 51 ###

Sedans are pretty hard to manage. It feels as though the weight
keeps tossing me around. It handles especially badly in the
turns. 
\>Though I suppose it could be that I'm not a good enough
driver yet\.\

### String 52 ###

Simply winning races isn't all that hard. What I want is to race
in a beautiful manner, which means that sometimes I end up
losing races that I should have won\.\

### String 53 ###

I've never raced so hard before. I could get hooked on this!
Let's race again when you have the time\.\

### String 54 ###

I came out of the turns OK. Was there a problem with extending
my top speed? No, that wasn't it either... Man! 
Why did I lose?

### String 55 ###

You're not a bad a driver, you know that? I'd love to see you in
action again sometime!

### String 56 ###

Hey you! Maybe you beat me, but don't look at me as I'm good for
nothing! I've only just started out at street racing! Next time
for sure, you'll say, "Ya got me!"

### String 57 ###

I may not be as good as the other members of my team, but I've
had my driver's license for seven years now! I'm so mad about
being beaten like this that I won't be able to sleep at night! 
\>I won't let it end this way!

### String 58 ###

There's a simple reason why $\Crying Singer\* and $\Strange Drummer\*
aren't getting along: a woman. 
\>$\Strange Dreamer\* likes $\Little Venus\*, but doesn't have the nerve 
to make a pass at her, and so he's jealous of $\Crying Singer\*. 
\>Because of all this, I was against bringing women onto our team 
in the first place\.\

### String 59 ###

I just can't get along with $\Indulgent Dream Child\*. He's so
gloomy. He tries to come across as a warmer, happier persona on
the team, but it seems like he's putting on an act. I also don't
like the fact that he keeps trying to avoid me, too\.\

### String 60 ###

The first time I heard $\Insomnia Crow\* DJ I was blown away.
\>But I was even more blown away when I saw him drive.
The guy's a genius!
\>I'm unbelievably happy that I get to pair with him\.\

### String 61 ###

I ran into $\Crying Singer\* at a Parking Area the other day! I'm a
fan of his band, so I was so thrilled that I got him to
autograph my dashboard!

### String 62 ###

I tell you, my team's leader is really just a front. $\Twilight
Guitarist\* is the better driver, but as you know, $\Crying Singer\*
is a self-centered so-and-so, 
\>and nobody's been able to set him straight, which makes wonder 
sometimes whether what we have can really be called a "team"\.\

### String 63 ###

Some say that $\Twilight Guitarist\* is a better driver than $\Crying
Singer\*, but that's a lie. 
\>He's good, but long past his athletic peak. In a flat-out race, 
I think $\Crying Singer\* would come out on top\.\

### String 64 ###

Sheesh! No sign of $\Little Venus\* again! Could she be trying to
avoid me?

### String 65 ###

Eeek! That was $\Revolver Heaven\* that passed by just now! Oh man,
what a stud!

### String 66 ###

I don't understand complicated stuff. I just race, and give it
my all. My team's leader is skilled and smart, but he has this
tendency to get caught up in pointless stuff\.\

### String 67 ###

Me, a better driver than $\Crying Singer\*? 
\>Don't be stupid! He may not look it, but he works hard, driving 
lots more practice laps than me, so he can thoroughly 
familiarize himself with the territory\.\

### String 68 ###

If you want to see one of my DJ gigs, I'm at the club run by
$\Hesitant Stoneface\*. 
\>We often race together on the Metro Expressway. 
He races an opponent first, then I come along. We're
the best duo on the Metro!

### String 69 ###

The other day, I went to a club, where I was surprised to
meet a guy who said he races the Metro, together
with his protege. I hope we meet up out there sometime\.\

### String 70 ###

The Metro is a whole different place these days, what
with all the weakling street racing teams that are out there
now. 
\>I want to race against someone where I can go all out,
where emotions run high on all sides! 
\>Maybe the reason I'm feeling this way is because Phantom Nine\* 
has been blowing away all the street racing teams with 
any vitality\.\

### String 71 ###

I've driven a lot of cars in my time, but the one I've settled
on would be the 70 Supra. I don't know how many good years I've
got left, but I'm gonna stake them all on this car. 
\>We're pals forever, after all\.\

### String 72 ###

Wow! $\Raspberry Kiss\* is actually the actress Shiho Yasui! 
\>You could make a pretty cool TV show by pairing her up with 
Takashi Tobikawa, don't you think? We could base it on that 
street racer that everyone on the Metro is talking about, right?
\>You know, the one who took down $\Skull Bullet\*... whatshisname...
Oh, and $\Crying Singer\* would do the theme song, of course\.\

### String 73 ###

Hey, listen to this! $\Midnight Cinderella\* has no ambition
at all! You might not think so to look at her, but she's really
pretty solid. 
\>She turned me down when I offered to teach her about makeup! 
And when I asked why, she said, "There's a racer that I'm after. 
I'm trying to focus solely on that objective."

### String 74 ###

Mr. Miyauchi, one of the directors at the station where I work,
is really something. I respect him both professionally and as a
street racer! 
\>I don't know how he can get so much speed out of that 70 Supra. 
I may start driving one myself if I get to be a director\.\

### String 75 ###

$\Scramble Wyvern\* is really something. He usually stays in his
team leader's shadow, but his time will come, if he just puts
his mind to it. 
\>What matters, in street racing as well as in acting, is whether 
one can rise to the occasion or not. 
\>It seems to me that the time is fast approaching when he'll have 
to decide whether he's going to end up as Takashi Tobikawa's
student, or make his own big break\.\

### String 76 ###

Hey, you! You need to deck out your car! Are you putting stylish
vinyl panels on it? Plain cars are boring! 
\>Aerodynamics are crucial too! It doesn't take much of a change 
there to alter a car completely, I tell you. 
\>And there's neon, too! You need neon if you wanna stand out from 
the crowd! 
\>The key here is to choose colors that won't clash with your 
car's paint job, while also being stylish and mature in 
appearance\.\

### String 77 ###

Me, be better than my mentor? No way, no way, I tell you! I
admit I'd be lying if I said I didn't want to go beyond him, but
I want him to be my mentor, now and always! 
\>Don't talk about this stuff again! Please! I'm begging you!

### String 78 ###

What does Takashi think he's doing racing so late at night when
we've got a location shoot tomorrow? 
\>I know that we're the fastest team on Rte. 3 thanks to him, 
but this stuff doesn't pay the freight!

### String 79 ###

One time, I told a customer that aerodynamics are just
decoration, and that the important types don't get it. The boss
belted me one for that, hard enough to break my back teeth. 
\>And I was just kidding, too. There was no call for that. Right,
aerodynamics aren't decoration at all, which you probably know
already\.\

### String 80 ###

Hmm... You know, the older you get, the harder it is to go
racing two or more days in a row. 
The Sandman is passing me by.
\>The Sandman is passing me by... Say, that's a pretty clever turn
of phrase, don't you think? What? Boring? Oh, is that so…

### String 81 ###

What kind of music do you listen to when you race the Metro
Expressway? I listen to Eurobeat and nothing but! 
\>You can get into an even better groove when you listen to your 
favorite music as you race! 
\>But you need to be careful if you're listening to something up 
tempo, because you could speed up without realizing it, and that 
could cause trouble!

### String 82 ###

Don't you think that monthly parking spaces in Tokyo cost too
much? I mean, they're packing tens of thousands of cars into
what are mostly vacant lots, with room to spare! 
\>And they're so cramped that it's a pain to get into and out of! 
It just burns me up!

### String 83 ###

I'm thinking of getting a new car, which means I won't be
driving my current car for too much longer. But the thought of
that makes my heart ache, you know? 
\>I mean, I drive it practically every day. I want it to find a 
new owner who'll take good care of it\.\

### String 84 ###

I have no problem going fast on the Metro, but I
can't stand roller coasters, and I don't know why. 
\>Maybe it's because I have no control over their direction or 
speed, or because I'm afraid of heights... Man! Just thinking 
about it gives me the shakes!

### String 85 ###

I'd say my driving today was about a 70 out of 100. There's
still a lot I can learn about this car. I'll tinker with the
settings some more tomorrow, and then go racing again\.\

### String 86 ###

I'd give my driving today about 80 out of a possible 100. I
think I've managed a passing grade this time. 
\>But I'll never be the fastest street racer on the Metro if I 
accept this as good enough! I've got to strive to be 
better still!

### String 87 ###

Whew! I've finally reached the 90％ driving threshold! It sure
was hard work getting to this point!

### String 88 ###

I think I could safely give myself full marks for my driving
today. That's based solely on my own personal criteria, though.
\>This car isn't on a par with the one that took down $\Snake
Eyes\*…

### String 89 ###

Morning has broken, I see. I need to get a nap before I go to
work in the afternoon\.\

### String 90 ###

Ack! Look at the time! Once again, I've raced straight through
to morning!

### String 91 ###

