### String 1 ###

Some racers do nothing but drive, while others
just hang out at parking areas.
\>So if you really want to be the top dog,
you need to get on the horn yourself.
I wouldn't blame you for thinking that's a hassle, though\.\

### String 2 ###

Have you heard of the Wanderers? 
They're these lone wolves who don't do much
racing at all. For starters, many of them don't even
\>hit the road unless there's someone out there that they
think is worth the trouble. And even if they do
think you're good enough, some of them still won't 
\>race if they don't like you. I guess they're what you'd 
call the rarest of beasts\.\

### String 3 ###

You find some guys who try to get you to race them in gangs of 
three or more, one after another. I think that's just SO sleazy! 
I mean, that amounts to victory through attrition! 
\>I guess I could always counter with a team of my own, though. 
But I just don't seem to have the knack for holding teams 
together. 
\>What? You too? 
\>Well, in that case, I don't know how much good this will do, but 
the only way to beat those weasels is to conserve your energy as 
much as possible, drive as cautiously as you can, 
\>and keep them from passing you at any cost! Yeah, yeah, if it 
were easy, anybody could do it, I know\.\

### String 4 ###

Man, that really burns me up! 
\>Oh, sorry, I'm not talking about you. Listen to this. I was in a 
race the other day, and just when I was about to win, another 
car on the opposite team got into the act. 
\>Two against one, you know? I mean, that's just dirty pool! And 
you better watch out for cheaters like that too. You never know 
where they'll turn up next\.\

### String 5 ###

While it's important to beat your opponent in a race, another 
crucial factor that separates winners from losers is how well 
you can dodge other cars on the road. 
\>And you need to be especially careful in the wee hours, because 
that's when traffic is heaviest\.\

### String 6 ###

Many of the *\Wanderers\* only come out when they see things going 
to their liking, so if you want to race all of them, the trick 
is to drive the Metro under all kinds of conditions. 
\>And you can pick up otherhints by asking around at parking areas 
too. I recommend it highly\.\

### String 7 ###

What *\handle\* are you going by currently?
\><silence>
\>Hmm. That's pretty cool. You see, handles are how both the fans 
and other racers tell you what they think of you. 
\>So if you don't like your current handle, you might try a 
different approach to racing, or improve your driving technique.
\>Basically, the point is to strive to get people to call you by a 
really sharp handle\.\

### String 8 ###

I hear you can also get *\handles\* for the average speeds you get 
in a race! 
\>And since you've chosen to be a road racer, then you want handle 
that signifies the fastest speeds at least once in your career\.\

### String 9 ###

You know how you can speed up by cutting it close to walls when 
you take curves? Well, the thing is, people see when you drive 
like that, even if it does make you go faster.
\>And that kind of attention just naturally wrecks your *\handle\*. 
And having a bad handle might make you seem tough out there, 
but it's nothing to be proud of, you know?

### String 10 ###

Say, have you heard the news? 
They say that there's a *\handle\* that you can get for taking down 
every undefeated racer on the Metro Expressway. 
\>I'd like to know what that handle could be. You don't suppose 
there's anybody out there who could pull off a stunt like that, 
do you? If there is,  I'd sure like to meet him\.\

### String 11 ###

I think it's about time I changed my tires. Soft-grip tires wear
more rapidly, which makes them more costly. I suppose the way I
drive might have something to do with too, come to think of it\.\

### String 12 ###

Let me see, how many losses do I have?
Five, six, seven in a row now…
\>I'm gonna be in trouble before I know it.
They'll start using a handle for me that says, "Loser"!

### String 13 ###

You know about the racing team that claims the C1 stretch of the 
Metro as its turf? They race in both directions, so you can pick 
the one you like best when you race them\.\

### String 14 ###

About the C1 stretch: horsepower alone won't cut it there. 
That's because there's hardly any stretch where you can go flat 
out. 
\>You need a chassis that fits both you and the road conditions. 
But there are straights on the other side of the Kasumigaseki 
Tunnel. 
\>You might even be able to hit 200mph on the Akasaka Straight. If 
you get the chance, go for it. And when you do, shout out that 
you hit that speed. I owe it to me\.\

### String 15 ###

Are you wondering where the best place is to race on the C1 
inside loop? Well, different people will have different answers, 
but I like the stretch by the Ginza.
\>You can make it work for you, if you handle the struts right. If 
not, well, too bad. But if you're gonna race these roads, you 
need to find the places that work best for you\.\

### String 16 ###

I--I went on a date... with a man... the other day... We went
driving... in Hakone... in separate cars, but still... 
\>He was driving an AE86, and before I knew it, I'd left him in 
my dust... I kind of feel bad about the whole thing..\.\

### String 17 ###

You can see Tokyo Tower from the C1 loop near 
Shiba Park.
\>I mean, when you're on the inner loop, heading for 
Shiba Park. You can see different lighting on the 
Tower depending on when you drive by there.
\> 
It's an amazing sight.
Take your girlfriend over there one of these times.
You don't have a girlfriend? You're kidding!
\>Well, then, maybe I might...
Oh, uh, nothing, nothing\.\

### String 18 ###

Drivers have to do a lot of cornering on the Metro. That means 
you need to learn the lay of the land. One way to do this is to 
drive race routes before a race, to see what they're like. 
\>You know, just cruise. It's kind of fun, actually.
It's a more laid-back driving mode than usual\.\

### String 19 ###

You mean "oversteering" means turning too tight in the corners, 
so you cut into the inside lane?! 
\>I thought it was the other way round: you don't turn tight 
enough, and swing over into the outside lane! Well, well. 
\>So I had it backwards. But I've got it now!
Thanks for setting me straight on that!

### String 20 ###

I love a good turbocharger. I get chills when the
turbocharger kicks in. Unlike a supercharger, a 
turbocharger runs on car exhaust, which means the
\> 
more engine RPMs you have, the more power you get.
So it's not much use at low RPMs, because you don't 
get enough power output.
\>There's just no substitute for it at higher power 
levels, though\.\

### String 21 ###

I don't get this four-wheel drive stuff. I mean, a 
man should drive standard rear-wheel drive, like a
man, you know? You don't get that sense of drift
\> 
when taking corners at high speed with four-wheel
drive! Only rear-wheel drive gives you that! 
\>You say that doesn't apply on the Metro? I know that.
But one can still dream right?

### String 22 ###

Do you have a code about the cars you drive?
\>One rule I have is, I only drive cars with rotary 
engines. Now, that's not to rule out other fast cars,
don't get me wrong. I just think it's important to
\> 
have a personal code, that's all. You need to feel you
can trust your racing with a particular car. 
And besides, it just seems cooler that way\.\

### String 23 ###

A stern-faced Lan Evo 9.
This car mysteriously drives exactly as I wish it to.
\>It is tolerant enough to forgive any and all selfishness on my
part.
\>It has power, and moves as if it were a part of me.
It's as if the saying "Strong and kind" were made for it.
\>I'm going to have it keep listening
to my selfish requests for a long time to come. :)

### String 24 ###

This chassis moved me the moment I laid eyes on it. I thought 
the Nissan Skyline Coupe was really hot. I was walking around 
and this car caught my eye as it drove away. 
\>And that was my first encounter with the Skyline--the new model 
with the rounded taillights. Talk about love at first sight! 
\>I'd just been thinking about buying a new car, and headed 
straight to the dealership. When I took it for a test drive, 
I was amazed at its stability. 
\>It's also got a good field of view, which makes driving a 
breeze. I was impressed, in a word. This new Skyline doesn't put 
on airs. It's a pleasure to drive\.\

### String 25 ###

It exudes luxury, the sort of thing a VIP would drive. And it's 
sporty at the same time. The dual aspect of  the Aristo drew me 
like a magnet.
\>The exterior says Old World style at a glance. It's flexible; 
it'll fit in for any use you might have forit. In my case, it's 
all about the sense of luxury. 
\>It just exudes maturity, wouldn't you say? And yet, under the 
hood, it's been customized to put out better than 400 (metric) 
horsepower, with ease. That's where the Aristo really shines\.\

### String 26 ###

Do you know what LSD is? "LSD" stands for "Limited Slip 
Differential", a crucial car component, as far as driving is 
concerned. 
\>There are three kinds of LSD: one-way, 1.5-way, and two-way. The 
one-way LSD works only when a car is accelerating, while the 
two-way LSD kicks in on acceleration and deceleration alike. 
\>The 1.5-way, LSD, on the other hand, kicks in mainly when 
accelerating, but only slightly when decelerating, essentially 
midway between the one-way and two way LSDs. 
\>The thing to remember is, you have to be careful with how you 
set the LSD, because it has a significant effect on your 
driving\.\

### String 27 ###

I like controlled drifts, you know? What about you? Do you use 
two-way LSD?  It may not be all that fast, but it's such a rush 
when you hit a controlled drift just right! 
\>It's tough to do, but it's so worth it. You really need to 
outfit your car with two-way LSD if you want to make controlled 
drfts, 
\>because the tires need to spin when you decelerate as well as 
accelerate in order to get them to drift. 
\>On the other hand, you can't set the LSD ratio too high, or you 
won't be able to steer properly. So be careful how you configure 
the LSD\.\

### String 28 ###

Whenever I get my hands on a car, I
always make it as low as I can, because
I love the way it feels going over
\>train crossings. I do end up tearing up
the undercarriage, though\.\

### String 29 ###

Hey, you. How do you customize your suspension?
\>I figure you need rigid suspension if
you're going to take on the Metro. But
the older you get, the rougher that
\>starts to feel. You get bounced around,
and takes a toll on your derriere.
\>Just once, I'd like to race down that
road with soft suspension\.\

### String 30 ###

That side-to-side wobble is called "roll". That's right. When 
you take a corner, centrifugal force makes your car tilt. The 
resulting side-to-side wobble is the roll. 
\>Yes. And roll reduces your car's stability, making it harder to 
handle. To improve your car's roll resistance, make your 
stabilizers tighter Yes. 
\>You can't try to eliminate roll altogether by making them too 
stiff, though, or else your car will experience sideslip 
instead. Yes. 
\>You can get more roll by using tires with stronger gripping 
force, and if you do that, you should also tighten your 
stabilizers. Yes. Got that? Good\.\

### String 31 ###

Wow, I never thought they'd take $\Midnight Cinderella\* down.
Bitten by a venomous snake, I tell you. And there's lots of 
those on the Metro. Venomous snakes, that is\.\

### String 32 ###

Here I figured we'd be the ones to take $\Snake Eyes\* down. I never 
thought somebody else would beat us to it. 
\>This may be the end of the Phantom Nine\*, but we'll keep on 
racing anyway, until we put together the fastest racing team on 
the Metro!

### String 33 ###

I hear you took down $\Snake Eyes\*.
Thanks a million!
\>But don't take it the wrong way. I'm not saying 
you're any good, or anything like that. You just 
remember that\.\

### String 34 ###

There used to be a gang called the $\Thirteen Knights\*. They 
went around trying to take down whoever was supposed to be the 
fastest driver at any given time. 
\>Rumor even has it that $\Bloodhound\*, who's supposed to be the 
fastest on the C1 Loop by night nowadays, was part of that gang 
back in the day. 
\>So he might come after you if you prove your stuff on the C1 
Loop by night. There's no telling\.\

### String 35 ###

I heard that that race between $\Midnight Cinderella\*
and the $\Platinum Prince\* was really something
else. Seems that $\Midnight Cinderella\* is
\>planning to challenge the $\Platinum Prince\* to a 
rematch. And they might just come after you, if you 
prove you've got what it takes on the C1 Loop late at
\>night. It could happen\.\

### String 36 ###

The current titleholder of fastest racer on the Metro is a dude 
called $\Snake Eyes\*. He used to race the Metro back in the day, 
until another driver beat him in a race. 
\>Seems that after that, he went to the US to beef up his driving 
skills. Word is that he was a big wheel in American street 
racing.
\>Anyway, he came back here a year ago, and took down the eight 
fastest racers at the time, one by one. Then he made himself 
their leader, thus forming the Phantom Nine\*. 
\>The story is that he's come back to the Metro to challenge the 
driver who beat him to another race\.\

### String 37 ###

There's a three-member subgroup of Phantom Nine\* that races on 
the C1 Loop, consisting of $\Iron Old Man\*, $\Golden Wisdom\*, and the 
$\Crimson Kid\*. 
\>Collectively, they're known as the Three from Kurosaki. $\Crimson\* 
is the youngest, but they say he's already pretty good. 
\>He may look easygoing on the outside, but word is that's just an 
act to fool the composition. 
\>He's actually pretty serious when it comes to competing. He's 
their point man when they race as a group\.\

### String 38 ###

I suggest you watch yourself where the Kurosaki 
Three, a Phantom Nine\* subgroup that races on 
the C1 Loop, is concerned. $\Old Iron Man\*
\>is a thoughtful, experienced driver, as his age 
suggests. He's got a sharp mind, and knows how to
\> 
handle a car. You'll find him bringing up the rear in a
race\.\

### String 39 ###

Looks like $\King Speed\* is racing again, after meeting you. He's 
the guy they used to call the fastest racer on the Metro. If you 
actually race him, he'll give you a race you'll never forget. 
\>I used to dream of only one thing: taking him down. But I never 
got good enough for that. 
\>Instead, I'm waiting for you to blow away all the Metro racing 
teams and then throw down with King Speed yourself. And you know 
something? I think he's looking forward to that too\.\

### String 40 ###

Looks like 1\*White Charisma\*'s back on the Metro. 
He must have heard that King Speed is racing again.
\> 
They were bitter rivals five years ago, until $\King 
Speed\* ran $\Charisma White\* off the Metro. 
Then he came back when King Speed met his match.
\>Coexistence is unthinkable where those two are 
concerned.
\>Question is, which one will win out this time around? 
Or will you blow away all the C1 Loop racing teams 
and take on $\Charisma White\* yourself, instead?

### String 41 ###

There's a driver called "$\Garage Haruo\*" who comes to the Kyobashi 
Parking Area at night. I hear he's a good enough customizer to 
launch his own business. 
\>If you decide to race him, *\make sure you customize each and 
every part of your car\*, a little at a time if you have to, 
because word is that he won't race against unmodified cars\.\

### String 42 ###

$\Kamikaze Koji\*, who drives around C1 at nighttime, 
works part-time at a gasoline station, and supposedly can only 
come to The Metro every 3 days.
\>Check your dates if you want to battle him\.\

### String 43 ###

Go to the Kyobashi Parking Area late at night, and 
you'll find the $\Silent Barbarian\*. But watch out: he 
only races against *\sedans\*\.\

### String 44 ###

I hear that $\Master Position\* works as a talent scout by day, and 
right now, he's setting up Cat + Cat\* for a second career a 
entertainers, 
\>so he's popping up all over the C1 Loop by night in hopes of 
getting info on them from drivers who've raced against them\.\

### String 45 ###

$\Straight-man Breaker\* is an electrician, so he makes 
a big deal about cars with lots of lights.
\>If you want to race him, *\ctrick out your car in lights*\, 
and check out the C1 Loop around daybreak\.\

### String 46 ###

$\Bloody Mary\* hits the C1 Loop around daybreak. 
He's not the most polite driver you're likely to meet.
\>Other drivers honk their horns at him all the time. 
*\That might be why they say he hates the standard car
horn sound\*\.\

### String 47 ###

$\Dog Ears\* has the most amazing hearing. No matter how far away, 
he can pick out the sound of his favorite *\NA engine\*, 
\>and he'll dash over to the C1 Loop to race against cars running 
on them, from anywhere, at any time\.\

### String 48 ###

$\Fleetfoot Valkyrie\*, who you'll find over at the 
Kyobashi Parking Area, is addicted to fast driving. 
\>He's been known to declare that he'll only race 
against cars that can go faster than *\186mph\*\.\

### String 49 ###

$\Speed Coaster\*, who shows up frequently at the 
Kyobashi Parking Area, supposedly maintains an 
average speed of 100mph when he races. He also
\> 
makes a point of not racing against anyone who can't
 at least keep up with that, or so I've heard\.\

### String 50 ###

You're not a real Metro street racer unless you 
know who the Rolling Guys\* are. They're famous for 
being made up solely of Toyota AE86 cars. 
\>They're also renowned for being the weakest racing team on 
the Metro, where high-powered cars are the rule, 
rather than the exception (smirk)\.\

### String 51 ###

My ambition is to join the Rolling Guys\* and conquer 
the Metro with my Toyota AE86. I mean, only the best racers 
could win with an underpowered car, right? 
\>I want a rebuilt engine and a full carbon chassis!
What's that you say? What do you mean, it wouldn't 
be the same car anymore?

### String 52 ###

Changing Stage\* is kind of an oddball team. It's made 
up of editors of car magazines. 
\>So they know lots about driving theory, but aren't really that 
good behind the wheel, probably because work keeps them from 
actually getting out on the road very much. 
\>I hear they're also well informed about the state of the
Metro, as well as the various racing teams that are 
active there\.\

### String 53 ###

They used to have a car club at my college that was pretty 
well-known on the Metro. Until Speed Planet\* came along, that is, 
and wiped them out, just like that. 
\>The car club members apparently joined other 
racing teams, or so I heard\.\

### String 54 ###

Fresh Market\* is a team of lively guys who work out of the 
Tsukiji Fish Market. 
\>They're definitely at home behind the wheel, seeing as how they 
do so much driving as part of their jobs, even taking into 
account the differences between cars and trucks. 
\>They're also polite, and other racing teams think they're 
pretty good. They're most known for steady, stable driving\.\

### String 55 ###

Phase X\* is a young team. All of its members are still in their 
teens, which means they don't yet have much experience behind 
the wheel. 
\>But they make up for that in stamina and enthusiasm, as well as 
internal cohesion. 
\>Once they've got the experience to go with their vitality, I bet 
they'll be one of the top racing teams on the Metro\.\

### String 56 ###

If you see any drivers dolled up in that Gothic style,
you can bet it's Team Desire. There's only the 
three of them, but they've got a definite presence. 
\>Oh, and one of them is apparently a guy, even though 
they all look like girls\.\

### String 57 ###

Cool Energy\* is made up entirely of entrepreneurs 
with offices in prime central Tokyo real estate. 
\>And their cars are all customized to the max, as you might 
imagine. 
\>On the other hand, they tend to rely too much on their hardware, 
and the scuttlebutt is that as a result, they're only so-so as 
drivers. 
\>Their overly aggressive style puts off the old-school 
street racers\.\

### String 58 ###

You know about the best racing team on the Metro?
About the only thing anyone knows about them is that 
it's got nine expert drivers. 
\>That and, they'll give you the evil eye if you start attracting 
too much attention to yourself. So be careful out there\.\

### String 59 ###

The Pleiades\* ranks along with the better known Subaru 
Impreza racing teams. They draw on the solid 
potential of the baseline Impreza hardware to the
\> 
utmost, even on the C1 Loop. And they go at it hammer and
tongs with $\Tri-edge\*, their main rivals. 
\>Their leaders apparently have a real history, and it's
likely to be a while yet before they finally have it out\.\

### String 60 ###

Two Limit\* is a special team, whose members all 
work in the same hospital. They put the teamwork 
they've learned on the job to good use on the Metro. 
\>It makes them pretty cohesive.
\>Not only that, but they also draw on the decision 
making ability that they've cultivated practicing 
medicine behind the wheel.
\>They're a solid team of racers overall\.\

### String 61 ###

The C1 Loop is a veritable war zone early in the 
morning. Two recently formed teams are fighting it
\> 
out for supremacy there. $\Blood Tears\*, is made
up of hardcore racers, led by Undying Duelist.
\>You need more than ordinary driving skill 
and hardware to beat them\.\

### String 62 ###

There's been an upsurge in guys wanting to sign up 
with $\Harvest Waltz\*, the leader of Freedom Light\*. 
\>But he personally tests them to see if they've got 
what it takes. They say he's ruthless in the way he 
runs them out. I bet it must be hard to maintain 
\>your membership, once you manage to get it\.\

### String 63 ###

No, really, I'm not kidding, there really is a team called 
Rolling Gals\*. They're all named "Rolling Gal 1," 
"Rolling Gal 2," and so on. 
\>And they naturally all drive Toyota AE86s. 
You gotta believe me. I couldn't make this stuff up!

### String 64 ###

Not all racers compete head to head. Watch out for 
Speed Planet\*.
\>They come at you in formation: $\Drifting Striker\*, 
$\Shikki the Whiz Kid\*, and $\Grim Redpoint\*. They're 
not all that great one-on-one, but if they can form
\>up and go after you as a group, they can cause you some real
grief. You need better driving skills then it takes to win at 
head to head racing\.\

### String 65 ###

The other day, I was racing against World's 
$\Greatest Dad\*, from Family Business\*. I had it in the
bag when all of a sudden, $\Big Mama\* got into the act, 
\>saying, "You've had it!" and "This is what love can 
do!" I thought, give me a break!

### String 66 ###

I hear that $\Sleeping Lion\*, leader of The Pleiades\*, has himself 
a capable right-hand man, known as $\Number Two\*. 
\>And his job is to back up his leader, no matter what it takes, 
when his leader is in a race. 
\>Basically, $\Number Two\* draws the attention of the opponent, 
allowing $\Sleeping Lion\* to take advantage of the lapse to take 
off. 
\>Even I could rack up more wins if I had a wingman like that!

### String 67 ###

I lost out on the Metro, but I don't mind getting beat on the 
tight ones. So long as we keep our pride in driving with love 
for the Metro, we'll always be able to race there\.\

### String 68 ###

You're pretty fast, you know that? Someone as good 
as you probably has an in with all the racer girls, I bet. 
Get me some introductions, if you can\.\

### String 69 ###

You've shown me that there are still some holes in 
my racing theory.
I'll get you next time!

### String 70 ###

Timing is key, in both comedy and racing. I feel as 
though you led me by the nose in our last match\.\

### String 71 ###

You taught me just how sophisticated the street 
racing on the Metro is. I wasn't completely blown 
away though. You're going down next time we meet!

### String 72 ###

You're still rough around the edges, but I think 
you're going to get faster from here on in. Give me 
the exclusive when you get famous\.\

### String 73 ###

Let me get some pictures of your ride one of these times. 
I got a really strong vibe off of you just driving down the road 
with you, so I figure I should be able to get some good shots\.\

### String 74 ###

I've shamed my leader by losing to an
amateur like you. We'll go at it again one of
these times\.\

### String 75 ###

Ha! You only beat me because you had better CPU 
control than mine! You gadget geek racers 
are all over the place nowadays. I hate it\.\

### String 76 ###

You've got the potential to be a pretty decent driver!
Racing is OK, but what do you think of making long-
distance parcel deliveries? Come and work for me\.\

### String 77 ###

Wow! You Metro racers are something else. 
You drive like nothing I've ever seen. I hope to be 
able to drive like that, and soon\.\

### String 78 ###

I haven't had any good catches lately, because there 
are more and more good drivers on the road these 
days. Like you\.\

### String 79 ###

Now that was a good practice bout. Thanks!

### String 80 ###

Racing against you has taught me a lesson: I have a
long road ahead. I hope I can race you again sometime\.\

### String 81 ###

I thought I knew a thing or two about cars, but racing against 
you, I realize that there's still a lot that I don't know. I 
hope you'll race with me and teach me more stuff\.\

### String 82 ###

I'm not doing too well. If I don't get more wins, my 
brother is liable to outstrip me one of these days..\.\

### String 83 ###

Ha ha ha! I guess I couldn't ramp up the power when I
really needed to. Must be the used parts I picked up 
cheap\.\

### String 84 ###

Aw man, why can't I do anything right? It's the same
thing, whether at home or on the road…

### String 85 ###

Hey you. I'm not just a racer, I'm a father, too! So
don't go making me look like a such a bum, huh?

### String 86 ###

Even though we lost the race, it was fun to go 
driving with my old man for the first time in a long 
while. Thanks a lot\.\

### String 87 ###

I thought anything could be had for a price, but I 
guess that's not true where street racing is
\> 
concerned. I can't believe that you beat my expensive
car with your el cheapo ride…

### String 88 ###

I felt the G forces pressing on me, as though my 
brain was about to explode. That was the real thing. 
I finally found what I was looking for\.\

### String 89 ###

This thrill, this excitement... They'd never 
understand this back at the company. You'll see my 
real driving ability someday!

### String 90 ###

I bet even our leader would recall 
what it was like when we all drove just for the sheer
fun of it if he raced you\.\

### String 91 ###

Will I wipe out before I reach the pinnacle of 
racing the Metro? Wait and see, for I am devoting 
the rest of my life to street racing!

### String 92 ###

I couldn't blaze my own trail when I raced you. 
\>Such is the nature of defeat. You drove spectacularly, by 
comparison. You made your own way, without taking direction from 
anyone else.That's how I want to go\.\

### String 93 ###

"Theory evolves through exposure to reality, not 
through blind adherence," says our leader. I finally 
understand what those words mean, for your
\> 
driving has far outstripped my theory on the subject. 
And that is why you have won\.\

### String 94 ###

I lost the race, but I was also very calm. 
And I think that was down to you.
\> 
The way you drive freed me from my road rage.
Would you race me again sometime?

### String 95 ###

It pains me that I couldn't get the most out this 
Impreza. I thought I knew all there was to know about
it. Who would have guessed that I was wrong?
\> 
I'm liking it even more than before, though. The 
next time I race you, I hope to know it even better 
than I do now\.\

### String 96 ###

Did you get a good look at my tail slide? What? 
You didn't have time to look because you were going 
faster than I was?
\>That's messed up!

### String 97 ###

I lost... I guess I'm just too concerned with safe 
driving.
Maybe I should try being bolder with my racing
style\.\

### String 98 ###

Hmph. I can't very well chew out my leader if I get 
beaten like this. If you know any good racing teams 
out there, give me an introduction\.\

### String 99 ###

Losing a race like I just did won't set a good example 
for 1\*Mynah Bird\*. So don't tell him about it!

### String 100 ###

There wasn't even a one in a hundred chance of 
 you winning this race.
\> 
I must go straight home right away, and work out 
where I went wrong\.\

### String 101 ###

I needed to be on form to avoid causing trouble for my 
leader. And yet, I lost... I swore that I would work 
with my leader to build the fastest racing team on
\> 
the Metro. And I will race against you as many time 
as it takes to make my dream come true!

### String 102 ###

Eh? That was you driving like that? You're kidding!
\> 
That's good enough to make you a first-class stunt 
driver. I can get you work if you want it. You'd have 
all the stunt work you could handle\.\

### String 103 ###

I guess I really need my own car to go all out. 
What's that? Why don't I use my own car? Hmm... 
Good question?

### String 104 ###

You got some good numbers this time around. 
Just what I'd expect from the car that took down the 
$\Skull Bullet\*.\\

### String 105 ###

Racing against you has got my creative juices 
flowing. I'll use this in my next series of articles!

### String 106 ###

I could actually graduate at any time. I just don't 
want to. Seriously, I could! You see, I like it here, in the 
college car club. I'm gonna stay here until the end\.\

### String 107 ###

I can graduate any time I want to, really.
I just don't want to.
\>I mean, I love this car club.
\>I plan to live out my destiny to its end with this club\.\

### String 108 ###

Have you seen $\Grim Redpoint\*? I was supposed to 
loan him my notes..\.\

### String 109 ###

You Tokyo racers are good. I thought I was pretty 
fast in Nagoya, but drivers like me are the norm
around these parts. That's a depressing thought\.\

### String 110 ###

Uh-oh, I was supposed to get $\Drifting Striker\*'s 
notes. But he's not here. Now what do I do? 
I'll be left back for sure\.\

### String 111 ###

I just know that I'll get what I want someday, in both
love and street racing. Keep taking chances, that's 
what I say\.\

### String 112 ###

I'm sure there were more members when me and Kamiya first joined
this club, but now there's only 7 of us...
\>Makes you kind of lonely\.\

### String 113 ###

I took a hit from my leader. How could he spread 
false rumors about $\King Speed\* starting out in our 
college car club?

### String 114 ###

My leader took me to a "French Maid Coffee Shop" 
for the first time. I could really get into this. I couldn't 
help thinking how much I'd like to take those girls down!

### String 115 ###

Cat + Cat\*'s $\White Cat\* is a babe, but $\Black Cat\* keeps an evil eye 
out, which makes it hard to get close to $\White Cat\*. 
\>They also race together, which means there isn't much of a 
chance to get $\White Cat\* alone\.\

### String 116 ###

I met this Japanese street racer when I was in the 
US. I got taken out in my first race and he kept 
\>on winning until he got the championship title. I can't
help but think that I haven't seen the last of him\.\

### String 117 ###

You don't want to be a leader. Trust me. All it does is tire you 
out. There are no perks to the job whatsoever. I was forced into 
my leader's showdown by my predecessor, $\Bloody Rose\*. 
\>I even suspect that he took a dive because he wanted out of the 
job himself\.\

### String 118 ###

That leader showdown? Yeah, I took a dive all right. I wanted to 
retire. You see, all our team has going for it is its history.
\>We've never really gotten our racing act together. 
I feel bad for $\Golden Beast\*, I admit\.\

### String 119 ###

Aw, man! Why do we have to have $\Golden Beast\* for 
a leader? I could be a better leader than him! I can't 
stand it…

### String 120 ###

Why does it cost so much to customize a car? 
It's so expensive that I can't afford to eat anything 
better than cup ramen\.\

### String 121 ###

I hear that Max Racing\*'s $\Blue Shadow\* is having an 
affair with a female racer, and his wife has hired a 
private eye to investigate. 
\>Now this investigator is himself a really good racer. 
There's no way they'll get away from him\.\

### String 122 ###

Me and my pals $\High-speed White Blade\* and $\High-
speed Bloodraine \*are known around these parts as 
the Three $\Musketeers of the Highway\*.
\>You're not a real racer if our names don't make you 
nervous. One of these days, we'll take over Max 
Racing\*. How'd you like to join us?

### String 123 ###

Oh, knock it off already with that "*\High-speed Three 
Musketeers\*" stuff. High-speed Blue Thunder is only 
one who gets excited at hearing that. 
\>Kanno and I just don't get it\.\

### String 124 ###

Wow! Who'd-a thunk it? There was this babe in a 
Gothic-Cutie outfit at the parking area the other day.
\>I tried to chat her up, and "she" turned out to be the 
captain of my intermediate school's baseball team! I 
can't believe that this is what he's into now\.\

### String 125 ###

Oh man! I ran into a member of my old intermediate school 
baseball team at the parking area! He actually saw me dressed up 
like this! I wonder if he recognized me!

### String 126 ###

I started out in a racing team that was so lame I've forgotten 
what its name was. 
\>And I've been in a bunch of other teams since then. I was even 
on the Rings\* team for a while, but only for a few months. 
\>We just didn't get along, you see. But its leader, $\Lonely 
Jackal\*, was one helluva of driver. I don't think there's anyone 
else out there like him, on any of the other teams I've been on. 
\>I mean, they've survived challenges by the Phantom Nine\*, 
no less\.\

### String 127 ###

I won second prize in a local shopping mall raffle: a
flat-screen TV. It's usually rough always being 
second banana.
\>This was the first time that coming in second meant 
something good, you know?

### String 128 ###

Looks like $\Sangai Dasher\* is upset with $\Highway Pandemonium\*'s 
malicious driving. He's not doing it deliberately, though. 
\>He's He's even apologized for it. 
And since they're teammates, I think he ought to let it slide, 
personally\.\

### String 129 ###

$\Highway Pandemonium\*'s driving like a madman again, I see. He's 
gonna get the whole team's reputation in trouble if he keeps up 
like this. 
\>If he doesn't heed my warnings, I my have to kick him out\.\

### String 130 ###

Oh no, I did it again! I didn't mean to, but I just get 
so angry when somebody gets in my way! If this goes 
on, Freedom Light\* might come after me!

### String 131 ###

Tony's been a security guard at the hospital for more than a 
decade. He's been a friend of mine since I was in school. 
\>In fact, I've known for the longest time that he races the 
Metro. I got into street racing myself because I admired him\.\

### String 132 ###

May of my patients are street racers too, including at least one 
who could suffer physical breakdown or even death if he keeps it 
up out there. 
\>As their doctor, I naturally try to talk them into giving up 
street racing, but it's hard, because I feel myself what it 
means to him\.\

### String 133 ###

I've been working security at Hamura General 
Hospital for more than a decade now. I'll tell you, 
though: our team leader is a real son-of-a-gun. 
\>I've never seen anybody with more intense competitive 
spirit. Not even $\Snake Eyes\* can touch him\.\

### String 134 ###

As a nurse, I'm flatly opposed to racers with serious
illnesses staying staying in the game. 
\>$\The Avenging White Knight\* is an outpatient at the hospital where 
I work, and he insists that he's going to stay on the road. 
\>My thinking is, only the living can enjoy street racing. 
I just want him to get off the Metro\.\

### String 135 ###

Mr. Niigaki, who's a patient at our hospital, is an investment 
advisor for a securities firm. He's very rich, but his recent 
physical shows he's not in very good health. 
\>Despite Dr. Mitsugawa advising him to give up racing on the 
Metro, it looks as though he's still out there\.\

### String 136 ###

More and more drivers are asking me to get them introductions to 
female TV announcers, and I'm sick of it. 
\>I say they should work on themselves if they want to be more 
attractive to women, rather than try to get me to do their dirty 
work!

### String 137 ###

The way one drives varies depending on how much 
one cares about one's one's car. Only losers blame 
their cars for their lousy driving\.\

### String 138 ###

Keep a grip on yourself in the most dire circumstances, and you 
may find yourself capable of doing things you never thought you 
could do. 
\>I suspect that's why people get to this point, neuroses and all\.\

### String 139 ###

I've had a longtime rivalry with $\Undying Duelist\*, the leader of 
Blood Tears\*. We challenge one another to keep getting better.
\>And it'll likely keep going on until one of us admits he's been 
beaten by the other, I expect. There's no telling where our 
competition will ultimately end up.
\>The only thing I know for sure is that I really want to beat 
him\.\

### String 140 ###

Oh no! Bayside Typhoon is almost on! It's this show on Mini FM 
hosted by a real-world Metro street racer. That makes it really 
useful to those of us who're in the game\.\

### String 141 ###

Our leader is overly hung up on beating $\Undying Duelist\*. 
Beating Blood\* Tears is just one rung on the ladder, and I wish 
he'd figure that out already\.\

### String 142 ###

$\Harvest Waltz\* and $\Undying Duelist\*. They're awfully alike, for 
all of the fierceness of their rivalry, you know? 
\>Sometimes I even see elements of my leader in the way that 
$\Undying Duelist\* drives. Maybe it's precisely because they're so 
similar that they keep going after one another\.\

### String 143 ###

There aren't many racers who can coax maximum performance out of 
their cars. Our leader, $\Harvest Waltz\*, is one of these. Whether 
a car thrives or not ultimately depends on its driver. 
\>That is, you can customize a car all you want, but it's all for 
nothing if the driver hasn't got what it takes to draw on all 
that performance\.\

### String 144 ###

Your car's condition has a major effect on its performance. I 
don't get into a race until I think my car is 100%. 
\>And to those who think that's cowardice, let me say this: a race 
only happens once. And you'll end up regretting it afterwards if 
you go into it with less than your best, don't you think?

### String 145 ###

Just so you know, there is no such thing as a perfectly 
customized car. Every car can have faults or breakdowns, and at 
any time. The trick is getting as close to perfect as you can.
\>And that's what I think customization is all about\.\

### String 146 ###

I don't think I have enough experience yet, which is why I hope 
to catch up to the rest of the gang, and put Blood Tears\* in 
their place. Just thinking about me gives me a thrill\.\

### String 147 ###

I saw a guy run like mad and fall spectacularly down the stairs 
by the restroom back there, and toss up his soda. 
\>He caught me looking and looked himself as if he were going to 
die for a moment. Then his expression changed, as if he'd gotten 
over it, and said, "Thank you." 
\>I have no idea what he meant by that\.\

### String 148 ###

People have this perception of electronic game developers as 
being chaotic places in various respects. 
\>And as someone who works in a software house, I'd have to say 
that this is true, to one degree or another. 
\>I know, you're wondering why I would admit to working for such a 
company, if I felt that way about the work I do. 
\>Well, sometimes I agree with that sentiment, for example, when I 
see regular companies' offices on TV, 
\>and I catch myself thinking, why don't they have action figures 
on their desks, or comic magazines lying around the office?

### String 149 ###

I was holed up in the garage all day yesterday. It's fair to say 
that I do that every so often: go to the garage and check out my 
car's condition. 
\>And there's something aesthetically pleasing about looking under 
the hood, too\.\

### String 150 ###

Some racers will tell you that rear spoilers are tacky, and 
won't race cars that have them. I disagree. I think it's a 
question of personal taste\.\

### String 151 ###

The important thing in street racing is to hang in there until 
the very end. 
\>Even if you think you're beaten, you can still turn things 
around at any instant by capitalizing on your opponents' 
mistakes. 
\>On the other hand, it is also important to stay alert until the
very end, because you might make a mistake that your opponent 
can take advantage of instead\.\

### String 152 ###

I love the Metro at daybreak! Coffee in the can just 
tastes better when you drink it at the parking area, 
with the morning breeze blowing on your cheeks\.\

### String 153 ###

Sigh... I can't do it. I still don't have the courage to 
get into the race. Once again, I'm just going to watch
it go by\.\

### String 154 ###

I finally ran in my first race the other day! I also got 
blown away. Doesn't everybody start out
like that, more or less?

### String 155 ###

My car's not running too well. I'd better get a 
customizer to give it the once-over\.\

### String 156 ###

My car wasn't running well, so I took it to the Akibara Speed 
Factory. 
\>They checked it out, and now it's great! I found out later that 
their boss is apparently pretty renowned in our circles. Lots of 
street racers take their cars to him for maintenance\.\

### String 157 ###

Excuse me, but have you seen the $\Platinum Prince\*? 
I was all set to have it out with him this time for sure, only 
to have him run out on me again!

### String 158 ###

Mami has a cat to keep her company, so she won't be
alone. She calls her cat "King Speed." Funny, isn't it?
\>She says it was the handle of the guy who was the fastest racer 
on the Metro, once upon a time\.\

### String 159 ###

Hey, my gas tank's dry as a bone. Might as well go home; 
I haven't got any money to buy more gas\.\

### String 160 ###

